<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<language>
	
	<!-- Adeptus Mechanicus -->
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Analysis—Blessed Inception"/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story0BeginningDescription" value="You have fond memories of your days as a menial in the canyons of Mars and as an Tech-Acolyte on Fecundia. Decitor Cambre-Neon 7 was with you then, first as a fellow menial, then a bodyguard, now as your Skitarii Marshal. He has shared your mission, this last century. So when he confirmed that the execution protocols were finally approved and released, you eagerly began initiating the early stages.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;That mission meant you had to be absent from your post, as Magos Benedict is quick to remind you. Absent when the Ork invasion began. Absent when the Tyranids breached containment. Absent when the Adeptus Mechanicus forces—including the prized Kastelans—were scattered across the planet. Absent as Gladius Prime—once a proud Hive World—was reduced to a wasteland with barely a billion souls scrabbling in the ruins and with every Xenos and heretic battling for its remaining wealth.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But you cannot explain to Benedict. You must treat your mission as if it came from the High Lords of Terra or the Fabricator General. Indeed, the Astra Militarum or Adeptus Astartes would not even support your studies of the Tyranids, and hence must be treated as hostile—let alone your ultimate plan."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story0Stage0Description" value="But before planning, one must survive. And to survive, Cambre-Neon 7 reminds you, we must build Mars anew, here."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story0Stage1Description" value="You have taken your remaining Skitarii retinue to a derelict hive city, which will be the foundation of your Forge. You chose this location with a reason—at its heart, an ancient Titan frame left here at the time of the planet’s conquest. If resurrected, it would be unstoppable. You order Benedict to oversee its renovation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Benedict—Magos Gerontocrat Benedict Sacerdos Quo-Vadis, to say their full name—is a worry. You have suspected their loyalty ever since the rebellion on Unnunicia IV. There, in the moment of your triumph over the heretic cultists, they displayed something akin to emotion. You would have rid yourself of them, but their permissions match your own—indeed, you suspect they somehow exceed them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Archmagos, request. Production multiplication essential. One, Manufactorum Cybernetica proximity—two, production line efficiency. Approval?”"/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story0EndingDescription" value="From Archaeopter height, the sprawling Manufactoria please you—you can almost see the interlinked flow of materials from this height, with your data overlays reflecting the specialisation that drives your economic surge. The Titan may still take a lifetime to renovate, but this is a good start."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story1" value="Chapter 2: Design—Variable Reduction"/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story1BeginningDescription" value="As the Archaeopter brings you back, you look down on your new Forge—on the bismulters and the mekanvils, on the lobotomized servitors, on the properly-catechised tools, on the blessed workers lean and loyal in mind and body. And you see that it is good. Cambre-Neon 7 is still by your side and echoes that thought. “We do the Omnissiah’s work, Magos. We have built, now we must survive.”"/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story1Stage0Description" value="Survival will be a challenge—this planet is full of problems. You decide to solve those that might burgeon first: that is, eliminate hegemonizing groups before they get a chance to grow and become a threat."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story1Stage1Description" value="In the Genetor’s necrospariums, the Ork corpses are as expected. But the Tyranids… they are already adapting. Indeed, as you watch, a “dead” hormagaunt is immolated in the act of consuming most of a servitor. This is troubling. Your strategy banked on them not having a local Hive Mind, but it seems they have already grown something like one, out in the ash wastes. If your mission was different, this would be a disaster.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Benedict enters. “Tyranid excursion equals failure. Your absence, your failure. Convenient/inconvenient. Improvement required. Investigation mandated. So say All.” Their insinuations filter through the data networks, subtly altering your access—you can feel your information feeds narrowing and your control weakening as your fellow Magi agree with Benedict’s concerns.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Benedict’s lack of loyalty troubles you. Are they a traitor or just ambitious? That burst of hate and joy he displayed on Unnunicia IV was far beyond expected norms. You have never found sufficient data to reach a conclusion but now see a way to getting conclusive evidence—perhaps this increase in correlative input will lead to an over-reach by Benedict aiding your extrapolation of sensitive and guarded data?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So you pledge to set up an independent investigation of the outbreak, open protocols and feeds for all to see, and to accept the results. Benedict nods and leaves silently, accepting the proposal. The information networks loosen again as your pledge is disseminated.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Gaps in logic paths become evident to you quickly, leading to more detailed probing of the historic protocols. Why was the study of Tyranids sanctioned on a Hive world, when the risks of such a venture were so clear even from a base calculation? How did the containment fail? Most pertinently, several ancient Kastelans and their Datasmiths did survive the breach but reject your commands.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You will start your investigation there."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story1EndingDescription" value="You have enough inputs—enough rogue Tech-Priests. Now to the interrogation… Benedict is buzzing with static. If he’s capable of pleasure, this is where he takes it. You allow him to proceed."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story2" value="Chapter 3: Testing—Uncertain Inputs"/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story2BeginningDescription" value="The rogue Tech-priests were silent, no matter what technique Benedict employed (myriad methods and often… disconcerting). But vivisecting their cogitator units reveals their orders came ultimately from Mars itself and are contrary to your briefing. The Tyranids weren’t established here to research weaknesses as on Fecundia but as a failsafe defence—a weapon of last resort.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;How could anyone have cogitated positivity for the idea of utilizing the foul Xenos in this way? The notion of containing these creatures much less controlling them was unthinkable. Exploiting them against the planet itself? Or anyone seeking to conquer it? A foolhardy, destructive failsafe, if true. What could possibly be here that Earth could want to destroy so badly, to risk a new Hive Fleet on an Imperial Hive World? And how was it concealed from you? Have you been betrayed by Mars?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(Was Benedict aware?)"/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story2Stage0Description" value="It seems like you must investigate this planet more closely. For that, you need better machine spirit permissions. Your irritation bleeds into your environment, setting nearby servitors jittering, dead eyes twitching. You order your forces to bring you anything out of the ordinary, whilst you work to unlock better template permissions in the archives."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story2Stage1Description" value="As you enter the forge archives, Benedict is departing. How does he have these permissions? You barely have them! He nods and speaks as you pass. “Hive derelict—not empty. Titan databank active. Legio Venator. Discovery, secrets… Xenos. Ancient Xenos. Parallel investigation. Return shortly. Omnissiah’s benediction.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You are glad to see him go but are worried what he might have discovered in the Titan’s memory. What would that ancient machine have seen here, before it was abandoned?"/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story2EndingDescription" value="Benedict returns. He hasn’t paused to clean himself from his battles, heading straight to you, augmentations still steaming with off-coloured entrails. “T’au ambush. Scarred Ethereal leader. Captured… died silent. No data. No heresy…” (Is he… smiling?) “Parallel investigation failure. My failure. Apologies.” And he is gone, his Skitarii close behind.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Nothing? He found nothing?! You do not believe him. More, you do not trust him, or his smile. You realise now that you will never trust him. You must remove him."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story3" value="Chapter 4: Transition—Heretical Deviations"/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story3BeginningDescription" value=""/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story3Stage0Description" value="To remove a fellow Magos will not be easy. He has his own followers, his own power base. You need support—more than the simple troops of the Doctrina. As tactically sound as they are, you need more Tech-Priests like you… and to inspire them."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story3Stage1Description" value="You surreptitiously send your new aides to the locations Benedict visited but find nothing—indeed, their unsubtle interrogations of the local survivors only manage to bring the attention of a sizable Dark Mechanicus force upon you. Was Benedict in league with them?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;They are a ragtag assembly, but you learn quickly that they are not to be underestimated. A comm arrives and distracted by thoughts of Benedict’s heresy, you automatically begin decrypting it. Another mistake. A scream of machine code blasts through your ministrations and cripples your forces. They have a Warpsmith, apparently, a veteran Techmarine of the Long War…&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You systems are crippled, glitching with the Warpsmith’s overlaid message. “Machine god (2). betrayerbetrayerbetrayer. Welcome --&gt; Fallen.” You work to purge it. As it is written in the Quaestos Mechanicor, “From the mouths of heretics emit naught but foul vapours. Cut out the tongue and be clean.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You order the Warpsmith’s tongue cut out and your forces struggle to the assault."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story3EndingDescription" value="The Warpsmith lies eviscerated amidst the remains of his daemonic engines, his crushed vox still whispering “…betrayer…” You order all the heretical remains immolated and the Skitarii responsible wiped and purged from the maniples, for fear of contamination.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On your return, Decitor Cambre-Neon 7 prostrates himself before you. He found Magos Benedict leaving the city with many Skitarii and Magi. He was unable to engage, because of the Magos’ superiority in the Forge hierarchy.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Magos, he has betrayed you, whatever his reason. And he has taken himself to those who cannot know our mission—the Astra Militarum and the Adeptus Astartes. We must subjugate them all to prevent the heresy spreading.” You cannot disagree, but this is a step beyond."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story4" value="Chapter 5: Evaluation—Questoris Deployment"/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story4BeginningDescription" value="“…Archmagos heretek. Fecundia, Mars, Gladius, beyond. Evidence Attached. Extreme DEVIATION…” The message loops, over and over. Benedict claims that you plan impossible wickedness and that they are a Procurator, sent to investigate YOU. That you are connected with the Tyranid facility’s breach.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lies! All lies! You are loyal to the Omnissiah! It would be madness to release Tyranids anywhere. For safety’s sake, you block the transmissions within the Mechanicus domain. But you are glad he sent them."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story4Stage0Description" value="That’s because Cambre-Neon 7 has traced the route of the signal, to a Chapter Fortress. You must ascertain if Benedict is still there or merely routing the signal through it."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story4Stage1Description" value="The Infiltrators have located Benedict. Two key facts emerge. First, that he is preparing to flee to orbit with a key artefact taken from the Astra Militarum—an ancient device that has some level of control over the warp storms—normally fascinating in itself, and something you could take in triumph back to Mars, if that were your objective. But he can seal you in, should he get to orbit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Second, that you simply do not have the siege weaponry to assault the Fortress. Yet the noble scions of the Questoris Mechanicus await your orders—you are confident that a single Imperial Knight would crack that fortress wide open."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story4EndingDescription" value="The Marine fortress is a ruin. A pity that the Emperor’s creations were wasted so, though they were not true servants of the Omnissiah. And, more critically, Benedict escaped, although he left his artefact in the ruins of the Apothecarion.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But you do now have his data files on the planet. Irrelevant nonsense, about active Exodite technology embedded in the planet, like the artefact—something you will pay attention to when the world is yours. But here is what you were looking for—the Adeptus Astartes suspected that a shard of the C’tan Deceiver was hidden in the Astra Militarum ranks. This is your target, at last! This was what the Omnissiah sent you to find, and seize."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story5" value="Chapter 6: Implementation—And/Or Simulation"/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story5BeginningDescription" value=""/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story5Stage0Description" value="Such was the success of the Knight assault that you order renovation of the Titan frame to be stepped up, ostensibly to undo Benedict’s heretical sabotage—but you fear this is too late to aid in your true mission, the capture of this malevolent C’tan! Cambre-Neon 7 indicates that the Necrons have technology that could be used for this end… this is heresy. But the Omnissiah so commands."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story5Stage1Description" value="The Deceiver fought well. Later, long after the battle is done. You invite Decitor Cambre-Neon 7 to the ruins of the Space Marine city where you can be alone—where you can gloat. You hear him enter the fallen Apothecarion and pride overwhelms your restraint protocols. You declare that you have delivered the Deceiver shard to the Omnissiah!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Query!&gt;? Omnissiah?! HERETEK.”, a flat voice states. It is not the Decitor—it is Benedict, somehow. You try to shut him out, to signal for aid, but your commands go unanswered—his permissions exceed yours now. You feel, distantly, he has been able to take over your city without alerting you—without a shot being fired.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As your Skitarii (now Benedict’s) enter, you feel him taking ultimate control, even of you, somehow—your mechanical parts are shutting down, your ancient human organs cannot sustain you, the darkness closes about you…&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;…and in the dark, you feel the Omnissiah enter, empowered. Glory, glory, glory.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Trapped in your dying flesh, in your mind’s eye, you see the ruined Apothecarion filled with static hallelujahs. You feel joy as his body (Living metal? Chitin? Iridescent ichor? Blackstone crackling in its wake?) sways above you all. You do not know if this is in your dying mind or reality anymore—but you’d swear that the others’ screams are real. Very real.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Later, you think this is later. You are bowing to your master, the saviour of mankind, your Omnissiah. You are rejuvenated, in control again. Everything is so clear, you understand it all.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(Are you deceived?) Now to return to the Titan frame, your greatest gift to him, and rule this world at his command."/>
<entry name="AdeptusMechanicus/Story5EndingDescription" value="Errors were made. Benedict was so close to betraying you, betraying the Imperium, betraying the Omnissiah. But the Omnissiah forgives all. (This is real?)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Empowered by the consumption of the Deceiver shard, you and the Omnissiah waken the Titan’s machine spirits together. (Are you dreaming?) It steps forward, shaking the hive city from its shoulders. Your conquest of Gladius Prime begins here…"/>
	
	<!-- AstraMilitarum -->
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Life in the Guard"/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story0BeginningDescription" value="Gladius Prime had seemed an excellent placement for a senior Imperial administrator. With its rich resources and strategic location, it was both easy and prestigious to rule. For the local people, life had been by the book—until the day the planet's space stations fell flaming from the sky and the Orks descended, followed by even worse Xenos horrors. The resident Space Marine chapter stood fast but could barely hold out.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As the Commander of the reinforcing Astra Militarum forces, you landed on the planet months ago—but the unexpected reappearance of the planet's warp storms has trapped you on the surface. You've regrouped the surviving civilians and Astra Militarum troops into one city, but there are still soldiers scattered beyond the walls. We must gather them, rebuild our cities, and reclaim this planet. For the Emperor!"/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story0Stage0Description" value="Our first stage is to get the Imperium's war factories back online. In an Imperial Manufactorum, colonists can live and die without ever seeing the outside world, endlessly building war machines for the glory of mankind."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story0Stage1Description" value="We must find our scattered allies and foes. The Imperial Sentinel scout walker may be fragile, but its speed will allow us to explore the planet more quickly. Build one as soon as possible."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story0Stage2Description" value="From the safety of his sentinel, the pilot reports that surviving civilians are being hunted by the degenerate Kroot—a polymorphic Xenos species gone feral."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story0EndingDescription" value="We've established the city and secured our borders. Yet our troops are severely understrength—but that's a problem for a later time."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story1" value="Chapter 2: Rallying the Remnants"/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story1BeginningDescription" value="Though we've rebuilt our city and cleared its perimeter, our missing soldiers outside the city are still being hunted down by the foul Xenos. Through night and day, the guardsmen's desperate pleas for help dominate our Comm-links. We must gather them, rebuild our cities, and reclaim this planet. For the Emperor!"/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story1Stage0Description" value="The guardsmen are moving in small groups, surviving by using established covert warfare techniques. Contact them and recover them."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story1EndingDescription" value="With this many soldiers reclaimed, we can rest more easily behind our walls. But we must still keep reinforcing—the Xenos cannot be allowed to take this world."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story2" value="Chapter 3: A Palace Fit For A Priest"/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story2BeginningDescription" value="Among the surviving guardsmen of the expedition, we've made a lucky find—an Imperial Tech-priest of Mars. He has an idea as to what might be causing the warp storms, but our current facilities aren't sufficient for his research, nor is the location of our city propitious for the rites of the Machine God. He insists we expand our civilisation beyond these walls, then build Cogitator Stations in two cities to aid his research. With distance, he theorises that he can measure disturbances in the warp between the twin cities, and use the computing machines to locate the storm's source. With his help we can surely clear the swirling clouds of the warp and call the Imperium for aid. This plan is our best—our only—hope."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story2Stage0Description" value="Make preparations for expansion and build a Cogitator Station—the souls of the humans on this planet depend on you."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story2EndingDescription" value="The Cogitator Station stands tall above the plain, proclaiming the Emperor's might to any who might oppose it. Deep inside, the Tech-priest is building his laboratory."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story3" value="Chapter 4: Through the Storm"/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story3BeginningDescription" value="Ensconced in the subterranean workshops of the Cogitator Station, the Tech-priest has rapidly built a small army of Servitors and Skitarii, apparently to study the planet. The Astra Militarum guarding the city have been reporting strange experiments and are uneasy in his presence—but then the cult of the Machine God has always been somewhat otherworldly. Upon emerging from his workshops, he reports that the key to the warp storms seems to be the unusual artefacts that are sometimes uncovered on the surface of the planet. He insists we bring any we find to him—but many are in the hands of the Xenos. We will have to search, beg, barter or steal it from them."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story3Stage0Description" value="Each artefact is unique and highly sought-after. One of them may be the key to calming the Warp Storms—if it is, we must find it."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story3EndingDescription" value="We have found three unusual devices that fit the Tech-priest's description. Now he must research them."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story4" value="Chapter 5: Hold the Line"/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story4BeginningDescription" value="Meeting the Tech-priest has become… difficult. The soldiers around his chamber seem less to be guarding him than guarding the city against him. You meet in something like No Man's Land inside the Cogitator Station, to transfer the artefact, surrounded by armed troops and his newly-repaired Kastelan robots. The Tech-priest's cybernetic eyes glitter red as you silently hand over the strange equipment. As he turns to go, you catch his sleeve and the soldiers all freeze. “How soon can we expect results?” you ask. His vocoder hisses static and spits “soon”, before he stalks away. You leave, troubled. Soon enough you experience the results."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story4Stage0Description" value="Alarms ring throughout the city. Of all things to face, Enslavers! Warpborn horrors man has only heard of in folk tales are assaulting the city. And the Tech-priest has vanished. Survive the attack—we will deal with him soon enough."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story4EndingDescription" value="The Enslavers are vanquished, beaten back to the warp, at great cost. In the Tech-priest's abandoned chambers you find horrors beyond human ken—and an artefact that must have lured them. What was he doing? We must find him."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story5" value="Chapter 6: The Better Part of Valour"/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story5BeginningDescription" value="The Tech-priest has betrayed you—why, you don't know. Perhaps he was always loyal to Mars, perhaps the whispers of heresy penetrated his mind. Whatever the reason, he has made his escape while you were busy building palaces and battling foes. Your scouts have located his hiding place—he has installed an artefact on an offworld gunship, apparently hoping to punch through the warp storm with it. You must stop him before he does. Beware though—his Kastelan war machines are amongst the best ancient Martian technology can produce. This will be a hard fight."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story5Stage0Description" value="The Tech-priest and his machines stand ready for battle."/>
<entry name="AstraMilitarum/Story5EndingDescription" value="As you defeat the last of the Tech-priest's troops, a failsafe trigger is activated. The still part-repaired gunship detonates, activating the artefact. Across the planet, the psychically-sensitive sigh as the warp storm fades away. Your Astropaths make contact with the Astronomican again and send out a call for aid. Emperor willing, soon enough, the Imperial Navy will arrive and this planet will be reclaimed for the Imperium!"/>
	
	<!-- Chaos Space Marines -->
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Corpses for the Corpse God"/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story0BeginningDescription" value="In your ten thousand years of war, you do not remember a worse sojourn in the Warp. Following Abaddon’s 13th Black Crusade in the days after the fall of Cadia, your cruiser jumped into the Warp—and became stuck there, like a wasp in amber.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Time became unreliable. Your crew and the ship itself became infested with the stuff of the Warp, possessed or mutated, until only a handful of your troops remained intact. When the cruiser finally burst from the warp above the Imperial world of Gladius Prime, it was a demonship and your surviving troops fled to the planet below.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After so many millennia though, you know that there is purpose to this. You have been tested and survived. You know that the Dark Gods had reason to send your warband to Gladius Prime and that you must discover it, or face their wrath."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story0Stage0Description" value="To a weaker eye, the planet would look devastated, with its imperial populace demoralised. To you, it looks ripe for corruption. You start immediately."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story0Stage1Description" value="Given your labours, a Chaos Spawn was hardly the blessing you’d hoped for. The writhing beast was once your Master of Executions. Now he—it—is chained in your compound, a twisted wreck that barely survives the mutations tearing it apart and reforming from moment to moment.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your companion’s mind is gone. From its many mouths, however, he gibbers prophecy. “…the thousandth sword, the circuit completed, the gods in accord, infinity infested…” Your cultists interpret its words to warn of an Imperial attack—but, in its wake, revelation."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story0EndingDescription" value="The bound-daemonkin nailed to your throne howl to herald an arrival. Into your chamber strides the shifting Enioch, your Master of Possession. His familiars have been whispering since arriving on the planet and now talk of a great prospect for the planet, for any Lord with the power to take it. “Please the four Gods” hiss Enioch’s many voices. “And they will make this planet a fit home for a Daemon Prince.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This planet is, in some sense you don’t bother to comprehend, alive. With the aid of Enioch and the guidance of the gods, you shall take it—and hopefully ascend to Daemonhood yourself."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story1" value="Chapter 2: The Rites of Tzeentch"/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story1BeginningDescription" value="There are no mirrors in your chambers. When the gods first blessed you with mutation, you shattered them all in your pride. But you have let the frames remain, to remind you of what you have become.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As you sit alone pondering Enioch’s untrustworthy words, the empty frames fill with a fleshy eye of Tzeentch, repeating endlessly, spilling trypophobic into the plasteel walls. Soon you are observed from every wall by the God’s blinking icon made flesh."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story1Stage0Description" value="You summon your aspirant Sorcerer. She performs rituals in front of the eyes, minor sacrifices, whispers secrets to them and listens as the eyelashes whisper together a language only she understands. She claims that the god demands tribute of you. That you must learn better to change."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story1Stage1Description" value="Your sorcerer returns, more twisted than before. She says that Fateweaver has spoken to her, oracular as ever. For now, she feels you are overstepping yourself—that you should honour Tzeentch with sacrifices, simple and complex. Overstepping yourself? How dare she! You narrow your eyes, knowing who that first sacrifice should be."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story1EndingDescription" value="You finger her eye sockets idly. The sorcerer served her purpose well, even if she was an unwilling sacrifice. You hope Tzeentch enjoys the savour of the soul of one of his own.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Her skull chatters to life in your gauntleted hand and whispers in the Changer’s voice. “Your defiance is… intriguing. This planet has a heart. We must change its beat for our own.” You smile as you crush the skull. This is a good start."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story2" value="Chapter 3: The Sacrament of Nurgle"/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story2BeginningDescription" value="The Master of Possession is announced at your chambers again. Enioch enters unhelmeted and even he seems momentarily set back by the eyes staring from the walls, the shattered skull in your hand. You relay Tzeentch’s message and he smiles, sly.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Excellent. One god on side, my Lord, as far as the Changer can be trusted.” He peers closely at the blinking wall-eyes. “Our next prospect is more. Avuncular. And more obvious in his desires. All we need do is spread disease in his name, and we shall surely acquire his blessing.” An eye suddenly reveals inch-long teeth and snaps at him, before he crushes it with a fist."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story2Stage0Description" value="You dismiss him, commanding your cultists to perform the rituals of Nurgle. Soon, you hear the wails from the city-altars. Soon, flies begin landing on the eyes around you, laying eggs between frantically-fluttering lashes."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story2Stage1Description" value="The city heaves with tight-packed life, ideal for disease to spread—and your troops, already infected with Nurgle’s blight, stalk the streets like tallymen. Before nightfall, a pandemic rocks the city. Those who survive will always bear Nurgle’s blessings. As you lie, yourself feverish with a godsent malady, the fly-eaten eyes around you open like ragged mouths. A hundred throatless voices giggle a command. “Infect the swarm-god, spread disease even to the children of the Great Devourer, and receive my blessing”."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story2EndingDescription" value="You climb the corpses of the Tyranid megafauna. Such fools, the loyalists are, to fear these single-souled beasts. They die, they rot, like anything else. In the twitching heart of a flesh-building, you see the Mark of Nurgle. Bloated purple flies leave the ventricle walls and gather closely round you, a buzzing cloak. You know you have his blessing."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story3" value="Chapter 4: The Rituals of Khorne"/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story3BeginningDescription" value="Enioch stands in your chamber when you return, accompanied by a figure wreathed in technology. They’re inspecting the eye-wall, rotted and infected as it is. Before the new figure even turns, its mechatendrils and weapons are all aimed at you. A Warpsmith, then.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Enioch speaks “Two gods on side. The simplest challenge is next. All he wants is, well- You know.” He gestures at the wall, where the pustulent eyes are already bleeding. They start gushing. Flooding. Quickly the chamber is filling. The daemonkin at your throne panic as the blood rises. The blood is… green?"/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story3Stage0Description" value="The Warpsmith speaks. “Blood, #1F5429 not #67080B? Khorne 110010 fight. Orks! Located @ 52.941040, -1.174028.” Ork blood isn’t green, you know—you’ve killed enough—but you can see the reasoning. You order Enioch to start the rites of Khorne and the Warpsmith to prepare his machines for war."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story3Stage1Description" value="You have come to see what new horrors the Dark Mechanicum has created, ahead of the assault on the Orks. Instead, the Warpsmith seems intent on giving you a tour of his Infernal Fabricator. His flat machine tongue explanations of what should be unholy horrors frustrate and bore you. After he’s proudly presented the third identical soul-rending and daemon-entrapment station, you grab him by his fusion claws and crush him close.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“I don’t care.” You bellow. “Khorne doesn’t care. Nurgle doesn’t care. No-one cares. The greenskins must die! Build more daemon engines! Or-” He nods, implacable, and strides off on his mechatendrils.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Soon, you will have the forces to crush the Greenskins."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story3Stage2Description" value="The Warpsmith has worked hard, with help from the Master of Possession. With unholy ritual, infernal contracts and the lives of many slaves, he has produced serried ranks of half-daemon, half-machine monstrosities to crush the Greenskins into bloody paste for the Lord of Skulls’ pleasure. You order the assault."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story3EndingDescription" value="Your retinue stands on an escarpment, overlooking the Ork camp. The Daemon Engines are still happily stalking the few Greenskins who aren’t dead or disabled. Everywhere else is blood, pooling in the fighting pits and drops.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Ork chief is still trying to crawl towards you, even with his limbs removed. They really are rather resilient. You sigh, reach down and hack his head off. It carries on trying to bite your ankles, until Enioch kicks it into the pool of blood. As the Ork head sinks, yelling incoherent threats, a daemonic mouth forms out of gore, swallows it and bellows “BLOOD FOR THE BLOOD GOD” before collapsing. Khorne, it appears, approves."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story4" value="Chapter 5: The Liturgy of Slaanesh"/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story4BeginningDescription" value="Do you fear walking back into your chambers? Perhaps the gods are playing with you, not choosing you for ascension? No, you are a Chaos Lord, and you have no choice but to go on—to step backwards, is to demand spawnhood like the Master of Executions. That said, Enioch accompanies you in.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You step in the room. The hall is long and quiet. The eyes are quivering but shut. The floor is clear of blood and pus. Even your horrid daemonkin seem intact, purring. It all is *too* calm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Then you see why. A daemon sits on your throne. Your heart catches. Beauty personified. Alabaster skin, iridescent chitin, eyes faceted like jewels. You struggle for control at its scent, lick dry lips at the erotic curve of its impossible claws. As you struggle with yourself, the walleyes peel open and distorted tongues, limbs and organs emerge, straining for your touch."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story4Stage0Description" value="“Little lord. You want Slaanesh’s blessing, little Lord?” purrs the Enrapturess, “Come, your task is simple. Teach the machines. Teach them to suffer and to love.” Enioch groans in ecstasy and you turn to silence him with a growl. When you turn back, the room is empty once more. You slump on your skull-encrusted throne and order the rites of Slaanesh to begin."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story4Stage1Description" value="Outside your denuded chamber, the city groans in a midnight ecstasy. The Lord of Excess, She Who Thirsts owns it tonight. Every form of depravity, every torture, every transgression happens in the city streets. Your dreams are troubled, delightful. In the morning, you find a gift at your door. And the Warpsmith waiting, untouched by the lust and horror, with coordinates of a Necron tomb."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story4EndingDescription" value="You’re not sure whether you taught the Necrons to love—but you certainly taught them suffering. Trapping their soulless bodies from escape, experimenting with tortures and horrors, watching the Warpsmith cutting their fleshmetal open to hyperstimulate their pleasure centres… before this day you wouldn’t have said you could make a Necron suffer like this, couldn’t drive a Necron mad with lust.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You feel a heavy crustacean-like claw rest on your shoulder and a rush of lust. And a sultry voice whispers into your ear, “congratulations, little Lord.”"/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story5" value="Chapter 6: A True Daemon World"/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story5BeginningDescription" value="The preparations are made. The gods have all signalled your favour (and not just on the walls of your chamber). Now comes your moment.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You invoke the favour of each god in turn—Khorne, Tzeentch, Nurgle, Slaanesh. Across the surface of the planet, a great sigil of Chaos is drawn by their unholy power, encompassing the infinity circuit at the planet’s core."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story5Stage0Description" value="The final stage is to pour the spirit of a true Daemon into the machinery. Enioch’s wheedling and the Gods’ blessings have secured you the service of an ancient Daemon Prince. He is the centre of the star—the focus, upon which the Warpsmith and Master of Possession will work. Unwilling, but compelled by the gods, he aids you."/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story5Stage1Description" value="Now the ritual begins in earnest. The Master of Possession and Warpsmith know what to do. The Warpsmith’s arcane machinery attunes itself to the planet’s pylons and circuits, whilst Enioch orders cultists to each point of the star. Through blood and brute worship, you will complete the ritual and infest the Old One’s ancient defenses.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Finally, the fools of the Imperium awake to your presence. But are they too late?"/>
<entry name="ChaosSpaceMarines/Story5EndingDescription" value="Everything happens at once. Enioch’s wry face collapses into dust even as he invokes the gods. The warp swallows the Daemon Prince, purple flames immolate the praying cultists, and the Warpsmith is pulled into his arcane machinery, gibbering 1s and 0s. Only you survive, becalmed in the storm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Failure—and eternal torment—is a moment away.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But, after ten thousand years of striving and horror, you feel the gods’ touch upon you. Dark wings sprout from your back, your limbs grow monstrous. You are a newborn Daemon Prince of Chaos Undivided, howling your birth to a dying world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your freedom lasts but a second. The ritual drags you into the planet’s core, consuming the ancient spirits hiding there. You are the planet now, a true daemon world. Your unholy presence pulls it and its billion surviving souls into the Warp. There, you will torment them eternally."/>

	<!-- Drukhari -->
<entry name="Drukhari/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Portrait of an Archon"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story0BeginningDescription" value="Pink-flecked spittle mars the perfection of his lips. He is yelling in my face, enjoying the way I shrink back from the noise, tasting my scattered tears. A moment later, he is composed again, settling himself on his chair. It groans and gurgles, as an attending wrack feeds it. One of the chair’s eyes is blue. It is watching me.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“You see”, says the Archon, continuing, “You see we simply had to visit Gladius Prime. So much anguish, so many of the herd to torment. And certain treasures, like yourself.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;He pauses to inhale crimson vapour from a small skull, carved with dark cherubim. “After all, the place was pandemonium. It took the subtle moves of a tactical genius surpassing even Vect himself—I talk, of course, of myself—to recognise its potential, to tip its billions into utter misery…”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story0Stage0Description" value="“It was unfortunate, then, that I brought the trueborn, Rakien with me. Arrogant, sadistic, spoiled… a perfect tool, if he wasn’t such a fool.” The scowl distorts his whole face. “He almost ruined everything…”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story0Stage1Description" value="“As I entered the outpost, Rakien was busy with a captured Adeptus Arbites, intent on a quite delightful torment involving groxgut and a needle. 'Rakien,' I said. 'Dracon, I must interrupt your fun. Do not ignore…' I growled my next words, theatrically, I admit. '…your Archon.'&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;He dropped the nail gun then and dropped to his knees. 'My Archon. Forgive me.'&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;'Better. Now, we’ve spent rather a lot on this expedition. Must show something for it, rapidly, lest my rivals decide they’re better off in charge. Torment some chattels…? Hmm. A demonstration of force, perhaps…”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story0EndingDescription" value="“‘Master,’ said Rakien to me, leaning on his Dark Lance. We were atop my Raider barge, savouring the pain as our forces stormed the Imperial Bastion. ‘Could we not have used the existing Webway portals? Why all this expense?’&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;‘First, never question me again,’ I smiled, ‘lest you end up like them.’ Rakien glanced down at the Grotesque hanging from the hooks on the craft’s prow and nodded thoughtfully.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;‘Now.' I said, 'A certain Lord of Excess has taken an unwelcome interest in my well-being and his minions have been watching for my presence in the Real. So I have been avoiding the, ah, better-trodden paths. For a century or two.' I frowned. An athletic figure was approaching rapidly, killing as she came. I could see her perfect, sadistic smile from here. 'Perhaps I was not cautious enough.'”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story1" value="Chapter 2: Depths and Heights"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story1BeginningDescription" value="An iron grip pushes my face into warm mercury. Under and out, under and out. My lungs ache and when I scream the liquid metal rushes in, oddly flavourless, as I choke to unconsciousness."/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story1Stage0Description" value="When I come to, the Archon is wiping his hand on a flayed Votann skin and smiling broadly at me. “All that time raiding in realspace. I need regular top-ups, you know? Where was I. Oh, yes—the Succubus.”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story1Stage1Description" value="“The ynnitach Graie Loxlove had led her wyches to Gladius in the hope of defeating mighty foes. Yet she savoured even more telling me that my nemesis was on Gladius Prime. 'Whispers from Commorragh,'' She said, 'Your Perfervid friend has followed us here. And the webway is sealed behind it. Who set that lovelorn horror on your trail, I wonder…?' She smirked, pirouetted and flipped away.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;'The Perfected, Lord?' asked Rakien.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;'Halfwit! Per-fer-vid' I said. 'She Who Thirsts has found us—or rather her minion has. An oddly reasonable Chaos type who’s been bothering me for centuries. We should expect trouble…'&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As if on cue, on the horizon, dust clouds. More humans, keen to avenge their fallen kin. Expected but rather more quickly than I’d anticipated. The Perfervid was meddling already. In return for Loxlove’s taunts, I let the wyches handle them…”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story1EndingDescription" value="“Surprisingly, for wyches, there were many survivors. Unsurprisingly, my followers bickered and fought and poisoned and killed for their share. Rakien begged me for one of his own—but I handed mine to the Haemonculus, Arkanic. As I always say, ‘Never offend an ancient flesh-sculptor unless you have to’. Especially, if you can torment a minion at the same time—ah, I can still taste his injured pride, his rage, his frustration…”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story2" value="Chapter 3: Our Perfect Friend"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story2BeginningDescription" value="The Archon sips from a jewel-encrusted goblet and leans back on his chair. Its single eye looks up at him, tears running from the blue iris. “I was toying with a felled Astartes and had just cracked their fascinating sub-dermal layer, when the vox on its helmet crackled out a honeyed Terran voice. 'Are you there, Gyrthineus? Did you enjoy my present?' Of course, it was that blasted Perfervid.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I leaned down and spoke into the vox. 'Oh, Perfervid. It was simply delightful. Sisters AND Marines, such a treat. We’re tormenting them now.' I absentmindedly lashed the Marine with my agoniser as we talked.'My pleasure, darling. But don’t take too long with them. I found some new aliens, ones I’ve not seen. Little blue things, but well-equipped and with such sweet screams. I’m sending them your way, to soften you up. Will visit later, to get your soul for my Prince. Farewell for now!' The vox went dead. Like its owner, I noticed, who’d I’d… expired whilst distracted. His head rolled to the floor and I picked it up.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;'Why not simply kill this upstart mon’keigh?' began Rakien, 'Why let them manipulate us this way? First, he sends Imperials, now T’au-'. I cut him off with a taste of my agoniser, leaving him whimpering pleasantly at my feet."/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story2Stage0Description" value="'Hold your tongue!' I said. 'We are under strength and unprepared for battle, either against the T’au or the forces of She Who Thirsts. And the Perfervid means to feed all our souls to Sai'lanthresh.' As I gazed at the marine’s flayed skull, an idea formed. 'The T’au do have a flaw though. Strike for the head…'”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story2Stage1Description" value="“‘Decapitation. Figurative and literal.' I said, tossing the withered blue head to Rakien. 'Round up the other T’au for transport to Commorragh. Now what have you missed?'&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;He looked around, panicked, 'Lord, I am sor- Oh. We are observed!' On a far crest overlooking the butchered T’au compound, he saw the glint. 'Rangers! The Aeldari, here?'&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;'Your chance to impress me. Make a… deal with them.’”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story2EndingDescription" value="“'Arrogant fool!', I yelled at Rakien, lashing him. He sobbed and writhed, as much for my pleasure as from his pain. ' I meant MAKE a deal with them! Not ‘deal with them’! As much as I take joy in the humiliation of our repressed kin, we need them. To unseal the webway gates, so we can leave.' I passed the agoniser to Arkanic. 'Patch this fool up, while I deal with the remaining Craftworld scum. They will demand more, now we have killed their people.' I looked at Rakien. 'His healing… it can hurt.'”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story3" value="Chapter 4: The Way of All Flesh"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story3BeginningDescription" value="The Archon rests his exquisite jaw on his noble fist and sighs deeply. “The Perfervid’s messages had ceased, which I felt a slight frisson of sadness at—one so enjoys torment, whether giving or receiving. Hellion scouts reported that he was chasing down another prize amongst the humans, a living saint. These Slaaneshi, so fickle in their delights!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So to the Aeldari camp, beside a dormant gate of ornate wraithbone. Where you and I became acquainted for the first time, hmm. You, in your full Seer garb, with your perfect smile. Behind you, aspect warriors, an exarch poised, and an ancient Farseer casting runes. You spoke.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;'The arrogant mon’keighs have meddled with The Great Devourer,' you told me. 'Our Farseer is near to the crystal sleep. Yet she sees terrible events will befall the Craftworlds should this strain leave the planet. Thanks to your forces, we are now too weak to tackle it. You must eliminate it, then we can all return home.' You dismissed me, like a mere Wrack. And that was when I started making plans for you…” The Archon caresses my chin with a bladed finger and I feel blood begin to drip."/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story3Stage0Description" value="He turns on his heel and walks to the window. “Anyway. Those beasts without a Hive Mind? Easy prey, I thought. Little did I know how determined they were…”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story3Stage1Description" value="“Simply destroying the creatures themselves was not enough. The foolish mon’keighs who had meddled with them still knew their secrets. At least they’d make good workers for Commorragh…”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story3EndingDescription" value="“Having completed your tasks, I returned to your encampment, eager to see you again. I was planning a delightful betrayal, to defeat your warriors and spirit you all back to my fleshpits in Commorragh. To use this to rise to command of my Kabal. Little did I know what awaited me…”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story4" value="Chapter 5: The Confessions of an Ascended"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story4BeginningDescription" value="The Archon is standing now, gazing out of a tall window at the dark beauty of Commorragh’s impossible spires. He continues talking.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“All seemed well on our approach. I swept down upon your camp with my raiding forces silenced, from all sides so that none might escape. Then I noticed that the tableau was… frozen. The Aeldari figures… impaled, drained. You yourself… absent. Even the Webway gate was darkened, encased with… Blackstone?“&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Archon turns from the window, gesticulating with his goblet, dark liquid spilling across the floor. “A moment of horrible realisation struck me… but it was too late. Stepping from the corrupted gate… the Perfervid had come… and he had ascended.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Instead of the elegant Marine who had pursued me for centuries, now there stood a Daemon Prince, massive yet limber. Yet his voice was still the refined drawl of that ancient Terran noble. 'Gyrthineus, your kin are sadly consumed, for which the Prince of Pleasure has richly rewarded me. And I made this perfect trap just for you. For our final consummation.' The warp lingered about him as he strode forward, tendrils from the Noctilith gate pulling at his back."/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story4Stage0Description" value="I am no fool. So I fled, whilst he tore apart my Raiders. Our only hope was to bring down the gate and send him back to the Warp…”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story4Stage1Description" value="“'Oh, Gyrthineus.' sang the Perfervid as he faded back into the gateway, 'A mere reprieve from our affection…'&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Yet soon my Hellions reported that you still lived, my dear. I sent Rakien to fetch you, in the hope you could open the webway as promised, forgetting that idiot’s bloodthirstiness towards your kind. I must apologise for… the carnage. I would have brought all of you here, to suffer together.”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story4EndingDescription" value="“I will never tire of dead Aeldari, even against my orders. But just a handful were left alive—you, a farseer and an Exarch. I left Rakien to be chastised by the Haemonculus Arkanic yet again, whilst you were brought to my chambers.”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story5" value="Chapter 6: Ascent and Fall"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story5BeginningDescription" value="“'I am no worldsinger'. You said to me, hoarse. I had not yet touched you, though your torments had already been lengthy. 'But there is wraithbone here, as in the Crone or Exodite worlds.' You know what you told me then—of the ritual of the Young Prince, of the Deceiver’s death at Khaine’s hand, of how the Daemon had compromised your access to the webway. Of how the Necrons had claimed the Avatar’s chambers…”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story5Stage0Description" value="“I listened to Rakien’s delicious shrieks, as the Haemonculus worked on him, and a plan came to mind.”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story5Stage1Description" value="&lt;br/&gt;“Remember that sweet moment? When we stood outside the Avatar’s Chamber. You and the farseer, voices still raw from screaming, struck up a battle hymn and my Incubi guards joined in. The Dracon and Exarch were there too, chained together. 'Rakien,' I said, smiling innocently, 'Head in there, would you?' I pointed to the rust-red door.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;'Archon!' he gasped. 'I- that would be certain death. What have I-?' You and the seer spread some sweet-smelling gunk on the two of them, and began the carving of the runes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;'Oh, my boy. I may affect a certain effete dissolution, but I have survived Commorragh for centuries. I know your idiot role is an act. I know you hate me and want to replace me. And I know that you told the Perfervid where to find me. Now, you either go in there or you die out here. Slowly.'&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Do you remember his face? As his mask fell, horror and anger raged across his face. He moved towards me and the Incubi about us raised their klaives. He stopped.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;'I- well-played, Archon. Father… Your rivals would have given me your place. I hope Slaanesh takes all time to consume your soul.' He strode calmly into the chamber, the Exarch following, carrying the Suin Daellae. The doors shut behind them. I was so proud of him—in that moment he was a true Drukhari. But my fellow Archons plotting so openly? That was troubling.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Then an age of your incessant chanting and, ahhh. That terrible cry. Slowly the doors opened and out strode the avatar, Kaela Mensha Khaine. The Incubi knelt to it, worshipful. You did not see but, as it passed me, it turned its head. I could see no recognition in its metal eyes, only molten hatred.”"/>
<entry name="Drukhari/Story5EndingDescription" value="“And that was it!” guffaws Archon Roche, triumphantly. “Khaine consumed the Perfervid, I returned here with a planet to raid at will and with you, my prize. We rarely capture a warlock. Of course, before I display you to high society, certain changes will be necessary—we can’t have you calling down She Who Thirsts upon us here…”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;He beckons to the fleshcrafter then pauses, looking at his arm, as it jerks and freezes. His eyes bulge, then quickly settle, resigned. “I- ah. A subtle poison. Intense, bypassed my wards. When I cut you?”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I stand from the chair, shedding the loose chains, Warlock garb and affected terror. “In my false tears, Duke Roche. A paralytic from a female Catachan Devil barb.” I bow, deeply.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;His face is seizing now, as Arkanic advances on him. “Loxlove! Superb disguise. Arkanic’s support I presume.” He is struggling to get his final words out. “Wh-who-?”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Why, everyone, dear. Too loud was your boasting against our Dark Muse, too great your success for your fellow Archons of the Kabal. And bringing a forbidden seer to Commorragh,” I bow, deeply, “endangering us all… that was the justification for your fall, of course. A lifetime as a Grotesque awaits…”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I allow Arkanic and his wracks to take Roche so that he might be fleshcrafted into a humbler form. Then I seat myself into the warmth of his living chair and sample his crimson vapours. A fine vintage indeed… It is good to be back in Commorragh."/>

	<!-- Eldar -->
<entry name="Eldar/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Through the Webway"/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story0BeginningDescription" value="The Black Council of the Black Library sent a messenger. To us, on our isolated Craftworld. A silent Solitaire, who laid alien cards before me, the Imperial Tarot. The Emperor. The Ace of Swords.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;An Imperial colony then, I thought. As if in response to my thought, the Solitaire spread an array—near all the deck, entangled and enmeshed. War, I thought. Total war.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Then a final three, atop the pile. The Blind Seer. And The Lord of Swords. The Lightning Tower. Ha, that is myself, I said, distracted. And this—what is this?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In asking, I doomed myself. All my kind know that you do not question a Solitaire and live. But questions of such importance demand answers.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We closed the great doors on my craftworld and kin, then. The Solitaire performed for me alone and I learned of the Hundredth Sword of Vaul on Gladius Prime. The skeins of fate spelled my death, of course—but augured a slim chance of securing the Sword, whatever it is. That was within our power and worth my loss."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story0Stage0Description" value="Yet the moment that I stepped through the Webway gate I sensed the wrongness of this world, this Gladius. It teemed with life—half the galaxy’s races were here—yet war saturated its surface. It was the Bloody-Handed God’s place so I sent to the Craftworlds for one of his own—an Autarch."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story0Stage1Description" value="The Autaurch arrived, his far-seeing eyes already judging the maps and simulations presented to him. He laughed, half with despair, half with delight (I miss that laugh now). “Enslavers! Orks! Devils! Seer, I declare we shall have to fight every creature that ever graced a deathworld’s forecourt. With whom should we dance first, do you think? Perhaps the T’au?” I indicated the grey-black spheres in the holo and his face fell. “Umbra? Why am I not surprised to find them here?”"/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story0EndingDescription" value="As the strange shadow creature faded, an intense pain suffused me and with it a vision. A humanoid figure rent asunder… a sibilant voice whispering ‘linger’… and a pull on my soul, of the Ancient Enemy, the Unnamed herself. More horrors were yet to come."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story1" value="Chapter 2: Anaris, Lost and Found"/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story1BeginningDescription" value="At our gates, a dusty ranger presented herself. Aerl Longsight, sometime of the Path of the Outcast. She had arrived here before the Ork invasion and Warp Storms and discovered an ancient device girdling the planet, beneath the hive cities. Her investigations were interrupted by waking Necrons so she’d sent word for our aid, to continue her research and bury the tomb world before it awoke fully."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story1Stage0Description" value="Her suggestion was that we should investigate a dormant tomb beneath a minor Tyranid hive nearby."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story1EndingDescription" value="Aerl reported that the glyphs sealing the tomb were old—perhaps older even than the Aeldari—and that they called this world Anaris, that is ‘dawn’s light’. In our stories, Anaris was the name of the Hundredth Sword of Vaul, wielded by the smith god of legend. “We came to find the sword.” said the Autarch, frowning. “But is this sword a planet or a prison or a weapon? Whatever, I long to wield it.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is hard to disentangle our history from myth. We believe that the Old Ones created us to defeat the soulless Necrons and Yngir—the C’tan. We also believe that the gods Isha and Kurnous bore us into this world and loved us. In our history, we know that our creation triggered the Enslaver plague and the death of the Old Ones. In our myths, we know that Khaine tried to destroy us because we threatened the gods.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Perhaps these events were the same events. Perhaps it was here that Vaul stood against Khaine, having bound this Necron tomb world in defeat. Perhaps it was here he himself was ‘bound to his anvil’. The autarch found my reasoning specious, but we agreed that we must seize the blade before our enemies could."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story2" value="Chapter 3: The Oubliette of Heaven"/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story2BeginningDescription" value="Aerl and her rangers reported spirit stones were scattered across a large swathe of the planet’s surface. They were unlike others I’d seen—imperfect, highly variable, mostly non-functional and uniformly empty—like experiments searching for the right form. Most importantly, they shouldn’t have been here—they’re only found on Crone Worlds, in the heart of our dead empire."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story2Stage0Description" value="Our myths say that the smith god Vaul created spirit stones from the tears of our mother Isha who used them to secretly commune with her children. Found amidst these precursor stones are other wraithbone devices, similarly variable. I asked the bonesingers and spiritseers to collect them and experiment with them—cautiously, of course."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story2Stage1Description" value="Now that we had the devices it was clear that they are beyond our craft—they are impossibly perfect. From the few working ones we could ascertain that this planet is a prison. The Warp Storms are its bars, the sentinel devices are its guards. It was built to trap the Necrons. But it was more than that—we could see it was an oubliette too, housing something that needed to be forgotten. Who was it that was sealed here for 60 million years? Who was the guard, who the prisoner?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Whilst we investigated, the Necrons sensed our presence at their silent tomb and swiftly raised an army against us. The autarch led our forces, whilst I manipulated the ancient devices to our aid."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story2EndingDescription" value="With the aid of these devices, we defeated the Necrons. Their shattered forms were a strange type, not as advanced in their metal physiology as those we battled elsewhere in the modern era. They must have fallen early in the War in Heaven and been trapped here. What a thing, to know nothing of the past sixty million years! To know nothing of our fall, of the rise of She Who Thirsts and her kin!"/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story3" value="Chapter 4: The Anvil God"/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story3BeginningDescription" value="With the Necron threat in abeyance, Aerl identified a nexus, near the surface, where I could commune with the planetary device."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story3Stage0Description" value="It was infested by a younger race, already set on learning its secrets. Their extermination was a necessity."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story3Stage1Description" value="Something in the infinity circuit whispered to me. I was not used to how… unified it is. It felt like a single personality rather than the millions of souls I knew from a Craftworld’s circuits. Perhaps sixty million years alone had amalgamated them… or it had always been alone. It had certainly become confused, tongue-tied… difficult.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Yet it told me slivers of its past. That it fought the Necrons. That it defeated them, here. That the Old Ones lost because they lacked the ‘final sword’. That Vaul was already bound. That a fragment of the god—Khaine—fell here and slept. That he needs waking to free the planet.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We determined to raise him from his slumber. But we first needed to deal with a nascent chaos threat, that was attempting to corrupt the infinity circuits themselves."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story3EndingDescription" value="The spiritseers and I saw the abomination of the Chaos design—the sacrifice of so many lives and so much suffering to imbue one of their devil-gods into the planet—but also, darkly, something of its potential. If we could eliminate opposition, we reasoned, we could achieve something similar with the device—to turn Anaris into something like an Exodite world, but with these unique defenses…"/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story4" value="Chapter 5: Cegorach’s Twin"/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story4BeginningDescription" value="We began the ritual. We select the Young King from the Exarchs, mounted the wraithbone garland on his brow, sent him naked into the chamber."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story4Stage0Description" value="Waited days until the screams had died. And waited."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story4Stage1Description" value="I was holding vigil outside the Shrine of Khaine, for the Avatar to emerge, communing with the infinity circuit again. A hand fell on my shoulder—the Solitaire. How strange to see them here. And then they melted into Aerl. Then into the Autarch, a human techpriest, a warpsmith, an Ork Mek… myself, bent beneath wisdom and years. Not-I smirked. In a voice that could swallow sun-spots, it leered. “Not wise to be alone, little Seer.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For a moment, I was confused. Then I was lying on my side, rolled away from the melted Shrine doors. Kaela Mensha Khaine stood where I knelt, a hand of molten blood and metal grasping my double by its neck. It writhed, fought, melted in the Avatar’s grasp and a long twisted figure of golden energy was there, a wicked smile gracing a mocking Aeldari face, as it struggled with the bloody-handed god.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The war wasn’t lost because of the sword. It was lost because the gods fought amongst themselves. And standing before us was the Jackal God, Cegorach’s dark double, he who sows dissent. The Yngir or C’tan called Mephet'ran. The Deceiver. It fled then, a battle of immortal gods laying waste to the chambers, and the Avatar pursued it."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story4EndingDescription" value="Anaris’ Avatar of Khaine slaughtered the weakened C’tan and its forces alongside me, its Suin Daellae dripping gore constantly. It talked whilst it fought, in a way that no Avatar had before—in its howl of bloodlust it revealed secrets, history, things it knew I could never tell my people. From that moment, I have spoken to no-one for fear of revealing the horrors in a weakened moment. Those tales must die with me."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story5" value="Chapter 6: Umbra"/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story5BeginningDescription" value="Despite the newfound wisdom, I was still full of questions. Was it here, then that the War in Heaven was lost? When Vaul and Khaine fought and the pantheon took sides, was the Deceiver whispering in the gods’ ears? Was this planet meant to be a model for the Necrons’ ultimate defeat? I knew that then I would have to descend into the planet and become one with it, to learn truly. To give answers back."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story5Stage0Description" value="Before that time, the spirit had to test us. To see if we Aeldari were still worthy of waking it. It sent foes against us, ritually. To re-enact the battle of Eldanesh and Ulthanesh, Vaul and Khaine, Khaine and Slaanesh. To judge me worthy. The Umbra came too and I had a sudden moment of realisation that they have the same psychic scent about them as Khaine and the World Spirit did—of the ancient wonders that predated our race. Who they once were—an Old One? A C’tan? These secrets await, below."/>
<entry name="Eldar/Story5EndingDescription" value="I write this before I descend into Anaris’ core. Suffice to say, we were victorious and the planet is in our grasp. We are exterminating the other races and departing ourselves. Only the seers and wraiths will stay, to witness this. The full activation of these great infinity circuits, to see what this planet is capable of when fully awake! I hunger to know what it is—what has been trapped inside since the War in Heaven. Is it Vaul? Is it the first among the Aeldari? Is it something else? Already I feel the crystal change coming upon me."/>
	
	<!-- Necrons -->
<entry name="Necrons/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Scourge of the Old Ones"/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story0BeginningDescription" value="As the proud leader of a Necrontyr dynasty, you'd never known defeat. Never, until your people met the Old Ones, and dared to attack their star-spanning empire. Your dynasty had been on the frontline when the war with the Old Ones started, and you were some of the first to face their wrath. Your Fringeworlds were scoured and your Coreworlds besieged for generations. When the C'tan called the Messenger—and now the Deceiver—promised your people immortality through biotransference into undying machine bodies, you snatched at it greedily. Later, you betrayed him and his kind, shattering them into C'tan shards now used as weapons.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To no avail, sadly. Though your new soulless bodies were nigh-indestructible, even as their empire collapsed the Old Ones encircled your crownworld and used their uncanny powers to trap you within it, driving their warp technology into its surface, binding you to the depths. You retreated to the underground stasis tombs that Szarekh, the Silent King, had ordered constructed, and waited for the final assault—which never came. Eventually, you slept, awaiting the Silent King's call.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Now, sixty million years have passed and you've awoken into… chaos. Signs of battle between the Old Ones' humanoid creations litter the surface, as do the ancient enemy's traps. These devastated your people upon awakening, leaving a few surviving tombs widely scattered. Through the warp storm, you can hear nothing from your overlord Szarekh.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Where are the Old Ones? Who won the war? Is this another trap? Where are your C'tan gods? We must investigate—cautiously."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story0Stage0Description" value="Our first task is to quickly wake a cohort, to defend against the Old One's forces."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story0Stage1Description" value="The living have spread across this world like weeds—particularly the virulent humans, the Old One's final curse, whose primitive dwellings cover the surface. Enslave them if you can, exterminate them if you cannot."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story0Stage2Description" value="A human leader cursed us as he lay dying, and revealed in his ignorance the location of one of our retreats. We must see if our brethren still live."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story0EndingDescription" value="Only a Necron could tell that this tomb was breached from the outside and resealed. Who or what waits for us inside?"/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story1" value="Chapter 2: Messenger From the Past"/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story1BeginningDescription" value="One of the tombs holds a Triarch Praetorian called Eystan—a Necron judge. However, he is not of our dynasty, but instead a traveller who became trapped here, long after our slumber began. He tells us that after we destroyed our C'tan gods at the orders of the Silent King, we were victorious in the War in Heaven, crushing the Old Ones. Afterwards we slept, weakened by battle. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In those dying days, Eystan's group had been dispatched into the webway to lead an invasion of Old One homeworlds—but he lost his way in the maze and became stranded on our world when the Webway collapsed. He forced his way into the tomb's entrance, but with no way to enter it proper, has spent sixty million years alone, listening to the waking galaxy. This obfuscating warp storm is a new phenomenon—he believes intended to trap us here."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story1Stage0Description" value="Eystan thinks he knows a way off the planet, involving the fragmented Webway portals—but it involves awakening a Cryptek of our dynasty. Fortunately, our records indicate that a chronomancer Cryptek loyal to the dynasty was entombed nearby."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story1Stage1Description" value="It will take some time for the Cryptek's delicate mental machinery to recover fully from the long sleep—but we can accelerate the process by exposure to the world outside, and to battle."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story1EndingDescription" value="The Cryptek, Ptanotek, is fully recovered and as keen as anyone else to discover Eystan's putative Webway escape route. But her instruments show something unusual in a distant tomb—Necrons who respond to no signals, who are massacring everything they come across, be they beast, man, or Necron…"/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story2" value="Chapter 3: Fragments of the Destroyer"/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story2BeginningDescription" value="When we slew our star-gods, the C’tan, they didn’t die easily. After all, they were fundamental parts of the universe who had achieved sentience—they couldn’t be truly annihilated, only atomised and trapped, lest they re-coalesce. And some C’tan left a curse at the moment of their death, like Llandu'gors’ Flayer disease that drives so many of our warriors to madness.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Destroyer Cults—which have sprung up on the peripheries of our cities too—are another reflection of the C’tan’s curse. These nihilists are drawn from the best of us—Immortals, Lychguard and Lords—and in their madness, seek only the death of all life.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But whilst we can communicate with our local cults, this maddened army is incommunicate and kills isolated Necrons alongside the living. We must stop them, if we can."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story2Stage0Description" value="The rebel Necrons have formed into an army, led by a formidable Lord. Let us tackle them carefully, when we are ready."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story2EndingDescription" value="What a loss—your people, turned to such mindless horrors. Eystan reports that many such dooms have befallen the Necron people since awakening, for daring to raise their hands against their gods."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story3" value="Chapter 4: Vaul's Anvil"/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story3BeginningDescription" value="Ptanotek, the Cryptek, has studied the warp storm and come to a conclusion—the Old One technology that maintains the storm is embedded in this planet. The machine that built it is surely here too. If we can find it, she's sure that she can reverse-engineer its technology, and perhaps dissipate the Warp Storm.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;That might be harder than it sounds. For, in the intervening millennia, Aeldari, Man, Ork, Jokaero and stranger creatures have left their creations on your Crownworld's surface, and cannibalised the Old One's technology. Gather their artefacts for the Cryptek to study, and we may be able to find the mechanism by which to control the Old One machinery."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story3Stage0Description" value="These artefacts range from palm-sized devices to floating monoliths taller than a Tomb Stalker, but the Cryptek insists they are all useful."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story3EndingDescription" value="The Cryptek Ptanotek looks at the gathered primitive treasures with hungry eyes. Examining the artefacts, she takes an ancient piece from each and rapidly rebuilds a giant Old One artefact, which she asserts could control the storms. Silencing the Cryptek’s protests, Eystan volunteers to test it, far from the city—and you agree."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story4" value="Chapter 5: A Messenger Revealed"/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story4BeginningDescription" value="Eystan has been gone only a short time, the mountainous artefact floating behind, when the Cryptek demands an audience. Her Scarabs enter en masse with her, prompting your Lychguard to gather about you defensively. Instead of conflict, though, the Scarabs bring something else.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ptanotek explains her scarabs were exploring a long-destroyed Old One habitat, when they happened on some unusual remains. Before she could personally investigate, her scarabs were driven off by the Psychneuein which had infested the ruin.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But they did manage to recover one thing—she presents you with a Rod of Covenant, a traditional Praetorian weapon. One that absolutely should not have been in an Old One ruin. What is going on?"/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story4Stage0Description" value="The Cryptek demands that she investigate the Old One building personally—and you agree."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story4Stage1Description" value="Under the building is an Old One vault, with human and Necron tracks leading to its sealed door. The Cryptek can unseal it—but it will take time."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story4EndingDescription" value="You personally attend the vault's opening. Inside the ruin, you discover long-dead remains—human warriors and a group of Triarch Praetorians, including a mangled corpse that is visibly Eystan's. Yet you saw him right before the Cryptek discovered this vault—or something that looked like him, at least."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story5" value="Chapter 6: The Silent King's Secret"/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story5BeginningDescription" value="Eystan communicates with you—or, rather, the thing that pretended to be Eystan does. It is a transcendent shard of Mephet'ran, the Messenger, the Deceiver, the same C'tan who doomed your people to these metal bodies with its mellifluous lies. Around it stands a legion of your fellow Necrons, blank-eyed like the Destroyers you defeated before.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In Eystan's tortured voice, Mephet'ran gloats that you have handed it the keys to the Old One's technology, and invites you to submit to your ancient masters. You cut off the communication in despair.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your Cryptek has her own secrets, however. From a hidden stasis tomb, a Spyder raises a cherished gift from the Silent King, saved from the days of rebellion—an Aeonic device explicitly made to kill a C'tan. If we can recover the control device and use the Old One and Silent King's technology side by side, we can crush this hubristic C'tan.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And once we've shown the other races of this planet that we can crush even a Star God, surely they will fall in line too."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story5Stage0Description" value="Shortly, Doom Scythe scouts report that the arrogant C'tan has left the control device with an army of his soulless Necrons. A lightning raid with your full force should be sufficient to drive them off and reclaim it."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story5Stage1Description" value="Rather than dissipate the warp storm, the Cryptek plans to ramp it up, so much so that the atmosphere crackles. This will burn away at everything physical—with the solely-physical C'tan affected most of all."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story5Stage2Description" value="The C'tan too late realises its error and, burning with the Old Ones' energies, orders its soulless armies to attack. If you can defeat it, you will cow the slave races by making them witness a god's destruction."/>
<entry name="Necrons/Story5EndingDescription" value="The Cryptek deploys her Aeonic weapon, and the thing that killed Eystan one moment screams incoherently and the next whimpers, its incomprehensible intelligence splintered a hundred-fold into Tesseract Vaults under your command.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Knowing now that Eystan was The Messenger, you know that everything he told you was almost certainly a lie—his tales of the war in heaven, the fall of the Old Ones and so on. After all, to think that the Necrons could have defeated both the Old Ones and the C’tan is beyond comprehension.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So, beyond the warp storm, the Old Ones doubtless still rule—but here, you shall stay safe inside this defensive tempest they have so kindly created. This shall remain a true planet of the Necrons, with you ruling over these mortal slaves until such day as you are strong enough to challenge the galaxy once again."/>
		
	<!-- Orks -->
<entry name="Orks/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Boyz is Bored"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story0BeginningDescription" value="“Zogging Gork, that 'urt!” You dig yourself out of the wreckage of your Boss Tower and see a few boyz around you doing the same—but very few, injured and demoralised. An old Dok, Bonez, stomps his way through the rubble towards you. “Most of the boyz is dead, boss. That zogging storm got 'em. Plenty of spare bitz though.” He hefts a detached Ork arm in his hand thoughtfully. “Anyhow, as the only Dok still standin', I reckon yer boyz could do with some R&amp;R. I prescribe 'physikal exercize'. Should fix 'em up nicely!” He grins a mouthful of steel teeth at you. “RIGHT” you bellow at your boyz. “Who wants a fight?” Ragged cheers greet you from across the camp."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story0Stage0Description" value="Getting your Waaagh! going again means getting into fights—and lots of them. Thankfully, that's what Orks do best."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story0Stage1Description" value="Now the boyz are back in action, we need to feed them up and recruit more. Better fungus solves both problems."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story0EndingDescription" value="The boyz are happy and your Waaagh! is back on track. Now to find a real fight…"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story1" value="Chapter 2: Headz-a-Poppin"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story1BeginningDescription" value="“'Ere Boss, look at this.” says Dok, indicating that the two nervous boyz with him should bring their wriggling sack into your rebuilt Boss Tower. They drop it on the floor and back away rapidly. “Wossat? A big Faceeater? A mushling?” you ask, kicking the sack. “Naw, it's just Wurrrdred.” Bonez answers, as an Ork lurches howling out of the sack's mouth, his eyes fizzing. A dangerous tension builds in your head as the greenskin psyker gets near. You shove him back, knocking him on his backside. “The other Weirdboyz' 'eds all popped inna storm.” says Dok, “and 'e says he can feel the fing wot did it.” Wurrrdred nods, and drools. “It's a Gork fing,” he gibbers “I swears it. Maybe Mork. Right near too.” You scowl at the cowering Ork Psyker. “Mork, my arse. Grab some boyz and go lookit what it really is.” Your boot helps him out of the door."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story1Stage0Description" value="Wurrrdred isn't quite sure where the Fing is. But if he wanders about a bit and your boyz can clear out any nearby psychic pollution, he's sure he can track it down."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story1EndingDescription" value="Nearby can be heard the sounds of Ork celebration—cheering, gunfire and the occasional scream of a grot. Wurrrdred, however, is wandering, his Warp-addled mind restless amidst the Imperial ruins. He squats down by a seemingly-inconsequential rock, sniffs at it, then presses his hand into a crack. A great chasm opens up before him, plunging into the depths of the planet. “Erk,” he mumbles to himself, dropping pebbles into it, “Wot's dis fing?”"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story2" value="Chapter 3: Wot's Dis Fing?"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story2BeginningDescription" value="You're standing on a hilltop, watching a Mek kicking an engine the size of a Hive block. The aeons-old space hulk that brought you to this planet was grounded by the warp storm and terribly damaged. Your few remaining Meks are putting their heads together to fix it, hoping that you can get off-planet and continue your Waaagh! away from this murderous storm. Because, as Bonez said, “Even Orks can't fight da sky!” As you watch, the Mek's banging triggers something it shouldn't. The giant engine suddenly hiccups, flash-frying him and a nearby herd of Squigs.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You're gnawing on your fourth flambeed Squig when Wurrrdred and his entourage bring the good news. They've found the Gork and Mork gubbins—sort of."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story2Stage0Description" value="Wurrrdred has in fact found the entrance to an underground labyrinth, which must riddle the entire world. You'll need a base much closer, in order to both explore and defend it."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story2Stage1Description" value="What the zog… You've barely built your brand new fort when a bunch of humies arrive. They don't seem happy, but you're not sure why. Never mind, fighting them will keep the boyz busy while the grotz and Meks explore the tunnels."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story2EndingDescription" value="When the humie assault ends, you turn your attention to the labyrinth again, where a few survivors are trickling out. The snots and grots that went underground with the Meks are mostly gone—burned or torn apart by robot horrors and traps—but the Meks themselves have survived and emerged with ancient technology galore."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story3" value="Chapter 4: Da Keyz, Da Secretz"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story3BeginningDescription" value="Oddgub, the most unhinged of your Meks, is bouncing with glee. “It iz somefing Gorky or Morky, it really iz.” You glare at his burnt hair squigs and the gouges torn into his armour by the tin'edz in the depths, and give him a good whack to calm him down. Later, when he comes round, he explains. “Dunno what 'alf this gubbinz is, but some bits'll make the hulk go faster than any enjinn I can make. Get us off this rok, fer sure. Just, uh…” he trails off, looking nervously at your power claw, and backs off. “We ain't got no keyz!” He's already running when you start shouting."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story3Stage0Description" value="Your patience isn't infinite. Just gather as much as ancient junk as you can, then see if the Keyz are in there somewhere."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story3EndingDescription" value="Oddgub is about to start rooting through the mound of ancient junk and artefacts your boyz have collected when the Weirdboy Wurrrdred runs into the room, yelling, pursued by his minders. He dives into the pile gibbering, and when they pull him out, there's a small artefact stuck in his ear—a series of silver spikes accompanied by a pair of stippled cubes. Oddgub pulls it out and dangles it in front of you. “Da Keyz!”"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story4" value="Chapter 5: Red Wunz Go Fasta"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story4BeginningDescription" value="The ancient engine bitz look incongruously tiny and insignificant when welded to the edge of your giant hulk, but the Meks, learning from their mistakes, are taking no risks. A lone grot is dispatched to hammer on the engines, in the hope of triggering them. As he strikes his first blow, the ancient devices tremble and inch the hulk clear of the ground. The grot's cheers are curtailed by the hulk slamming back down, atomising him in the blast wave.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Standing on a distant hilltop, you get back on your feet with a big grin on your face—your Waaagh! isn't going to end on this mudball. Now you only have to work out how to get through the warp storm without being torn apart by daemonic horrors. Oddgub has a cunning plan though. All the Hulk needs is to be a bit faster. And what goes fastest? “Red wunz.”"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story4Stage0Description" value="You don't have enough red paint by far. And most of the paint squigs died in the warp storm, so it'll be months before there are more. But the humies have probably got tons of it in their city. Failing all else, they ooze red when you hit them. Why not, uh, ask them nicely for some?"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story4EndingDescription" value="As you sit on the wreckage of an armoured vehicle, the humie city burns in the distance. One of Bonez' grot orderlies is stitching your ear back on, with understandable caution. Bonez and Oddgub are managing the collection of the red stuff from the humies. Even with a missing ear, it's pretty noisy."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story5" value="Chapter 6: Bad Moon Rising"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story5BeginningDescription" value="All is ready. The Meks have tested the engines, the hulk has been painted a particularly bloody shade of scarlet, and all the Orks in the Waaagh! believe it's going to work. Now you just have to move the moon-sized ship to a good launch spot for what Oddgub calls the right 'lunch tragedy' and hit the big red button. And tie Wurrrdred to the front for luck.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bonez sidles up. “Boss, gud news. Da humies and tin'edz and da rest wanna get a lift.” He dodges your fist as you roar “WATT?! ZOG 'EM ALL.” He grins. “'zactly. We're gonna get wun last fight. Figgered you'd like that.” You drop your fist and order your grots to bring your biggest shootaz and choppas and mega armour…"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story5Stage0Description" value="Oddgub and the Meks say we need to move the hulk before we can take off. The Runtherdz have the ideal thing…"/>
<entry name="Orks/Story5Stage1Description" value="The Squiggoth starts to drag the hulk into position. Now you just have to kill anyone who comes close. “Zog ‘em all!”."/>
<entry name="Orks/Story5EndingDescription" value="Tied to the tip of the hulk, Wurrrdred is practically glowing with accumulated Waaagh! energy from the ongoing battle below. You're the last to clamber aboard, still firing, reluctant to leave any enemy still standing. You signal to Oddgub to press the Big Red Button. Throughout the vast mass of shattered ships that make up the hulk, every engine fires—from the smallest Rogue Trader scout to kustom Orky engines to the Gorky silent liftaz. The battlefield beneath you is cleared of life in the blast, as you spiral up to the storm—with Wurrrdred's Waaagh-charged head clearing a path through it out to the stars, twinkling with the promise of endless war."/>
	
	<!-- Sisters of Battle -->
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story0" value="Chapter 1: The Book of Vandire"/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story0BeginningDescription" value="And in those days, the warriors of the Adepta Sororitas did walk upon the face of Gladius Prime. They saw the works of the Emperor, the suppression of heresy and the deep riches of the planet dedicated to humanity’s glory, and they saw it was good. First amongst us was Canoness Vandire, last of a long-penitent family. As with all Sororitas, she was orphaned and raised in the Schola Progenium and excelled in trials of the Convent Prioris. She knew her role, to ensure the spiritual purity of humanity and if she suffered the sin of pride at how well she did that, she expiated fully for it every day. Vandire, and we her sisters, walked among the people of Gladius. We did not suffer the heretic to live, but this world was unusually peaceful and spiritual, raising shrines and prayers to the God-Emperor daily."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story0Stage0Description" value="Yet a mere year after our arrival, this shining example of humanity was crushed by cursed xenos. In the ruins of the world, only a handful of us clung to our faith and slowly regathered our strength—though of Canoness Vandire, there was no sign."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story0Stage1Description" value="It had been the foul Greenskins that had devastated this world, in their repugnant lust for battle. As they seemed certain to overwhelm our lines, Vandire emerged once again, as from seclusion, to lead our holy work."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story0EndingDescription" value="Then Vandire, our Canoness, stood before her sisters and we rejoiced. And she said, As the God-Emperor liveth, we have done well this day; even so we will do more, for there is much more to be done. And she called the faithful together and planned our campaign."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story1" value="Chapter 2: Threefold Betrayal"/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story1BeginningDescription" value="Heresy is the most familiar road to sin, but lack of faith in the Emperor’s instruments is a starting step on that path. Our Order was betrayed threefold by our fellow men, each betrayal greater than the last."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story1Stage0Description" value="First, the Astra Militarum. Weak of body and mind but strong in material, their forces needed no more than simple demonstrations of our faith—once their independent spirit had been sufficiently crushed, of course. Vandire directed this lesser purgation."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story1Stage1Description" value="With the remains of the Guard brought back to the fold, a harder task ahead. The Adeptus Mechanicus’ identification of their Omnissiah with the God-Emperor has been called a convenient fiction—here, it was one that they dispensed with in extremis. Vandire took no pleasure in the waste of the key resources they possessed, but could not ignore the insult to the God-Emperor they posed."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story1Stage2Description" value="Over the Mechanicus’ remains, our sisters cast holy water and devotions. Yet the final test was to come—the Adeptus Astartes. The God-Emperor’s own children had always denied His majesty, even his divinity, and refuted our calls to prayer. Surely we could not stand against our brothers—against the divine one’s own creation? We prayed for guidance."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story1Stage3Description" value="Our guidance was clear, even without the indirect revelation of the Ecclesiarchy. Vandire herself proclaimed a mark of heresy upon the Adeptus Astartes and called the faithful to war. It was the Emperor’s choice that the Adepta Sororitas should be the instruments of this planet’s salvation, not his sons."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story1EndingDescription" value="And their mighty forms were piled high, as at the Eternity Gate 10,000 years before, except by our intent. Then Vandire fell and wept, for it was so great, the loss of that made by the Emperor’s own hand. But greater works were yet to come."/>	
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story2" value="Chapter 3: The Wings of Justice"/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story2BeginningDescription" value="This is how the rebirth of Saint Celestine came about. The Adepta Sororitas had purged the people of Gladius Prime, made them pure in the eyes of the Emperor. Each defence of humanity, each of its bastions, had been tested and found wanting—Astra Militarum, Adeptus Mechanicus, Adeptus Astartes. Only the Adepta Sororitas had emerged unscathed."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story2Stage0Description" value="Yet the God-Emperor was not content, for He set a final trial for us. From the skies above, an ancient space hulk emerged, streaming with corrupted Warp energies, and from it descended heretics, scattering across the planet’s surface. Vandire urged them to repent their sins, but came there answer none. And then they closed upon us. And each of us knew it to be the moment of our martyrdom."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story2Stage1Description" value="The heretics never seemed to cease—as if the ship was birthing them. But lo a voice from heaven came, saying, These are my beloved sisters, in whom I am well pleased. And the sky burning as with a magnesium flame. And the heretics looked away. But we sisters rejoiced, as we saw salvation descending. That was how Saint Celestine came to Gladius Prime. On wings of justice, formed from her faith and love for The Emperor."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story2Stage2Description" value="And Celestine delivered up the forces of the old enemy to death, until she came to one marked with brass and crimson—a Lord of Chaos. He would not die, sundered though he was, until he had spoken with the voice of a Spirit, saying, This world, Celestine, is beyond the Emperor’s Light. You will die here and live again. But you may never leave. And with a gory finger he pointed to the roiling sky, where the demon ship hung amidst the endless warp storm and laughed and laughed and laughed. Celestine saying, Think not I come to bring peace, ended him. And his forces fled and were lost in the wilds. Then she retired to meditate, leaving Canoness Vandire to reinforce our position against the day of judgement."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story2Stage3Description" value="Even with Celestine’s presence, the heretic’s prophecy had shaken the faithful. Doubters were as numerous as the hairs on one’s head, filled with malice and guile and hypocrisies and evil speakings, and we loyalists could not crop them quickly enough. Faith was needed in this darkness."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story2EndingDescription" value="Our city smoked, from the corpses of the cleansed. And rang, from the orisons from the sacristies and shrines. And shined, with the faith of the people and the penitents. And Vandire saw that it was good."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story3" value="Chapter 4: The Path of the Penitent"/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story3BeginningDescription" value="My sisters, The Saint emerged from her solitude burning with passionate intensity saying, Heed not the heretic, should we hide here in fear? What is faith without works? And mother Vandire knelt and prayed with her to the God-Emperor."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story3Stage0Description" value="So Celestine set out to cleanse the planet, not fearing failure or death. At her back the Exorcists raised a chorus of battle-canticles and rocket salvoes. And we her sisters marched with her."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story3Stage1Description" value="&lt;br/&gt;In time, Celestine fell into silence. We did not question our Saint’s faith—we could not—but the battles she chose grew more deadly, drawing her closer to a death she seemed to hunger for. The heretic’s last words were whispered then—that we were beyond the Emperor’s Light, that this world was truly abandoned. Unwavering, Saint Celestine forged on, battling even more terrible xenos, seemingly generated from the planet’s very surface."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story3EndingDescription" value="&lt;br/&gt;And as the heretic foretold, Celestine could not find death; and where she did, she was reborn again. The Imperium’s greatest Saint was confined here on a single planet, whilst Chaos continued its foul machinations elsewhere. Celestine knew half the galaxy had lost sight of the blessed Astronomican, whilst Horus’ foul brood sundered The Imperium. Yet her faith did not falter. After weeks, she paused from the slaughter, composed herself, and listened for the Emperor’s Guidance."/>	
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story4" value="Chapter 5: The Defiler’s Legacy"/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story4BeginningDescription" value="Our sister Celestine’s visions were ever as through a glass darkly—but she drew confidence from their guidance and followed them without question. Her first vision was of a foe scaled in ancient pride, of close sealed chambers, airless and ancient, with eyes like morning stars. Numberless they raised themselves up, as of old, and in their hands—an answer?"/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story4Stage0Description" value="Preacher Melisal voxed in then. The planet’s most holy Ecclesiarchy Shrines were being overrun from underneath—ancient Necrons, raised from their slumber on this cursed planet. Even as he imprecated our assistance, a skinclad talon of shining metal closed about him and he was gone."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story4Stage1Description" value="We will put Melisal in remembrance. With reverence, his flayed hide was brought down from the steeples of Shrine Primus and laid aside, a relic one day of this war. For this is good and acceptable in the Emperor’s sight. Then came a terrified missionary to Celestine, a rare survivor, and fell down before her, and said to her, Saint, the creatures did search for artefacts beneath our shrines. And the same survivor went out and showed her where they had dug. And Celestine knew the mark of the Necron and said, we are hunting a Cryptek, a collector of wisdom. I know not what it has, merely that the Emperor commands we take it. Canoness, you shall claim it personally."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story4EndingDescription" value="And it came to pass, that the Necrons were utterly annihilated, yea unto the smallest scarab that crawled. And Canoness Vandire trod on the cooling necrodermis, piled against the tomb walls, and found the Cryptek where it had crawled in its agonies. And with arco-flagellants and Hospitaller tools and the Trial of Castigation she drew its secrets from it—of the pylons and of the C'tan they were intended to contain. When Vandire understood, she said unto Celestine, this planet is a trap for another and a good work it is. And Celestine knew the pylons of Cadia, how they had sapped her spirit and she saw these ones differed, and she saw it was good. In that same hour, Celestine said, there is still a way. Fleeing Cadia, the webway was our saviour. And I feel it here too."/>	
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story5" value="Chapter 6: The Ultimate Sacrifice"/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story5BeginningDescription" value="At the end of the Festival of the Saints, as it began to dawn, came Celestine and Vandire to see the gate. It stood at the end of an enclosed valley, once a pleasure garden for the Hive World’s rich. The valley ended in an ancient glacier which had been dug away to reveal the Webway Portal beneath. Its gates were sealed and its wraithbone was black as ash. About it, between the vale’s slopes, swelled a mighty Aeldari force."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story5Stage0Description" value="And Celestine said, we might talk to them, they aided me on Cadia. But Vandire would not brook treating with the xenos and Celestine demurred saying, I have no guidance here. But I must reach it. I mourn their death."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story5Stage1Description" value="And Celestine stood by the gate, amidst the fine dead of the Aeldari; and we worked to open the gate, but it would not move. And the mechanisms were beyond our comprehension. So Vandire cursed the foul xenos. Wherefore, an Aeldari Ranger was brought to her, a survivor of the battle, longsighted Aerl. And once she had cursed and damned the Saint, she calmed and explained. That the gate had been built by the damned Aeldari others call Drukhari. That they had been preparing for its destruction, as it could not be opened without hideous suffering. And we saw the charges set at the gate's edge and knew she spoke truth. And Vandire smiled then, a fair look, saying, that is fortunate for suffering comes our way. And Celestine looked at the augurs to see that the Chaos horde had not been idle whilst we searched, that it had augmented and taken much of this world. And that it came for vengeance for its lost Lord. Suffering, it seemed, would be on all sides."/>
<entry name="SistersOfBattle/Story5EndingDescription" value="Behold, the gate stood and Celestine stood by it. And we died all around it and our foes too, in agony and horror. And it crackled and opened to the screaming Empyrean, and she stepped through urging us after. And I followed, I followed the saint, the least of our humble remembrancers. And Vandire bowed and stopped my sisters saying, no, we cannot hold them. We die here. And we looked upon the battle behind her as a mighty Khornate war engine breached the end of the hidden valley, and knew she spoke truth. So we retreated in and knelt and prayed. And Vandire detonated the Aeldari charges and sealed the webway behind us. And now I am alone with Celestine in the Drukhari webway and I entrust these recordings to her. For men and women do not live long in this place."/>	

	<!-- Space Marines -->
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Final Foundation"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story0BeginningDescription" value="As Chapter Master, the arrival of an enormous Ork horde on your Chapter's homeworld was calamitous. But no-one ever said the Adeptus Astartes shirked a challenge. Yet, after months of fighting, the battle remained locked in a stalemate. You instructed the civilian Planetary Governor that Astra Militarum support was required—clearing the green menace was a priority, whatever the blow to the Chapter's pride.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Barely had the guardsmen landed when a system-wide warp storm began, devastating the planet. Of your majestic fleet, a single Battle Barge in low orbit was the sole survivor. When the surface storms calmed, your surviving marines emerged into a ruined world. You are trapped on the planet's surface, cut off from the Imperium, and surrounded by Xenos species to boot. But you are the Emperor's own sons, the Space Marines, and you will not die easily, or in vain!"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story0Stage0Description" value="Your Chapter planned for every eventuality, so your fortress holds enough food and resources to survive decades of battle and siege—but more complex devices, ammunition and wargear require the acquisition of rare resources. To stand a chance of defeating the Xenos menace, we need to secure the location of these key materials, so that Servitors and serfs can continuously extract them."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story0Stage1Description" value="With the Fortress built, focus your energies on requisitioning the rare materials from the remaining population."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story0EndingDescription" value="With our supply line secured, the Chapter is no longer striving merely to survive—now we must explore this world and investigate the origin of these unusual warp storms."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story1" value="Chapter 2: Whispers of Heresy"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story1BeginningDescription" value="Your Librarians have been suffering endless torments since the storm started, and are now mostly incapacitated—but your chief Librarian has pushed through the pain to stand before you. He reports, through gritted teeth, that the Librarians feel that something unholy accompanied the Astra Militarum here. It's something immensely, dangerously powerful, a void in the warp, and must be destroyed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;His suspicions are infectious. You order the detention of all Astra Militarum forces, but this soon gets out of hand, with your Marines executing Guardsmen on sight. This is not the Astartes way… but if ten thousand innocents must die to save the planet, then the Astartes are the Emperor's tool."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story1Stage0Description" value="The Librarian believes that, with the construction of a specially-shielded Reclusiam, he and his Battle-Brothers can locate the source of the warp disturbance."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story1Stage1Description" value="A large Astra Militarum formation has been located nearby, presumably having emerged from a secure bunker. The Librarian reports traces of contamination amongst them, which are distracting the Reclusiam brothers. Regrettably, we must purge them."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story1Stage2Description" value="With the formation destroyed and the disturbing influence removed, the Reclusiam reports that they've identified other nearby locations where the warp is in disarray. The Librarian insists on visiting them for further study."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story1EndingDescription" value="The Librarian communicates with his brothers in the Reclusiam to report that he's found something—an ancient building that resonates with traces of the Xenos."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story2" value="Chapter 3: Citadel of the Witch"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story2BeginningDescription" value="Though the power the Librarian detected has vanished, he's found something else at its location—an ancient Exodite building that apparently extends deep into the planet's core. As soon as he approaches, though, he has to fall back, in the face of a new menace—Necrons, emerging from the depths."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story2Stage0Description" value="The realisation that this is a Necron Tomb World sends dismay through the Fortress serfs, but we Astartes are implacable. Arrange a Strike Force to investigate the Exodite structure and cleanse the Necron threat."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story2EndingDescription" value="You've eliminated the Necrons and explored the hidden depths of the planet. Your victory is interrupted when the Librarian returns, with dire news."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story3" value="Chapter 4: The Emperor's Will"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story3BeginningDescription" value="In the Exodite ruins, you have discovered an alien structure, dating back to the Old Ones, and it appears to extend throughout the planet. It acts as something like a prison, keeping the Necrons trapped beneath an eternal warpstorm, and triggers terrible surface devastation to deal with more significant threats. More importantly, the Necron we fought weren't the sentient enemies we've fought before—but mindless beasts, scoured of intellect. We must discover more."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story3Stage0Description" value="You cannot hope to understand this technology alone. Though it goes against all Guilliman's teachings, perhaps studying the Xenos on this planet would reveal some unique insights?"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story3Stage1Description" value="Your studies of the Xenos bears immediate reward. Tracking their strange technology has identified several positions of interest on the planet's surface."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story3Stage2Description" value="Your scans have revealed even greater heresy—a hidden Fortress of Redemption, occupied by Astra Militarum who won’t respond to our messages. The Reclusiam brothers indicate some unknown corruption has seized the men’s minds and suggest bombarding them from the battlebarge to destroy the fortress safely."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story3Stage3Description" value="With the corrupted Guard destroyed, the Librarians feel it's finally safe to approach. Still, our Chapter Tactics mandate the use of drop-pods to enter the area and remove any remaining resistance."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story3EndingDescription" value="The veterans bring in the Exodite device found in the ruins, under careful guard. It appears to be an ancient artefact, like many others that dot the planet, constructed of a material similar to the Cadian pylons. You order it sequestered in the heart of your Chapter's fortress, under close guard, while you ascertain its function. Only your Techmarines may approach it, under Librarian guard. Weeks go by…"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story4" value="Chapter 5: Litany of Devotion"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story4BeginningDescription" value="The Techmarines make their report, impassive. The device is… terrifying. Its destructive power is akin to the Exterminatus action—but this is usually carried out by a fleet of ships, not a gunmetal case a Marine can carry in one hand. More terrifying is its presence on this world—who knows what else might be located in the depths, amongst the Old One ruins, and their abominable creations?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Weak as the Chapter is, you cannot hope to hold this planet, or to prevent the device or the structures from falling into the hands of the old enemy, Chaos. The Chapter council agrees that the device and the planet must destroyed, even at the cost of the Chapter itself. Then the Master of the Forge presents a sliver of hope—that even in death, the Chapter’s geneseed could be preserved, buried deep beneath the monastery, and hence survive this… Exterminatus device. You order work to begin immediately."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story4Stage0Description" value="Modified servitors begin burrowing beneath the monastery, digging down amidst the Old One structures, to find a safe location for the chapter geneseed and the apothecaries necessary to implant it in a new generation. The Master of the Forge is confident these structures will survive the Exterminatus, where nothing else could."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story4EndingDescription" value="The Bunkers are built and the ancient Techmarine prepares the machine rites that will trigger the device. What could be the final battle of your Chapter is looming near."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story5" value="Chapter 6: The Rites of Passage"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story5BeginningDescription" value="Now you must prepare for death. The Marines pray, apply Purity seals, practice in the firing ranges, and do whatever comes naturally for those preparing to die. No-one knows what will happen when you trigger the device, save that it's unlikely that anyone will survive—and that everything else on the planet will try to stop you…"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story5Stage0Description" value="The Master of the Forge studies an ancient lock carefully, his cybernetic eyes roving over the device's ornate surface. Then his saw arm comes down and he carefully bisects the lock. Immediately, a keening noise begins, getting louder and louder. The Techmarine nods in your direction—the device is ready for activation."/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story5Stage1Description" value="Your comms network registers surprised and hostile messages from the other factions on the planet, before their forces turn in your direction. Meanwhile, legions of mindless Necron units are crawling out of the planet's surface, all heading toward the Fortress. No Marine has faced such a force and lived—this will be a worthy death for the Chapter!"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story5Stage2Description" value="And now the true enemy is revealed, the source of the Librarians' misgivings—a C'tan Shard, the Deceiver. It's directing a larger assault of corrupted Guard and Necrons to your geneseed bunkers, obviously in the hope of entering them and surviving the Exterminatus. You must defend both the bunkers and the Exterminatus device until they are ready—fight well, Marines and your names will go down in Imperial history!"/>
<entry name="SpaceMarines/Story5EndingDescription" value="The end is near, one way or the other. You and your surviving veterans are fighting a desperate rearguard in the Fortress, driven back step by step by the C'tan's forces. As you retreat into the Forge, the foul C'tan shows itself, its golden face shifting horribly through forms and faces you know. The Master of the Forge hurls himself bodily at the abomination, buying time with his life. A heartbeat after he falls, you see the C'tan scowl in horror and disgust, and lunge towards you and the Exterminatus device. As the C'tan's killing blow descends upon you, the device's whine suddenly falls silent. In the moment of its detonation and your Chapter's destruction, you feel nothing but pride at carrying out the Emperor's Will."/>
		
	<!-- Tau -->
<entry name="Tau/Story0" value="Chapter 1: The Greater Good"/>
<entry name="Tau/Story0BeginningDescription" value="You should not be here. You cannot be here.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your ship was an ark, carrying the races and ideas of the T'au to new worlds, following Commander Surestrike’s fleet. You should be with him and your Fourth Sphere comrades, proselytising the Greater Good to new souls.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Instead, in the Vash'aun'an, the ‘space between the stars’, a dream of corruption swallowed the fleet. Your auxiliaries were lost or twisted to darkness. And in that timeless nightmare an impossible many-handed being saved your ship, alone of the fleet. Landed it here. On this gue’la Hive World, ruined by war, full of hostile aliens and trapped by storms.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As the ranking Shas’El not in stasis, the Ethereal Aun’Dak’E has named you Commander. He assigns you a new task—to take this planet for the T’au."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story0Stage0Description" value="But, first, he demands that you chase down your errant auxiliaries."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story0Stage1Description" value="You’re studying a dissected Vespid when Kor’Daron of the Air Caste arrives. His slender frame looms over the body, recoiling a little when he sees the signature deformities—the warped oculi, the unusual patterns grown under the mesoplarum, the oozing tergite.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“It is better dead.” he says, lugubriously, making the hand sign of the dove. “We are lucky we caught it amongst the pack. I am told that our orders say we should eliminate all the Mal'kor—but our scouts report other Vespid out there who do not bear the Mont taint. Would it not be right to at least attempt to bring them back to the Way?” You agree—as they say on Sa’cea, ‘the Way is always open’. And, as you admit to Kor’Daron honestly, the troops will come in useful. You order the Fire Warriors to prepare their Drones for war."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story0EndingDescription" value="The Vespid unit you recruited has been thoroughly tested by the Earth Caste technicians and cleared—the taint seems to have affected only a minority of the auxiliary races. Your relief is unbounded—for you, the T’au was always more than the T’au race."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story1" value="Chapter 2: Virtue Before Duty"/>
<entry name="Tau/Story1BeginningDescription" value="In your cell, your meditations are interrupted. That familiar cloying scent heralds the first among your ark’s Ethereals, the ruthless Aun’Dak’E.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Commander, the stars are strange.” says Aun’Dak’E. “We are adrift in space and time, and the homeworlds are lost. We may be the last of the T’au.” You feel the truth of what he says.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;He turns an iron gaze on you. “So when we requested the elimination of the auxiliaries, it was because we could not afford to gamble. Your actions risked our entire civilization, even if they seemed to bolster the good.” He orders you to purge any auxiliary or T’au that displays any signs of corruption—physical, mental, or spiritual."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story1Stage0Description" value="He leaves, but pauses on the threshold. “And you need better guidance—retrieve the Stasis Pods.”"/>
<entry name="Tau/Story1Stage1Description" value="Carefully, carefully, the Bentusin technicians have manoeuvred the stasis pods from your ark to the colony city. Inside is your most precious treasure—the sleeping forms of your experts and leaders, Engineers, Ethereals, Fireblades and the Commanders.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Aun’Dak’E comes to you again. “Kor’Doran’s scout drones have identified ancient structures beneath the planet’s surface. I must investigate this personally. I need to know we can rely on you in our absence. Can we?” His face is impassive, but his hand gestures are hostile, expectant.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You reassure him, your loyalty burning in your eyes, and prepare for his expedition."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story1Stage2Description" value="This is the first time since your home on Sa’cea that you have been without Ethereal guidance. Oddly, your daily meditations on the Good seem somehow richer, more complete. You feel a oneness with all life, even this planet’s innumerable foes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though you know Aun’Dak’E has always commanded the use of force first—and now you think how strange that is for someone so committed to the greater good—your inclination is persuasion first. You send the water caste to treat with the human refugees, bringing them to the Way, and bend your efforts to a proper harmony and happiness amongst the various races in your city."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story1EndingDescription" value="Surely this is the Greater Good. It feels like you are doing the right thing—the thing *she* would have done. Though you swore not to think of her."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story2" value="Chapter 3: The Unconvertibles"/>
<entry name="Tau/Story2BeginningDescription" value="Aun’Dak’E sends encrypted signals. He has found something unique under the planet and is attempting to communicate with it. But he is disgusted by your lack of military action—particularly against the greenskinned Be'gel— and orders you to wake a higher-ranking Commander to deal with them. It will be their task to lead in the field against the unconvertibles: the Be’gel, the swarm Y'he, the giant Gue'ron'sha humans, their Mont counterparts, the machine ancients and worse…"/>
<entry name="Tau/Story2Stage0Description" value="There is only one more senior than you, as he well knows. You must wake her—the one known as Shas’O Sa’cea Lawlasa. Known to the fleet as Commander Coldflame. Known to you as ta'lissera—blood-bonded."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story2EndingDescription" value="Watching her in action through the drone-link, you are so proud of her—of Coldflame. And terrified for her at the same time. It is not accepted by the T’au to express emotion about kin but she is more than that to you—you are both bound by the Ta'lissera, the bonding knife ritual, which is tighter than family.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So when she returns from her campaigns, her Battlesuit ruined and bloodied, you are always waiting for her with the Cadre guard, pride and relief poorly hidden behind the formalities. As ta'lissera, she knows what that means."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story3" value="Chapter 4: The Experience Machine"/>
<entry name="Tau/Story3BeginningDescription" value="Your meditation today was on humility and detachment. When you arose, Coldflame was lounging against your terminal. “Friend, I am proud of you.” she smiles, her hand gestures jocular and warm. “The way of the T’au should not be to shoot first. And don’t tell me not to call you ‘friend’—the Ethereals aren’t here and I outrank you, ha. Where are the Ethereals anyway?”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You explain that they are either in the field, in stasis or with Aun’Dak’E, investigating the planet’s secrets. “Well”, she laughs, “I guess we get to work out what the Greater Good is today, hmm? I’ve sent the Water Caste diplomats to treat with the human forces—and the survivors tell me that they’ve agreed to a deal. If we can eliminate their Mont traitors, we’ll have a truce.”"/>
<entry name="Tau/Story3Stage0Description" value="You cannot go against her—both from rank and filial pride. But this is a dangerous path…"/>
<entry name="Tau/Story3Stage1Description" value="You’re pleased with Coldflame for trying but the diplomatic endeavour has failed. The Imperium had no intention of dealing with the T’au truly. Whilst you were fighting their ‘Chaos’ enemies, they were preparing to attack. Already, Coldflame is turning her troops against them."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story3EndingDescription" value="You stand on a long ridge. The Imperial army lies spread out before you, fleeing or burning, insects before Coldflame’s tactical brilliance. Betrayal and surprise were no advantage against your superior technology. You know that other foes await you—but you are confident that she can defeat anything now. She leaves, for her next conquest."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story4" value="Chapter 5: The Survival Lottery"/>
<entry name="Tau/Story4BeginningDescription" value="Aun’Dak’E has returned, with fewer bodyguards and more scars. You can barely follow his boastful tale of his exploits beneath the planet’s surface, but you understand when he gives the planet a new name—“Muort’va’ul” or the ‘casque of the anvil.’&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Ethereals have even spoken to something intelligent in the depths. The Earth Caste and Bentusin are trying to understand it, but they say that there is an ancient Ar'cea device built throughout the world—placed by the Aeldari or their forebears millennia ago, to restrain a Necron god."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story4Stage0Description" value="In some way it is alive and may give them a unique weapon against your foes, that could eliminate every non-T’au on the planet’s surface—yes, your auxiliaries too. When Aun’Dak’E tells you this is the good, you believe it with fervour. He tells you what you must do."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story4EndingDescription" value="The Earth Caste have used the Bentu’sin’s labs to establish control of the device, though it will take time to activate. You relay Aun’Dak’E’s plan to Commander Coldflame remotely—and you can hear her audibly recoil. “To'tau'va! How is this the Good, Shas’El? The death of our allies? Of the billion gue’la on this planet? There must be a better way. I will find it and stop this madness.” She cuts the line—and is the last time you talk to her. You will always regret not saying more."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story5" value="Chapter 6: The Trolley Problem"/>
<entry name="Tau/Story5BeginningDescription" value="With so few Ethereals to spread calm and so much disorder from the journey here, the Coldflame rebellion spreads quickly. Hers is an open creed, accepting T’au, Gue’la, the auxiliary races… everyone save for Ethereals who are shot on sight. Their Earth Caste rebels quickly fortify a human settlement.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Aun’Dak’E stays with you constantly, reassuring you. “The Gue'senshi-lovers have gathered in one place, Commander. This is your chance to redeem yourself. To kill that traitor, Coldflame.” You look at the bonding knife, strapped to your hip. She is all to you—more than the T’au, perhaps? You hesitate."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story5Stage0Description" value="But then Aun’Dak’E leans over, overwhelmingly close. “You want that, Commander, don’t you?” And you want nothing more. You want nothing more."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story5Stage1Description" value="The settlement was a classic Kauyon—a feint to take your forces elsewhere. Inside… it was empty, worker drones faking activity, whilst Coldflame planned her attack elsewhere. It appears her Water Caste contacts with the Imperium paid off (is that pride you feel?) and they verified her tale about the device. They have turned up in force, to prevent you from using it."/>
<entry name="Tau/Story5EndingDescription" value="Aun’Dak’E watches with you as Coldflame dies. He tells you that you should be happy, that she was a traitor, that her death clears your name, that you are free from your bonds of oath and fealty. You smile and nod and inside you something breaks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Ethereal is gloating. He says you’ll be able to make use of the technology inside the planet, soon—that this world will become a beacon for the Greater Good. He talks of finally supplanting Aun’Va. You feel that you can’t but be happy for him.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And yet inside your broken bond burns, eating away at your reason. In your meditation, later, you twist your bonding knife over and over, careless of the cuts it inflicts. Away from Aun’Dak’E, you can only think of her—her empathy, her courage, her sacrifice. The Coldflame rebellion does not end here."/>
	
	<!-- Tyranids -->
<entry name="Tyranids/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Prophase"/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story0BeginningDescription" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;To: Magos Xenologis Lexidium. Report concerning Divisio Biologis operations on Gladius Prime.&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;…with the Astra Militarum as tech-priest liaison, to investigate the Circle Varnak facility on Gladius Prime—that is, the successful experiments which had resulted in victory at Fecundia… [missing data]&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;…when the storm stabilised, the planet was cut off. Fearing the worst, I made my way to the Genetor facility—but found it an empty ruin, with no trace of Servitors or Tech-Priests. I returned empty-handed to the surviving Imperial forces.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Soon, reports came in. Monsters, horrors—Tyranids. Yet the creatures were not coordinated swarms—they were isolated, running wild, easy prey for neophyte Marines or veteran guardsmen. I dared to hope we could eliminate them quickly.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;That wish was short-lived."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story0Stage0Description" value="Knowing what I know now, the Hive Mind focused on the creation of mighty synapse creatures—the Warriors, Tyrants and Primes."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story0Stage1Description" value="Where they appeared, the Tyranid forces had direction, cohesion. I began to despair…"/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story0EndingDescription" value="Soon, the wild Tyranids were gone. The Hive swarm had disappeared from view, presumably consolidating as they prepared to claim the planet."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story1" value="Chapter 2: Interphase"/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story1BeginningDescription" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;To: Magos Xenologis Lexidium. Report concerning Divisio Biologis operations on Gladius Prime.&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Tech-Adept, I had the data from Fecundia and Macragge, I knew the Tyranid methodology—they would be gathering biomass to mount their assault, stripping isolated areas down to the bedrock for materials and building their armies. And the Hive Mind was a gourmet, sampling the local genetic data, creating warriors tailored to our weaknesses to ensure victory. Even now, I knew the Malanthropes would be massing, working behind the warriors.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I should have warned the Astra Militarum, I know—but I was more concerned with protecting the products of our research. These Tyranids could be the key to defeating the next Hive Fleet. I chose to gather data, in the hope of getting it off planet, and hence I doomed this world."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story1Stage0Description" value="The Hive Mind needed biomass. Given that it came from just a few individuals in our facility, it will have needed more genetic data too. It will have looked to its Malanthropes, the slithering giants that followed its swarm."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story1Stage1Description" value="Once the Malanthropes were grown, they were dispatched to recover biomass and fresh genetic data by consuming great tracts of land, killing the local peak predators and sampling their data."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story1EndingDescription" value="Soon the Tyranids revealed themselves—much stronger and more varied than even I expected, given the limited numbers in the research facility."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story2" value="Chapter 3: Anoikis"/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story2BeginningDescription" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;To: Magos Xenologis Lexidium. Report concerning Divisio Biologis operations on Gladius Prime.&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Finally, the Space Marine Chapter and the Astra Militarum realised the threat—that they were trapped here, not merely with Orks and Necrons, but with Tyranids too. That humanity might be crushed between these three Xenos horrors. My remaining flesh ached with despair. Yet an unexpected ally gave us a chance to destroy them once and for all.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Tech-Adept, the planet itself rose up against them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It seems that Gladius housed some long-forgotten Xenos technology, perhaps the self-same that trapped us here under the warp storms. Great spires of burnished Exodite metal rose from the ground around the Tyranid hives. From my analyses of its remains, I suspect it may pre-date even the Aeldari—as far back as… [data missing]"/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story2Stage0Description" value="Where the spires rose, the warp storms intensified, purging the planet's surface of life. The Tyranids were thrown back—for a time."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story2Stage1Description" value="The Imperials forces, who had been prepared to die defending our cities, seized the moment and attacked. I lent some of my Kastelans to the effort, however small the chance of victory was."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story2EndingDescription" value="It was all for naught. Our forces were destroyed, torn apart and rendered down in the reclamation pools, even the ancient spires toppled."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story3" value="Chapter 4: Cytokinesis"/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story3BeginningDescription" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;To: Magos Xenologis Lexidium. Report concerning Divisio Biologis operations on Gladius Prime.&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With the planet as our ally, we dared to dream—but the human forces couldn't afford to lose another expedition like the last, instead focusing on [data missing]&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thankfully, the planet's ancient mechanisms threw up another trick—a psychic signal akin to that produced by the doomed Astropath on Fecundia which somehow divided the Hive Mind against itself. A second hive arose to fight the first, and a real hope emerged amongst the defenders that the Hive Fleet would spend all its biomass in futile internecine war.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I had no such illusions. I knew that one swarm would prevail and emerge the stronger for the test. That soon the isolated Tyranid strain would call out to space and attract the nearest Hive Fleet—perhaps a fragment of Tiamet—and then all would be consumed."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story3Stage0Description" value="The two Hive Minds met in battle soon after. I don't know if the original survived or the challenger, but it mattered little—the winner adapted first, then consumed its opponent's troops, so it shared the genetic data of both."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story3EndingDescription" value="As I predicted, this conflict, far from being an obstacle, was an accelerant for the Tyranids' planetary conquest. Our astropath reported that the hive had created something like a Brood Mind—a psychic beacon strong enough to pass through even the maelstrom above. The Hive Fleet was coming.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For Gladius Prime's loss to mean something, someone needed to survive and pass this data onto the Adeptus Mechanicus. I planned my escape from the planet."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story4" value="Chapter 5: Juxtacrinesis"/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story4BeginningDescription" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;To: Magos Xenologis Lexidium. Report concerning Divisio Biologis operations on Gladius Prime.&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Months passed, Tech-Adept. The planet continued to ramp up the pressure on the Xenos, turning the planet's life against them, even as the Shadow in the Warp fell over Gladius Prime and the Hive Fleet encircled it.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We now felt like bystanders in a battle between giants. It must have become obvious to the Hive Mind that it couldn't simply consume this world like normal—their dreaded spore pods couldn't get through the warp storms and they couldn't breed fast enough on the surface to overcome our defenses. It needed something special to crack the planet wide open.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The few Imperial satellites and the Space Marine Battle Barge reported that the hive fleet was circling the planet, throwing mycetic spores downward, probing the storm. Though nothing made it through, the fleet seemed to identify a relatively stable point in the storm. The Shadow In The Warp pushed on it, widening it."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story4Stage0Description" value="On the surface, the Hive Mind moved its resources, coordinating with the fleet above, aiming somehow to reach through the storm. Its forces were seen near to a dormant Necron tomb city—perhaps the storms were weaker there?"/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story4Stage1Description" value="There was a peace for a time, whilst the Hive Mind nested and gathered resources. Peace, only in the context of endless war, of course."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story4Stage2Description" value="Then, like a delicate strange flower but impossibly tall, a Capillary Tower rose from the new hive. We watched it stretch miles and miles high, growing into the atmosphere."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story4EndingDescription" value="From the surface, we could see only see the Capillary Tower. Yet the few Imperial craft in low orbit reported seeing the Hive Ships creeping closer extending strange tendrils trailing down to the tower's tip, burning with witchfire as the warp storm tore at them. It was a short connection only—but in reconnecting, the local Hive Mind fragment had learned how to destroy this world."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story5" value="Chapter 6: Phagein"/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story5BeginningDescription" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;To: Magos Xenologis Lexidium. Report concerning Divisio Biologis operations on Gladius Prime.&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Whatever it was that gestated on the planet then, we could all feel the horror of it—even my remaining flesh shrank as the thing grew. At its birth, every psyker on the planet howled—the Hive Mind had sent something monstrous to the planet.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The planet's defences knew that this was the end too—it scraped up everything left to it, every horror driven from its lair and forced towards the Tyranid hives. Orks, Psycheneuin, Catachan Devils, degenerate Kroot. And the Hive Mind defended its gestating horror with equal vigour."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story5Stage0Description" value="The battle was endless—it wasn't clear whether we'd survive the planet's defences, let alone the Tyranid assimilation."/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story5Stage1Description" value="My attempts to secure an artefact to stabilise the storm and a ship to leave Gladius had been frustrated by the Tyranid arrival and the loss of my Kastelans. Escape from the planet was impossible, I now recognised. In our makeshift fortifications, the Imperial Cult led the prayers to the God-Emperor one last time—and I prayed to the Omnissiah.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Then I organised for my notes to be preserved in the traditional method—buried alongside the Marines' gene-seed in a drill, deep in the planet's crust. And I prepared myself for death.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And out there, in the ruins of our civilisation, the Tyranid creature—the Doom of this planet—crept closer to its destiny, the heart of this strange alien world. Our satellites saw it battling towards the base of a Tower of Vaul—perhaps to access the Exodite mechanisms inside?"/>
<entry name="Tyranids/Story5EndingDescription" value="Have you ever felt a planet just… die? We all felt that at the last. Beneath our feet, it trembled. Whatever ancient power had been battling the Tyranids was finally defeated, its psychic energies absorbed by the Tyranid's monstrous creation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And then it started to come apart. That ancient machine, whatever it was, must have simply been holding the entire planet together—even now the earth shudders constantly beneath our feet, the gravity shifting wildly. If it continues at this rate, the planet will simply disintegrate—denying the Tyranids its resources at least.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I have no idea if this message will survive. I am handing it to my servitor, to send into the planet's crust now—I hope it will survive the collapse of the planet. May the Omnissiah have mercy on our souls."/>
		
	<!-- Side -->
<entry name="LordOfSkulls" value="Skulls for the Skull Throne"/>
<entry name="LordOfSkullsBeginningDescription" value="Your troops intercept a unsanctioned psyker's desperate last message to the Imperium. “So much war, so much death, so much blood… it's drawing this world through the warp rift, closer to his realm… into a realm of war without ending, where the mighty shall die and rise to fight again each morn. My greatest fear was that he would send one of his servants, to hurry our arrival—and it is realised. Whatever we do, this planet is Khorne's now. The Lord of Skulls is here.”"/>
<entry name="LordOfSkullsStage0Description" value="A great mechanical-demon beast is rampaging across the planet. Stop it."/>
<entry name="LordOfSkullsEndingDescription" value="You can't believe you've defeated it. Even the Lord of Skulls itself does not seem to believe, continuing to roll forward with much of its superstructure blown away or simply missing. It grinds to a halt, warp-forged runes cracking and rusting in seconds. A roar of wrath rocks Gladius then, as the Bloodthirster darkly bound to the war machine is finally banished back to the realm of the Chaos Gods and Khorne's waiting fury."/>
	
</language>
