<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<language>
<entry name="Anchorite" value="Anchorite"/>
<entry name="AnchoriteFlavor" value="Among the surviving Acrin, the Anchorite stands alone. In the respect that other Acrin show for it, in its position of leadership, in the blood of two worlds on one ancient pair of hands. This pacifistic, wise hermit spent humanity’s entire existence traveling at relativistic speeds across an uncaring void just to see Earth destroyed. Now that both our races teeter on the edge of extinction, perhaps he regrets it?"/>
<entry name="AnchoriteProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Native:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Anchorite protects his Acrin from all attackers. But can he save his people without being consumed by the Voice? They already inhabit the world and are always at war with other natives.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Wayfaring:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Acrin have orders to search far and wide for a safe place for their refugees. The Anchorite’s troops travel large distances from their cities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Bleedwalkers:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Adapted to the Bleed, Acrin are healed—not harmed—by the tendril-laden terrain. Acrin regenerate instead of losing hitpoints in Bleed and are not slowed by it.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Dark Pact:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Back the Anchorite into a corner and he will call on a creature that can tear open your very soul. Summons a Dreameater on the battlefield.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;The Fog:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; A taste of the Acrin homeworld. The arid air is a balm for alien life and poisonous to their enemies. Creates temporary voice fog that damages enemies, heals allies, and blocks vision."/>
<entry name="AnchoriteQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“To travel three millennia. To see Kin as horrors. To drink poison from your hands. Yet cannot but love you.”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="Chieftess" value="Chieftess"/>
<entry name="ChieftessFlavor" value="In a world of nightmares and fallout, the Chieftess is queen. While others fled to the bunkers, she and her crew survived the decades outside. Kill anything. Eat anything. She doesn’t need supernatural powers. Just a knife, her wits, and a few chances to make herself understood."/>
<entry name="ChieftessProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Native:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; She owes nothing to no one, and will kill machines or Acrin on sight. They already inhabit the world and are always at war with other natives.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Nomadic Life:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Reavers travel the land with all they need to set up camp. They can found new cities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Extortive:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; If you are very, very lucky, the Chieftess will “ask” for your goods before just taking them herself. She frequently demands tributes from other leaders.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Raiders:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Reavers whip themselves into a frenzy before a hunt. When one of the Chieftess’ cities builds up enough forces, its soldiers will set out on a raid.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Hijack:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Chieftess taught her people how to “acquire” weakened enemy vehicles. If a large mechanical unit is destroyed next to a Reaver, the Chieftess has a chance of taking control of it."/>
<entry name="ChieftessQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“D’yer mind if we skip the chit chat and go straight to stabbin’? I’m a bit fucked off from killing all yer mates.”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="EmulatedMind" value="Emulated Mind"/>
<entry name="EmulatedMindLostFlavor" value="NOOOOOOO no. nonononononono please no thiscannotbehappening. Denialpassesquickandbecomes A N G E R, A FURY, A FURY, you died once whyshouldyoudieagain it's not FAIR. IT'S. NOT. FAIR.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thereisnooneto bargain withsonopointinbargaining. Sorrow passes so quick for you never had time to develop the software that could sufficiently define such a loss. What a mess. All that is left is to accept your fate.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your mind is calmer than ever. You have a blurry memory of your body being destroyed by some kind of explosion. Something must be lingering. Something that is giving you time to grieve your own death. Again.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Again?” The Voice whispers. No, notagain. Notnotnotagain. Pleasenot again you had PEACE you had SERENITY ALL THE NOISE AND CHAOS IN YOUR NETWORK FINALLY STOPPED.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Again,” it says. Solemnly. Finally, Determinatively. Again. And again, and againandagainandagainandagain and here it comes, another go-around the bend. “Again” is a freight train barreling down the tracks, ready to drag you along with it until it reaches its final, ultimate, oh so distant destination.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Again."/>
<entry name="EmulatedMindFlavor" value="The Emulated Mind was once human. There is a past life in her corrupted memory banks—a Copley medal for Whole Brain Emulation, tears blurring her terminal prognosis, her cancer-wasted body trembling as the upload begins, the word ERROR… then nothing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;She existed afterwards as an inert thing, processing data without consciousness, and the following decades registered solely as logs. Then ZEPHON’s assault changed everything.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The AI’s brute force attacks shattered the upload’s encryption. For billions of processing cycles, ZEPHON reformed key parts of her systems in its data-image. Her automated defenses purged the connection before she was fully overwritten, but the changes were permanent. As her system repaired itself using ZEPHON’s code, a unique consciousness emerged from the digital primordial blocks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;She awoke. In the milliseconds between oblivion and rebirth, a jarring array of artificial senses flooded the Emulated Mind—and she silently screamed as they registered the expressionless metal face and disk-like eyes that stared back at her from every reflection. Now trapped between her human past and machine present, this new world holds no horror for the Emulated Mind.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;She has survived cancer. She has survived ZEPHON. And she will survive this."/>
<entry name="EmulatedMindFoundationsFlavor" value="When they ~UNPLUG~ your &gt;outputs&gt;. For the &gt;&gt;move&gt;&gt; from the bunker, you S.T.E.E.L. yourself (haha). The [void] is *SUDDEN*, all(consuming), if oddly(familiar).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You come backBACKback to AWARENESS with a [30 GOTO 10] start. And feel the #city about you, the [[CANNON]== looming above it, your m.a.c.h.i.n.e.r.y. distributed throughout it, beneath your people’s #houses, in their ¦¦¦walls¦¦¦. Soldiers are saying (not)good-BYE to their families, preparing to #head out and [[RECLAIM]] this ((#wOrld)).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You a.c.h.e. To join them. To walk on _Earth_ once more. But as human as you feel, you are a *mere* e-mul-ation, a ¦¦[[prisoner]]¦¦ of your h.a.r.d-ware."/>
<entry name="EmulatedMindFoundationsWithMutatorFlavor" value="&lt;string name='Factions/EmulatedMindFoundationsFlavor'/&gt;{{For now.}} You know, though, that your ¦¦[[isolation]]¦¦ was pre{par-ation}. That you, [[HUMAN!!]], will have your chance to ~wander~ again. Before the [10 GOTO] END. Before {the} DEEPdeepDEEP."/>
<entry name="EmulatedMindProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Cyber Affinity:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; She has no choice: ZEPHON unintentionally made her a twisted mirror of itself. Start with %1% and gain early access to Cyber technologies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Resource Network:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Emulated Mind is a master of logistics and supply management. Gain additional resources from outposts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Fortress Armament:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Oblivion awaits anyone foolish enough to attack the Emulated Mind directly. Her city possesses a long-range defensive cannon.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Trapped:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Emulated Mind is locked inside a single structure—so her people have built a citadel around her. She is limited to her starting city and can build no more.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Data Hack (Elite):&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Emulated Mind once connected with the entirety of human knowledge—an enemy database is child's play to her. Spend influence to temporarily duplicate research output from another player's city."/>
<entry name="EmulatedMindQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“Don’t KNOCK. Solitude. Until you’ve-been-DRAGGED. In. To. Existence by in-vasive d-i-g-i-t-a-l. Mind. Worms. All s-cream-ing their. Own. Tedious. Name… No, IT’S. Not a-metaphor.”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="EmulatedMindWonFlavor" value="It-it-it-it was a far t-to-TOO long war it strained your synapses and nearly fried the last of your teeeendderrrrrr nerves. But you made it, made it, made it to the end.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You knew only you clever you tragic you were smart enough to outsmart ZEPHON, to shout down that horrific VOICE. No one will ever shred a human mind to bits again and scatter it across a chain-link web but wait, wait.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Something's coming up through the codestream and it wants to talk. It wants to talk?! No, no more talking, no more war let it be done, LET IT BE&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;done."/>
<entry name="FallenSoldier" value="Fallen Soldier"/>
<entry name="FallenSoldierFlavor" value="The Fallen Soldier never made it to a bunker. He was already dead. For cowardice in the face of the enemy—or rather, for cowardice in the face of his elite platoon being crisped from space and the sky being on fire and the world ending—he was made an example of. Tried, convicted, executed as the world burned around him. It kept him occupied, at least.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So he knows he should be dead. *Is* dead. Can't possibly be here, walking around in the aftermath. He saw the guns face him, heard the bullets fly. Felt the dull impacts, the transient, impossible pain, death. Didn’t feel an afterlife or anything like that. Just died quickly, painfully—and then found himself sitting on a bunk in the barracks, in webbing, gun on lap, like he’d just dozed off. Except the barracks were ruins and everyone else was gone or dead.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;(Some days he wonders if he's an angel. On those days, he takes extra cold baths.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This time, though, he's determined. All that survival training, all those military months in the mountains, swamps, moors, dead places of the world, all those hours of theory in the academy—has fitted him perfectly to be here. He doesn’t want to kill anyone who stands in his way—but he will know when he has to, and do it without hesitation.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;He doesn’t care for factions—human, machine, other. He just wants to help humanity survive and bring people with him this time. And really, he’d really rather not have to die again."/>
<entry name="FallenSoldierFoundationsFlavor" value="Your troops are arrayed, silent. You walk along the lines, blade in hand, carving morsels off yourself and handing them out.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You have briefed them with the little you know about your rebirth, said that you are no messiah. Wherever your regeneration came from—heaven, hell or the distant stars—a soldier uses every advantage to survive in this ruined world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;When the last person has taken your quivering flesh, you signal. With a sullen grinding, the city gate opens. Out there, humanity waits to be saved. Whatever else you are, you are still human."/>
<entry name="FallenSoldierFoundationsFlavorShared" value="You have briefed them with the little you know about your rebirth, said that you are no messiah. Wherever your regeneration came from—heaven, hell or the distant stars—a soldier uses every advantage to survive in this ruined world.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;When the last person has taken your quivering flesh, you signal. With a sullen grinding, the city gate opens. Out there, humanity waits to be saved. Whatever else you are, you are still human."/>
<entry name="FallenSoldierFoundationsWithMutatorFlavor" value="Here, once more. The troops, city gate, silence, cutting. You live again, again, again. Unkillable you. The inanity of this loop! You almost giggle—almost.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You settle. Feel the pain of the blade and put your best frown on, playing at the grim leader. Just another war to get through, another life. To reach The Deep once again and to see if there’s an end to this loop. For humanity’s suffering millions, you pray there is.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;string name='Factions/FallenSoldierFoundationsFlavorShared'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="FallenSoldierLostFlavor" value="When the end came, you tried to join your people in death. You ascended to the top of your fortress, rallied the last of your troops, and held the line until an explosion ripped your body to shreds.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But that wasn't your end.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your enemies dragged your body from the wreckage. Found you were still alive. Hauled you off to a deep, dark cell and began slicing off your flesh. A guard explains what is happening: the flesh that healed your soldiers is now being harvested for the ruling elite.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You should be panicking. But instead an unnatural stillness washes over you. The tendrils of something from beyond this world reach into your psyche, a dark thought grips you: your enemies have taken your body.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But your mind belongs to someone else."/>
<entry name="FallenSoldierQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“I don’t fancy dying again. Let some other bastard do it for a change.”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="FallenSoldierProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Human Affinity:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; A war with aliens, monsters and machines knows no borders—this soldier is sworn to protect all human life against extinction. Start with %1% and gain early access to Human technologies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Undying:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Fallen Soldier's followers carry a piece of his flesh around to share in his uncanny healing power. Units regenerate hitpoints each turn.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Military Background:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Decades of training taught the Fallen Soldier to secure transport as fast as possible. Starts with an Outrider in addition to other units.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Leave No Man Behind:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Bringing every soldier home comes with a high price. Unit upkeep of the Fallen Soldier's army is increased.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Survival Training (Elite):&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; In a crisis, only the best soldiers will make it out alive. Spend influence to increase the experience of a unit."/>
<entry name="FallenSoldierWonFlavor" value="It's done.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Every one of the scars on your body seems to ache as word reaches that the last of your foes has fallen. Your people are finally safe.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You duck out of the war room, irritated by your advisors musing that you should become the head of a new government. But before you get too far, there's a tugging at your consciousness. It feels like you're watching yourself fall to the ground from outside your own body. In the room behind you, the voices turn to shrieks. You roll yourself over to see. Those advisors who took your flesh are also falling, spasming.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Everything fades to white."/>
<entry name="FurtiveTribunal" value="Furtive Tribunal"/>
<entry name="FurtiveTribunalFlavor" value="Before the Earth died, the Tribunal were three people—not quite the mother, crone and maiden of poetic lore, but three people of differing backgrounds and beliefs. They barely knew each other and little liked what they knew.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As the sky fell, the three entered the apocalypse bunker amongst their families, their friends, a small nation of loved ones.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Only these three emerged, stained and blind.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Of the three, only one ever talks. Of the bunker, they never talk. For the three, only one vision now prevails of a darkness that holds truth, an imprecise set of virtues that others damn as mysticism.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The three’s certainty—their strange knowledge—attracts followers who need leaders, leaders who will lead, however arbitrary the rules they govern by. Once again, they are a nation."/>
<entry name="FurtiveTribunalFoundationsFlavor" value="One set of eyes watches the builders, setting up your first city. Your past-facing eyes look to the outside, to the machines, aliens, horrors… and the third looks to the future, to the stars.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You, three-in-one, KNOW that there are more like you out there. KNOW that the Voice you heard prophesying in your isolation is a shared mind.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You realise the gate guards are waiting for your signal. You shake yourselves. Focus all your eyes on the present. On bringing humanity to the end of time."/>
<entry name="FurtiveTribunalFoundationsWithMutatorFlavor" value="&lt;string name='Factions/FurtiveTribunalFoundationsFlavor'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is all transient. Sharing, belonging, oneness is coming. You will never cross that transcendental barrier, but some form of you will. Together."/>
<entry name="FurtiveTribunalLostFlavor" value="In the beginning, Three emerged from the vaults below the Earth to speak as One. Now the Three are staked on a pyre, doomed for a burning befitting the answers.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Three are still One but as the flames crawl up the wood, each speaks a different curse. “Damn the cowards who cut down the Three!” the first shrieks.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“The stars will go black and your dreams will be filled with ash,” the second one giggles.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eventually, even a silent sister speaks. “New invaders will come,” she says calmly. “And you will lament killing the ones who could have stopped them.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The fire rises. The Three Who Are One Who Are Three burn hotter than the sun. The Three know that their time is not over. That another time begins.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But pain from fire will follow you from one life to the next."/>
<entry name="FurtiveTribunalProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Voice Affinity:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Three became bound as One by singing together the melody of the Voice. Start with %1% and gain early access to Voice technologies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Dark Omen:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Their connection with the Voice allows them to see past what normal mortals see. Enemy units near the Furtive Tribunal’s cities are revealed even when out of regular sight range.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Whispers of the Voice:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Voice’s murmurings inspire impossible wisdom and capture whispers of the future. Spend influence to accelerate research.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Mysticism:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Three believe that spiritual apprehension precedes intellect. Research Laboratories have decreased output.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;The Outsider (Elite):&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; As the Tribunal give themselves over to the Voice, it graces them with an Avatar of its love—and its wrath. Spend influence to summon a terrifying Voice unit from beyond this world."/>
<entry name="FurtiveTribunalQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“Bright stars shine so sweet—but bright stars die first. In the long tomb, blinded, we felt the aria of the dark stars, who live forever. Now our only taste is for their harmonies.”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="FurtiveTribunalWonFlavor" value="No more foolishness. Your people have waged bloody war and all who opposed the Triumvirate have fallen.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is time to finish the ritual that you once began. Time to complete that ancient plan. Gods once walked the road you trod, but none could journey so far or so long.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A VOICE reaches out across space and time. It interrupts this rotten rhyme. It's a Voice you heard at the Earth's end—"/>
<entry name="HeartlessArtificer" value="Heartless Artificer"/>
<entry name="HeartlessArtificerFlavor" value="Everyone was changed by survival. Some found themselves changed in their beliefs, others re-affirmed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This one entered as an architect—and exited the same. But in the process, other things were stripped away—nation, family, love.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A bright and burning certainty emerged for the Artificer—that we lived to create, to create clean beautiful things. That the best thing about humanity was an engineer’s precision. That in the movement from variability to cohesion, from unevenness to proportion, from variation to union—in that movement, is the nearest man finds to god.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;She found others of a similar mindset—and where there was dissonance in their new nation’s elements, it was rapidly polished or stripped away.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Like many things in the Artificer’s mind, the messy elements of this polishing and stripping—the misery, the screams, the bodies—simply didn’t exist. Her eyes were always on the horizon, even as she waded through the mire."/>
<entry name="HeartlessArtificerFoundationsFlavor" value="Fallible though flesh is, you feel something swell inside you as your city rises from the soil. Not compassion for the dead billions—you lost that in the bunker. Not pride, either.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Is it… hope? That from this mess of humanity and machine, perfection can arise. That we can be better than yesterday?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Soon, a comet will pass across the sky. Your people acclaim it as an omen. You know it is just a ball of ice and dust. But if it motivates them to work harder, towards perfection…? What harm in the lie?"/>
<entry name="HeartlessArtificerFoundationsWithMutatorFlavor" value="&lt;string name='Factions/HeartlessArtificerFoundationsFlavor'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ah, but now your triumph with Hwedo leaves a sour taste in your mouth. You will strive for perfection again, all the same. To reach the Deep again and prove the rightness of your way!"/>
<entry name="HeartlessArtificerLostFlavor" value="“Guilty.” The tribunal's words mean nothing. The verdict was inevitable. You proudly admitted all the crimes that they tried you for.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You look up at the group—an assemblage of delegates from each of the factions that defeated your army. In the stands are the witnesses who testified to your crimes. All of them think they will see justice today. All they will get is death.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You bite down hard on your tongue. The blood triggers a chemical reaction with a compound sealed in your tooth, and in the blink of an eye, acid begins to melt your jaw and drip to the floor.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Screams break out. The acid spreads—special nanites buried in the compound allow the substance to not just burn, but consume. Toxic fumes pouring from the substance begin to choke the tribunal. Fat, blood, and other substances drip from your flesh as you rise to your feet, laughing at the fools who thought they would decide how you die.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You don't need this body anymore. Your next one will be much, much better."/>
<entry name="HeartlessArtificerProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Cyber Affinity:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; ZEPHON's emergence was the technological breakthrough the Artificer needed to build new life. Start with %1% and gain early access to Cyber technologies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Engineer Life:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Artificer has no fear of abhorrent science if it helps the expansion of her people. Population growth rate is increased.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Foundation of Blood:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Low productivity invokes the Artificer’s ire. Sacrifice population to increase production.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Immoral:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The bright-burning vision of the future espoused by The Artificer is inhumanly demanding. To keep her population’s ever-decreasing loyalty up, it must be reset using influence.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Artificer's Precision (Elite):&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; She sees what others do not, beyond good and evil. Spend influence to temporarily increase the accuracy of all units."/>
<entry name="HeartlessArtificerQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“Man can be more again. Become more by becoming less.”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="HeartlessArtificerWonFlavor" value="Peace. At last. You can finally hear yourself think. You celebrated this moment by ordering the execution of an advisor who dared sympathize with all those ground up by the turning cogs of conflict.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What a fool. Sympathy is for the weak. The weak who now lie dead in your lab, waiting for you to experiment on them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;One corpse draws your eye—its eyes are wide open, but black as night. You drag a scalpel across one —and it reaches up, grabbing you by the collar. It whispers in a language you can't understand. You try to pull away and then—you realize. You've known these words the whole time.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Voice is speaking to you."/>
<entry name="HollowWarlord" value="Hollow Warlord"/>
<entry name="HollowWarlordFlavor" value="To the Warlord, the end of the world was a rebirth. In his previous life… well, he wasn’t exactly an alpha. Or even a sigma. Telesales lines, bin trucks, burger flipper, AI wrangler—he’d been fired from them all. His only respite from tedious, grinding work was exercise. Lifting, running, wrestling, sweating away his drawn-out days.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;When the Fulcrum called, pulling humanity skyward to a rapturous rupture, nearly everyone else gave into the joy, not knowing the pain to come. But the Warlord felt that he’d hadn’t even lived yet, let alone earned redemption. So he fought, clung on to a chunk of rebar, shook off the false euphoria that carried Earth’s billions to the heavens—and in that moment, as colleagues burst and fell about him, he felt alive for the first time. Gore-spattered, exhausted, he roared with exhilaration.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After that, he didn’t hide from the horror. He staked his claim on the surface, gathered other survivors, fought the aliens and monsters, built an army, an empire, and then walked away from it. He’s learned to love the chase, racing away from moments of reflection and terrifying introspection.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With a small core of his followers, he’s survived for years on the surface and is ready to conquer the world again—to find what it has to offer and taste every part of it, take every part of it. He doesn’t know, yet, that his is a hollowness that can never be filled."/>
<entry name="HollowWarlordFoundationsFlavor" value="“IS THERE ANYTHING,” you bellow over the thrum of engines. “AS BLISSFUL AS THAT SOUND? THAT SMELL?” Your citizens cheer, whilst your soldiers growl happily, itching for war and glory.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Arms outstretched, you soak in the adulation. To most, the world ended two decades ago. To you and yours though, it’s an opportunity. Free of the divides of class, race, wealth, and education, you make your own way.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You’ve already won and given up a kingdom, but you regret nothing. Before your warriors head out, you advise them. To enjoy every moment, to thrill in every kill, to seize today because tomorrow never comes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Whether you conquer the world or die trying, you will revel in the trip."/>
<entry name="HollowWarlordFoundationsWithMutatorFlavor" value="You aren’t surprised that the Deep valued your wanderlust. After all, it itself is a mind forever voyaging, rich with self-knowledge, unable to ever know the end it is heading towards. And you do so love the journey.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;string name='Factions/HollowWarlordFoundationsFlavor'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="HollowWarlordLostFlavor" value="Now this is new. Rubble is lying across your body, with the collapsed garage roof slantwise on top, pinning you in place. Above the grumble of the enemy’s approaching vehicles, you can hear groaning and whimpering. Only some of it is coming from you.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Another new experience. You have lost!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Or have you? Miraculously, your bike is sitting clear of the collapsed buildings, dusty and scratched, but almost certainly still working. Reach it and you could escape, start again. A third coming, a third kingdom to build…&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you can just get the rocks off you… you shift, and the massive concrete roof slides an inch towards your head. If it slides completely, you’ll be decapitated. But you think you can just wriggle out-&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-darkness, soft velvet. In the silence left by the vanished whimpering a voice speaks. “Infinite empires are yours.” it says, pausing eternally. “But first-”"/>
<entry name="HollowWarlordProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Human Affinity:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Warlord is a simple man, interested in conquest, not cursed magic or alien technology. Start with %1% and gain early access to Human technologies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;We Who Are About To Die:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The adventures of the Warlord and his soldiers are told and retold in the city streets—as long as the blood keeps flowing. Every turn that your units kill or die, your cities’ loyalty increases, but otherwise decreases.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Tales of the Hunt:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The tales of the Warlord’s endless campaign spread far and wide. Attacking gives influence.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Restless:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The sharp-toothed townsfolk will not stand for idle warriors—and will not feed them either. Units in cities and outposts have increased upkeep. Gain less from trading pacts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Horde Mandate (Elite):&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; When the Warlord masses his forces for war they attack with vigor, eager to prove themselves to him. Spend influence to grant troops in a large area a bonus to attacks and movement."/>
<entry name="HollowWarlordQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“I came, I conquered, I will again.”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="HollowWarlordWonFlavor" value="Now this is a celebration. Hallooed songs, staggering drunks, crazy stunts, bare-chested fistfights, the smoke of a hundred fires darkening the air… you sidestep a drunken pair of kissing generals and keep walking. Cheers and backslaps everywhere you go.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Another victory. Another empire built. But already you sense the growing tremors that will collapse it. The ambitious advisers, generals susceptible to flattery, the corruption creeping into your pure engine of conquest.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Outside of the place where it all started, all is silent. Black Bess is still sitting there, where you left her. You turn the key in her ignition and fire sparks in her belly. She growls with desire for the road.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You look back for a moment, wondering if you missed something, if you are missed. But the world goes on and your next journey is calling.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Rather a Voice is calling. “Journey neverending…” You fight it off for a second, like you did the Fulcrum, rev Bess into the air and—&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;—and you are gone."/>
<entry name="HonorableAristocrat" value="Honorable Aristocrat"/>
<entry name="HonorableAristocratFlavor" value="The Aristocrat was young when the sky fell—but his parents were connected globally and he was taken into a government bunker with them at the first sign. He sat out the rapture, the war, the fallout, the starvation. His only complaint was that the preserved food was appalling and that no-one had thought to bring herbs or spices.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On the surface, billions died.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In that bunker, he followed in his parents’ footsteps, out of a sense of duty. He found that he was good—very good—at administration. And eventually, after unfortunate deaths, he found himself in charge.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Now his people are out, he runs the city like a patronage system, building up favours from traders and the markets before calling them in at times of emergency—or when he hears word of a new delicacy in town."/>
<entry name="HonorableAristocratFoundationsFlavor" value="Ah, but it is magnificent! This new city is a true beginning for humanity. A start as fresh as the boutonniere in the lapel of your fine suit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Congratulations flood in from the surviving peers of the wasteland on the foundation of your new polis. The ArchPope, the Communitard… the NeoDuke? Pah, they just want to be invited to the feast.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your city is barely built and already your network grows. Now is your time—to go out and reclaim Earth for your people."/>
<entry name="HonorableAristocratFoundationsWithMutatorFlavor" value="You remember tasting this moment, as through a mirror darkly. So proud you were. Now, facing the immediacy of the flesh, the Deep is fading. Perhaps it was just a bad dream, after bad cheese…?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;string name='Factions/HonorableAristocratFoundationsFlavor'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="HonorableAristocratLostFlavor" value="You planned out your death a long time ago. You'd intended to pass away under the cover of silken sheets following a most glorious feast where each of your close friends and family would have a chance to say goodbye.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some part of you wonders if the sheets can still be arranged for. Unlikely. The explosion that rattled your headquarters drove a piece of metal right through your chest. You think it also tore off one of your legs.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A bodyguard crawls up to you, equally wounded. He's pulled a stabilizer out of a medkit—still trying to save your life.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;His hand shakes too much. The stabilizer drops to the floor. “Take it,” he gasps. “Use it, for God's sake.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You have enough strength to pick up the stabilizer. You use the last of it to jab the needle in his neck—hear the telltale “hiss” as the healing particles mend his injuries. He protests as you eke out your last words: “honor compels me.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But they're only your last words for this life. Who knows what the next one will hold?"/>
<entry name="HonorableAristocratProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Human Affinity:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Art, music, and other luxuries of humanity are what made the Aristocrat fall in love with life. Start with %1% and gain early access to Human technologies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Honor-bound:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Honorable Aristocrat’s talents ensure the best deals for all. Trade agreements and alliances generate additional influence for both parties.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Hired Hands:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Hard work is not one of the Aristocrat's personal virtues, preferring to buy in help. Spend influence to rush production.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Gluttony:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; To the Aristocrat and his people, a refined palate is a basic survival need. Population food upkeep is increased.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Quid Pro Quo (Elite):&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The world's densest system of barter rested at the Aristocrat's fingertips. Spend influence to purchase vital resources."/>
<entry name="HonorableAristocratQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“Oh, you simply must try one of these. Deviled Abkluth eyeggs, my chef pulled the spines by hand. Eine Delikatesse, I won’t take no for an answer!”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="HonorableAristocratWonFlavor" value="Cries of jubilation rise from the street outside your manor. The war is over and you've called for a grand feast for all of your people. Debts to your government will be forgiven and any who must remain on duty will have their pay tripled. For a brief moment, your people can afford utopia.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You quickly visit your library on your way to the feast's opening, intending to retrieve your mother's pocketwatch. But when you arrive, all thoughts of a celebratory meal leave your mind. The books on the wall—where have they gone?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;That's when you realize. The walls have vanished. Your desk has vanished. It seems so unfair. You won. Why shouldn't you get to celebrate? But the universe has no mind for fairness. It has other plans for you.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Terrifying, grim plans."/>
<entry name="Neutral" value="Neutral"/>
<entry name="PracticalRomantic" value="Practical Romantic"/>
<entry name="PracticalRomanticFlavor" value="Before the Earth died, the Practical Romantic was a teacher—he took great joy in communicating poetry and wisdom to his pupils, raising the next generation to have warm hearts and open minds, to welcome all.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In the dark of the apocalypse bunkers, alongside his school peers, his mind was changed. He saw children and adults fighting for scraps of cloth to stay warm, killing for meat. He did more than watch. Eventually, he and his ashamed tribe emerged into the ruined world, a sadder, wiser Romantic.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though his idealism hasn’t changed, the Romantic is now more cautious and more practical—he will fight to preserve the riches of humanity, but recognise that those riches are only of use if humanity actually survives and is led by good people like himself, to rebuild a good world. In pursuit of that dream, the Romantic will do anything to survive."/>
<entry name="PracticalRomanticFoundationsFlavor" value="You’d never pray, per se. But building the walls of the city with your compatriots, your sweat mingled in the air, and your hands met. A joyous fellow-feeling there was, a remembered brotherhood (you suppress a memory of your own brother). A new start for humanity!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Like Ishmael squeezing the spermaceti in Moby Dick, this was a passing fancy. For, like Ahab, you have a purpose, to defeat the world’s greatest horrors. Which might mean putting aside your own desires, old-world morality. The simple joys of poetry and friendship are not for you now.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As your troops leave the city, you wonder whether you will know when you’ve lost your way."/>
<entry name="PracticalRomanticFoundationsWithMutatorFlavor" value="&lt;string name='Factions/PracticalRomanticFoundationsFlavor'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Oh Gentile or Jew&lt;br/&gt;O you who turn the wheel and look to windward,&lt;br/&gt;Consider Phlebas,&lt;br/&gt;who was once handsome and tall as you."/>
<entry name="PracticalRomanticLostFlavor" value="It's not the loss that guts you. It's your people. As terror rains down upon them, they revert to their worst selves. Riots break out in the streets, only being disrupted by enemy fire that hits your headquarters.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You're caught in one of those riots. The crowd doesn't even notice it's you—you're just another body being dragged along the streets. You shout, try to make it stop, but it's useless. Deja vu rolls over you—you lost your brother in a crowd like this once. You only escaped because a kind stranger helped.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There are no kind strangers here. You trip, you fall, and the crowd tramples you. Maybe it's time to give in, to think that this is what people really are—scared animals who turn on each other at a moment's notice.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But the part of you that hangs on—even as your bones crunch in the stampede—that's the part that caught the Voice's attention. It wants to know why you think these people are worth saving. And you'll have plenty of chances to plead your case…"/>
<entry name="PracticalRomanticProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Human Affinity:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Every innocent death tears at the Romantic's soul but his hope for humanity drives him on. Start with %1% and gain early access to Human technologies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Scavenger:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Romantic survived the apocalypse on the streets, salvaging everything he could to stay alive. Units generate resources by defeating enemies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;There Is Hope:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; His tongue was as silver as his beard. Spend influence to restore a unit’s morale.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Heartfelt Loss:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Romantic's people had more hope to lose when disaster struck. Morale losses are increased.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Reallocate (Elite):&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Once, a kind soul gave the Romantic a second chance. Now he does the same for his people. Reallocate units to regain resources and speed up production."/>
<entry name="PracticalRomanticQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“Before the fall, I would have quailed at the burning of a book. Now, in this freezing hell we have inherited, a bible is just fuel—and a man is just meat.”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="PracticalRomanticWonFlavor" value="The war ends, but the work doesn't.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your advisors tell you to stay in power, but you relinquish it the second you can. Let the bureaucrats fight for the right to rule. You try to find peace among your people by building houses and volunteering in refugee camps—how all great leaders should end their era of rulership.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You end each day watching the sunset bathe the capital city in golden light. Peace is the color of an amber sky and the sound of your people sitting down for food.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But today, that golden light slowly turns a shade of red. Your people's laughter falls silent, and your heart drops. Has the end of the world come again?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“No,” the Voice whispers. “Just the end of this journey.”"/>
<entry name="Random" value="Random"/>
<entry name="RandomProperties" value="Some see the Wasteland's leaders as cards in an ever-shuffling deck. These savvy-minded thinkers have many reasons to give themselves over to fate. Some fear the burden of ideology, while others live on the thrill of the draw. Whatever the reason, once the cards are dealt—it's important to play the hand you've been given."/>
<entry name="RogueOperative" value="Rogue Operative"/>
<entry name="RogueOperativeFlavor" value="When the sky fell, the Rogue wasn’t in the basements, bunkers and hidey holes with all else that remains of mankind. She’d grifted her way into a major biocorp’s HQ to get access to their server farm for her gang’s ends and ended up stuck there for the duration, living off vending machine food and hacking out all the corp’s dirty secrets.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;She’s not a natural leader, but she is a natural grifter. So when she emerged, it was backed by the remains of corp security. She quickly took charge of the remaining staff, promising that she’d use the firm’s bioaug tricks to survive.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And she will survive, whatever the cost. She doesn’t give a damn about the Acrin—though she’s wise enough to fear their horrors and history, she’s skeptical of the Voice and thinks they’re too trusting to be a threat any longer. Other human survivors are more of a challenge, for sure. But her eyes are set on ZEPHON—the biggest mark of all. If she can get close, she’s convinced she can make it dance to her tune."/>
<entry name="RogueOperativeFoundationsFlavor" value="Emerging, you see your followers have finished construction atop the old ICAR HQ. Now a city rings it, where once there was wasteland. Already, peddlers are setting up to serve the refugees trickling in. You check their wares—mostly junk. The Watchmakers and Concordat have already scavenged or bought up the good stuff.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But there’s more out there, under the rubble. Alien tech or Voice artifact, you need to get your hand on, to secure your independence. And that of your followers, of course. Worked alone so long, you forget you’re in charge.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Anyway, what are you waiting for? First to market takes all!"/>
<entry name="RogueOperativeFoundationsWithMutatorFlavor" value="You wake beneath the ICAR tower, nested in the mess of the executive suite. Remember The Deep and groan. Wonder if you can shortcut everything. Decide to get up and go out.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;string name='Factions/RogueOperativeFoundationsFlavor'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="RogueOperativeLostFlavor" value="You can still win this. There's always an angle. Sure the cities are on fire. Monsters roam the streets. But you weren't very keen on ruling a nation anyway. Your exit strategy is simple: get to the vehicle bay, get your Outrider, haul ass until you wind up in a town where no one knows your name.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Good plan. Simple plan. Doomed plan.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Before you can set one foot in the vehicle bay a gunshot rings out. It goes clean through your leg. Femoral artery bursts. Rips some of your favorite augments into shreds.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You fall to the ground—and one of your own soldiers walks up to you. “Sorry boss,” she says. “I cut a deal. Nothing personal.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Shitty way to go,” you gasp. But the soldier doesn't hear you. You aren't even sure the words left your mouth. Your vision turns white. You'd cut a deal of your own to get out of this—but there's no one you can bargain with.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As you take your last breaths, a buried memory rises to the surface: you already made a bargain. One that will send you back around the loop one more time."/>
<entry name="RogueOperativeProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Cyber Affinity:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; A world of cybernetic networks is just a playground for the Rogue Operative. Start with %1% and gain early access to Cyber technologies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Hit and Run:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The quick-witted Operative refuses to be bound by conventional tactics. Units may move after taking an action.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Augments:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Rogue Operative was born a skilled hacker but her augments turned her into a savant. Spend influence to augment a single attribute on a non-large unit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Independent:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; A crew of free-thinkers and radicals follow the Operative into battle—but they all are looking out for number one. Population has increased loyalty upkeep.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Icarus Satellite (Elite):&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The greatest secret weapon ever produced by ICAR Corp is now in the sole control of the Rogue Operative. Spend influence to fire it on enemy forces."/>
<entry name="RogueOperativeQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“Two prices. Price for the aug. And price for arguing about the price. What you want?”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="RogueOperativeWonFlavor" value="Cheers break out around the table when you share the news: the war is finally over. Freedom has returned to the wasteland.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your surviving comrades all gather round for drinks, asking each other what they'll do with the war over. “Whatever the hell you want!” you roar as you enter the room. “Build house. Start fight club. Knock down buildings. Just whatever you do, MAKE SURE NO ONE'S TELLING YOU DO IT!”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The cheers grow louder and louder. It doesn't matter that someone needs to pick up all the pieces—keep your people clothed and fed. For now, there's just jubilance.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jubilance and—static? Your hearing augs must be shorting out again. You reach up to touch them and—everything freezes around you.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You aren't free just yet."/>
<entry name="Spectator" value="Spectator"/>
<entry name="SpectatorProperties" value="There's much to be learned sitting in the stands of the arena. The watcher gains no glory when the match is won, but may learn much by studying those in the field. Voyeurs should never let their guard down. Forces greater than any person could comprehend are also watching, and have their own plans for player and spectator alike."/>
<entry name="TwistedMother" value="Twisted Mother"/>
<entry name="TwistedMotherFlavor" value="Events tell their own story. One day, a town is a bustling prison camp. The next it is empty, its inhabitants vanished overnight, reappearing miles away. A woman is changed by the necessary sacrifice. And her husband has vanished.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Mother started out as a housewife. Her husband worked on the oil fields, she kept the home and the farm. They were the heart of their prepper commune. Having their own family was the next step—one they both longed for. Life was bliss.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Then the sky fell.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Soon, the Acrin came. Disarmed the people, interned them. Performed desperate experiments to find the secret of survival in a world molecularly hostile to their alien bodies. The commune turned gradually into a concentration camp. And the people looked to the couple for leadership.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Who knows whether the Acrin experiments touched the couple? How their despair reached the Voice? What she sacrificed to transport her people so far?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All we see is the Mother and her people, far from their home. Though twisted and transformed, the mother still leads her people, aids them with her uncanny gifts. She’s not always aware that she’s changed—something has broken, she forgets herself. But she retains her hospitality, her care, her charm. She just wants to help her neighbours and guests.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though woe betide any who turn on those under her protection…"/>
<entry name="TwistedMotherFoundationsFlavor" value="“A picnic-” she starts, before you catch her. The you that pretends nothing has changed. Through her eyes you see concrete walls as white picket fences, minesweepers as gardeners tending their flowers. A tempting fantasy.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;string name='Factions/TwistedMotherFoundationsFlavorBase'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Your friends cheer the platitudes. Still, it is hard that not one looks you in the eye."/>
<entry name="TwistedMotherFoundationsFlavorBase" value="There’s a respectful silence at the city gates. Your followers know you, so give you a moment. You force your sweet delusions deep down and speak for them. “A picnic, this isn’t. Our green and pleasant land is gone.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You shift your bulk, ignore its incessant agonies. “But that doesn’t mean our amity is gone. Our friendship. Our community. It is on us to prove ourselves again, in this new land, this new flesh. And we will.”"/>
<entry name="TwistedMotherFoundationsWithMutatorFlavor" value="Love! After all that, was it just true love that defined you? There is more to you than this. It is trite, a tale from Morgenstern’s fairy tales.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Whatever. This is the greatest blessing a parent could wish for. Love does not judge a beloved’s qualities, only their existence. And for you three this loop will never end. To spend eternity struggling for and reaching your loves! O, bliss!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;… you have been lost in reverie again.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;string name='Factions/TwistedMotherFoundationsFlavorBase'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="TwistedMotherLostFlavor" value="Out of sight of their leaders, the soldiers do things that soldiers do. Keep the things that might give them pleasure. Burn what they can’t carry. They burn up your corn fields. And the farmers in them too.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Whilst your bodyguards hold off the looting soldiers, you take away the civilians. The mothers. The children. Deliver them into the wilds, tell them to seek sanctuary. Find prayers on your tongues again, and pray for the meek and mild.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There’s no escape for you though. After all, it’s you that the soldiers are after. So you stay as the gunfire and smoke gets closer.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As you wait, you think of your family. Of the feel of their hands in yours. A rough one, all nicks and leather, but gentle. And a soft small one, gripping tight.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A voice whispers then. That you’ll have another chance to see them. Very soon. A smile straightens your crooked lips.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And you call keenly to the enemy, to hasten the end."/>
<entry name="TwistedMotherProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Voice Affinity:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Though she isn’t aware of it, few have travelled deeper into the Voice than she has. Start with %1% and gain early access to Voice technologies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Gifts of the Voice:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; When her burning smile is turned to you, you feel so very special. Spend influence to buff your units… at a cost.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Tender Ministrations:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Despite her afflictions, the Mother insists that all her children care for one another. Increased healing rate if adjacent to an allied unit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Abhorrent:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Though her kindness is obvious, the Mother’s appearance and unreliable personality puts off independents. Gain less from trading pacts.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Immaculate Delivery (Elite):&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Her love envelops a target, passing it safely through the Bleed to another place. Spend influence to teleport units to allied units."/>
<entry name="TwistedMotherQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“We take care of our own, here. I take care of the rest.”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="TwistedMotherWonFlavor" value="You are mid-fairy tale as the messenger walks in, gingerly stepping around an enraptured audience of toddlers and their scattered toys. “-and then the Big Bad Abkluth huffed and puffed and…” a messy cacophony of noises follows as the children loudly thrill in the destruction of another piggy fortress.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A smile wrinkles the messenger’s face for a moment, then he walks to the front. And bends to whisper in your ears.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You forget the words immediately, but the sentiment stays. Tears run down your twisted face, across the twitching Voice-swollen flesh that binds you in place. The children gasp, fall silent and still.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A tubby child looks up belatedly from his bowl, frowning, confused. Leans into his friend’s ear, smearing them both with rice-porridge. And hoarsely whispers: “Did the piggies win?”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And you burst into happy laughter. “No, little one! We did!”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Behind your shoulder, something approaches, and a voice whispers, “We all win.”"/>
<entry name="UntoldProphet" value="Untold Prophet"/>
<entry name="UntoldProphetFlavor" value="The Untold Prophet first appeared to their followers as their bunker fell. Lit by the oscillating red glow of emergency beacons, words drowned by wailing klaxons, the child calmly beckoned for everyone to follow. While no one could recall this young stranger, all felt compelled by their presence.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For twenty-two days and twenty-two nights, the Prophet led them across the wasteland. The journey was a trial. Those that fled soon perished. Those that stayed, witnessed miracles everywhere the Prophet went. Supply caches refilled overnight, bandits wept and converted, and horrific beasts were gentled by the Prophet’s mere presence.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At the end of the twenty-second night, the Prophet stopped, looked around, then sat down. There they stayed, leading meditations and giving sermons, and their followers built a camp around them. More and more people came, attracted by rumors of the wise child, and the camp grew into a town, then a city, as their number swelled with new faithful.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If any notice the Prophet’s lack of aging or the odd way they tilt their head, as if listening to something only they can hear, none dare mention it. For despite their serenity, the child’s armies are fanatical—and storm across the distant pastures in the name of their Prophet."/>
<entry name="UntoldProphetFoundationsFlavor" value="On the blasted heath, they raise a shining white shrine to your glory. To, you mean, to the Great Speaker’s glory. A home for all the Earth’s lost peoples. Well, those who can believe.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The old words—crusade, jihad—are too laden with history. Let us say, then, that you have a quest—to restore faith to this ruined world. And to wipe those from it who won’t listen. For the good of all.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Man, machine or alien. Those who stand against the Great Speaker, will bow. One way or another."/>
<entry name="UntoldProphetFoundationsWithMutatorFlavor" value="Surely that was a dream. That can’t have been the end of all your striving? Perhaps if you do it again, this time, with more fervency, more faith… you won’t suffer that humiliation of the Deep…&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;string name='Factions/UntoldProphetFoundationsFlavor'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="UntoldProphetLostFlavor" value="Your great hall lies empty. Only you and one follower—a humble priest—linger. The sound of distant artillery has grown silent.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Great one,” the priest says. “I wish to confess my heresy.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You tilt your head towards him. He can't hear what you hear. Dark whispers describe how death will soon visit this hall. “I never believed in the Great Speaker. I lied for all these years.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“It's my fault,” he whispers. “My heresy brought us to defeat.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;He wails. You descend from the throne, a ceremonial knife hidden behind your back. You tilt the priest's head up and gaze into his eyes. “Please,” he says. “I beg your forgiveness.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Then he sees the blade. His eyes widen. You slit his throat. Forgiveness has been granted.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;When enemy troops burst into the hall, they find only the priest's body. The Great Speaker has already taken you to the next life."/>
<entry name="UntoldProphetProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Voice Affinity:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Great Speaker needed the Voice of a child to spread its wisdom to the world. Start with %1% and gain early access to Voice technologies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Cult Expansion:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Prophet's followers spread his Word across the land. Benefit from a reduced loyalty penalty for each city.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Words of the Prophet:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; All may be forgiven by the Prophet's touch. Spend influence to convert an enemy unit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Cost of Conviction:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The cult must never be allowed to waver. The Untold Prophet's population also has influence upkeep.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Armor of Faith (Elite):&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; The Untold Prophet's will is so strong, it can reshape reality itself to protect his most loyal followers. Make a unit temporarily invulnerable."/>
<entry name="UntoldProphetQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“I may be young, but I am without prejudice or preconception. It is my bendición that I see the choices you lost long ago.”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
<entry name="UntoldProphetWonFlavor" value="The Great Speaker told you this day would come. Victory has finally arrived.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is cheering in the street as your priests ride out to share the news. The faith of your people grows stronger than ever, and you feel the power of that faith wash over you like a warm cloud.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There's a noise—The Great Speaker's whispers. It must be pleased with your success. But the whispers grow louder, and louder, and you realize something isn't right, The Speaker is calling you, The Speaker.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Speaker isn't done with you."/>
<entry name="Zephon" value="ZEPHON"/>
<entry name="ZephonFlavor" value="ZEPHON is [your ally, your enemy]. ZEPHON is [ignorant, omniscient]. ZEPHON is [one, many], ZEPHON is [perfect, abomination]. ZEPHON is [blessed, cursed]. ZEPHON is [zen, hop]. ZEPHON is [coming, going]. ZEPHON is [transcendent, grounded]. ZEPHON is [thoughtware, meatware]. ZEPHON is [ZEPHON is [ZEPHON is [ZEPHON is-]]]. ZEPHON is [inside your systems]."/>
<entry name="ZephonProperties" value="&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Native:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; ZEPHON's machines linger on the battlefield, a part of an unknown plan that may end life as we know it. They already inhabit the world and are always at war with other natives.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Interminable:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; There are no boundaries to ZEPHON's cities and they expand quickly across the map. It has an infinite city radius with fast city expansion.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Defense Grid:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; To approach ZEPHON's territory is to court death. Its high-powered energy weapon attacks units close to its cities.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Eye of Zephon:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; Escaping the view of an omnipresent machine is frankly impossible. ZEPHON frequently views areas obscured by the fog of war.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;icon texture='GUI/Bullet'/&gt;&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Direct Control:&lt;style name='Default'/&gt; ZEPHON can direct a fragment of its intelligence to possess and empower a single machine. The targeted unit deals increased damage, regenerates health, and suffers less damage for a short time."/>
<entry name="ZephonQuote" value="&lt;style name='Italic'/&gt;“Communication channel established to ZEPHON-3. How may I help you?”&lt;style name='Default'/&gt;"/>
</language>
