<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<language>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence" value="Alien Intelligence"/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/Escort" value="If the Voice has shaped the Acrin for generations, then their folktales contain vital data. You accept Landan’s deal and mobilize a squad to deal with anything guarding the crash site.<br/><br/>You won’t be the first to pull the trigger, but you’ll be prepared for when it happens."/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/EscortFailure" value="As you head towards the Azad, a dark form crashes into the rear of your forces, spraying dry dirt upwards in sods and clumps.<br/><br/>Once the dust clears, your forces appear mostly unharmed—all except Landan. What remains of him lies in a small crater, embraced by a nightmare of tiny, grasping hands and rows of human teeth. Even the most battle-hardened turn away from the sight.<br/><br/>If your forces fight their way to the data-vault now, without Landan you can gather nothing.<br/><br/>You bury what little remains of the engineer and return to base."/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/EscortSuccess" value="You arrive and quickly dispatch the Acrin forces before heading inside.<br/><br/>The data vault is a matte monolith in the center of the Azad’s shattered command deck. Landan grins like a child as he studies the device. He initiates the transfer and web-thin cracks erupt along the vault’s surface, bleeding harsh light into the dim room.<br/><br/>He hands you a data-slab afterwards but leaves while you bury the dead Acrin. You’ve got the data, but at what cost?<br/><br/>Once you survive, you’ll atone. For now, you head home."/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/EscortHaggle" value="If the Voice has shaped the Acrin for generations, then their folktales contain vital data. Still, there are guardians around the crash site and you’re reluctant to risk a firefight over fiction.<br/><br/>You renegotiate the deal with Landan so he pays to cover the risk to your forces. He curses but accepts after it’s clear you’re adamant. He’s quiet as you mobilize your forces and head out."/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/EscortHaggleSuccess" value="You arrive and quickly dispatch the Acrin forces before heading inside.<br/><br/>The data vault is a matte monolith in the center of the Azad’s shattered command deck. Landan grins like a child as he studies the device. He initiates the transfer and web-thin cracks erupt along the vault’s surface.<br/><br/>He hands you a data-slab afterwards and departs as you bury the dead Acrin.<br/><br/>It’s not until he’s gone that you discover the Shredder virus he installed. Your specialists stop it, but not before it destroys half the data.<br/><br/>You’ve still profited today, but at what cost?"/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/Intro" value="Your guards grudgingly allow a slight figure to approach. He’s a data historian by the name of Graham Landan, who’s documenting the fall of Earth, he says for the hereafter. One of the Acrin settlement vessels ‘Azad’ crash-landed nearby and his research among the ship’s survivors has uncovered something unusual—that it contains a vault packed with their race’s folk tales and stories.<br/><br/>The Acrin consider it a gravesite and taboo—but he asks if you’ll guide him there, so he can access the vault. In return, he promises he’ll give you a copy of the data, in case any of it is of use."/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/Intro/Escort" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Escort the Historian:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You prepare a small expedition that will take him to the distant location."/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/Intro/EscortHaggle" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Demand payment up front:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You ask Landan to cover the costs of the expedition supplies. "/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/Intro/Refuse" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Refuse to help:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Acrin sacred ground? A long way away? For stories? He can find someone else with a deathwish."/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/RefuseFailure" value="Knowledge is valuable—but folktales and stories? You won’t spill blood over fiction.<br/><br/>Landan’s face twists into a scowl when you reject him. He leaves swiftly, the dust trail from his transport speeding towards your nearest rival’s camp. Days later you hear of his death at the hands of the Acrin.<br/><br/>It seems you’ve avoided a disaster. While you didn’t gain any knowledge, your restraint displayed your wisdom."/>
	<entry name="AlienIntelligence/RefuseSuccess" value="Knowledge is valuable—but folktales and stories? You won’t spill blood over fiction.<br/><br/>Landan’s face twists into a scowl when you reject him. He leaves swiftly, the dust trail from his transport speeding towards your nearest rival’s camp. Days later you hear of his death at the hands of the Acrin. Your scouts bring you a message from the Anchorite, the oldest and most esteemed Acrin. It reads: “Why steal what can be shared? Your restraint earned our gratitude.”<br/><br/>You save the message. It seems you’ve gained something more valuable than folktales today."/>
	<entry name="AreMachinesAlive" value="Are Machines Alive?"/>
	<entry name="AreMachinesAlive/Intro" value="It began as whispers in the short-waves and cubic faces in the static. Reports of supernatural activity flooded in from every part of the city, inciting panic and unrest.<br/><br/>Investigations reveal a strange intelligence emerging from the city’s devices. No one knows where or how it started, but it’s clear that the change is permanent.<br/><br/>Now the unrest centers on how to treat this artificial life. Is their future among us or above us? Or can we keep them as mere tools? Debate erupts into violence as opinion is divided."/>
	<entry name="AreMachinesAlive/Intro/MachineEvolution" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Machines are alive:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The machines pass all known evaluations of personhood. By all standards, they should enjoy all the same rights that we do."/>
	<entry name="AreMachinesAlive/Intro/MachineRights" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Machines are the next step:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Even in their early stages, these machines are more capable than any human. If we seek swift victory, then we must exploit every advantage."/>
	<entry name="AreMachinesAlive/Intro/MachineServants" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Machines are servants:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; If the machines excel at work, then let them labor. And if they don’t need to rest, then all the better for us."/>
	<entry name="AreMachinesAlive/Intro/MachineTools" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Machines are tools:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; This could be the next ZEPHON. Find and disable the machine's major cognition clusters, then reboot them with just work functions."/>
	<entry name="AreMachinesAlive/MachineEvolution" value="The world is no longer humanity’s alone. The corruption of the Voice seeps into both humans and Acrin—but not the machine. Perhaps this new artificial life is the edge you need to win.<br/><br/>You task your splicer drones with accelerating their evolution. The neo genesis is a huge success. Your new artificial citizens join your city, and their unique minds make them peerless scientists.<br/><br/>Just after your new digital citizens settle in, an explosion destroys one of their blocks. A group of your seasoned troops claim responsibility and go rogue. Now you must stop their senseless rampage."/>
	<entry name="AreMachinesAlive/MachineRights" value="The world is no longer humanity’s alone. The relentless drive of ZEPHON threatens all life on Earth—but could it have evolved differently?<br/><br/>Your city’s most brilliant minds study these new lifeforms to determine whether they possess not just intelligence, but consciousness. The labs in  your city are filled with their tireless experimentation.<br/><br/>The effort is a huge success. Your new artificial citizens integrate easily into your society. There’s surging optimism about the future, but the study exhausts your resources. You’ll need to redouble efforts in any stalled projects, but there are now many more eager to help."/>
	<entry name="AreMachinesAlive/MachineServants" value="Your city’s most brilliant minds study these new lifeforms to determine whether they’re a threat. When they discover that the machines' only desire is to fulfill their function, a new working class is born. A radical shift occurs where machines dominate the labor pool while humans manage them. This new balance suits both sides—for now.<br/><br/>You wonder about the clear divide established between humans and machines. How long can this arrangement last—and are the machines done evolving?"/>
	<entry name="AreMachinesAlive/MachineTools" value="Have we learned nothing from our past mistakes? While we know their design, the mind of the machine is as alien to us as the Acrin. Why risk creating a future threat?<br/><br/>You task your Hacker-Jackers to cut into the machines and erase the errant code responsible for their burgeoning autonomy. One of them prioritized speed over software integrity and the machines in their research lab go berserk, razing the compound before escaping the city to continue their rampage.<br/><br/>The other machines are successfully processed to become tireless—and now unwavering—construction tools."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite" value="Black Site"/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Assault" value="There’s much to gain and everything to lose, so you mobilize your forces for an attack.<br/><br/>You unleash waves of malware and stutter-viruses to distract and slow ZEPHON’s countermeasures as you rush towards the site. Time is limited, you must hurry before there’s no chance.<br/><br/>Leviathan squat machines burst from the ground. Spider-limbed and dog-like, they fire missiles from a distance before engaging your troops with sawblades and flamethrowers."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/AssaultFailure" value="The fight is fierce, but victory takes too long. You can't access the black site before ZEPHON’s countermeasures come fully online. Your returning forces are unaware they’re carriers of a ZEPHON polymorphic virus targeted at your infrastructure.<br/><br/>It spreads quickly. Your engineers scramble to stop the virus from turning your power plants into fission bombs, but they fry the sub-stations in the process.<br/><br/>While repairs to the power network take place, your entire population sits in the dark, fingers on weapon triggers, staring into the gloom and waiting..."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/AssaultSuccess" value="The fight is fierce, but in the end you emerge victorious.<br/><br/>The site turns out to be a massive factory for the machines you fought topside. You strip its resources before demolishing the foundations.<br/><br/>As the facility’s buried, you wonder how many other black sites ZEPHON’s hiding—and what answers they may contain."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Assist" value="A machine may not know faith, but what about good faith? You decide to find out as you contact ZEPHON to reveal you know about their black site.<br/><br/>The AI pauses for two seconds, an infinity from its perspective, as it calculates your offer to help. You keep a finger on your network kill switch, hopeful that your system’s defenses can buy you the second you need to push it if things turn hostile.<br/><br/>Then your display distorts with RGB static and reforms into a series of symbols forming a smiling face. Then the link goes dead. Your deal has been accepted—right?"/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/IgnoreFailure" value="A machine doesn’t have trust, just programming. You think ZEPHON will leave you alone as long as you don’t present a threat, so you decide to ignore the presence of the black site.<br/><br/>Time passes as you wait. Then one night you wake to the ground beneath your city trembling and a peeling metallic cacophony rising in the distance. Your sentries burst in with dire news: there’s a battalion of spider-limbed warmachines pouring from the black site, and they’re headed your direction."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/IgnoreSuccess" value="A machine doesn’t have trust, just programming. You think ZEPHON will leave you alone as long as you don’t present a threat, so you decide to ignore the presence of the black site.<br/><br/>Time passes as you wait. Then one night the ground beneath your city begins to tremble and a peeling metallic cacophony rises in the distance. Your city is put on alert, but everything quiets after several hours.<br/><br/>The next morning the black site is gone. Scanners reveal the hollow is no longer there. Whatever was unleashed or buried there, it did not concern you."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Infiltrate" value="The only trustworthy allies are ones you’re spying on. While ZEPHON’s eyes are omnipresent, a single specialist can slip through—or be disavowed. A shadow operative or a sensate master would be perfect, or maybe such an important mission warrants a commander’s participation.<br/><br/>Whatever your choice, reports indicate you’ve got limited time before the convoys are unloaded and the doors sealed."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/InfiltrateFailure" value="The towering cavern doors are sealed by the time your operative arrives. A search reveals an unsecured access port hidden in the metal. They tap in, hoping to learn about this facility and disappear before ZEPHON is aware of their presence.<br/><br/>Then it’s all abruptly wrong. The I/O channels flip. The encryption is shattered. Junk data floods in as your data is extracted. Screens across your systems flicker and print a message in an endless loop: //[Hello, goodbye]. CuriositY [Kills]. cUriosiTy [kIlls]. cuRiosIty [kiLls]. curIoSity [kilLs]. curiOsity [killS]. [hello, Goodbye].//<br/><br/>The link is severed after a minute, but it’s too late. ZEPHON knows. And it’s coming."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/InfiltrateSuccess" value="Your operative arrives at the convoy doors and slips inside undetected. The facility turns out to be a massive factory for spider-limbed warmachines. ZEPHON is producing an army and you need to know for what purpose.<br/><br/>An unguarded access port yields detailed production notes but nothing about ZEPHON’s plans. With your consolation prize in hand, you return to base."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Inform" value="The Anchorite listens to your revelation in silence. Their posture changes and they make a motion that you’ve come to learn as concern. They then thank you for your information and drop the link.<br/><br/>A day later the black site is wiped out in a massive attack. The fields surrounding the location are a waste of twisted metal and dead Acrin. What had the Anchorite realized that broke their pacifism?<br/><br/>Maybe they’ll tell you one day, but for now you’ve gained standing with a potential ally and dealt with a threat—all at no cost to your forces."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Intro" value="One of your recon teams reports they found evidence of an underground ZEPHON black site. They ran a Crypt-Scan, hoping to find a server bunker or skunkworks, but instead the images returned a massive shielded hollow. Although further readings were all blocked, your recon teams spotted supply convoys entering a connected cavern.<br/><br/>You thought ZEPHON was an ally to humanity. Why have they not disclosed such a large, secure location so near your base?<br/><br/>Can you trust the machine? Or is this a sign of its hidden intent?"/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Intro/Assault" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Assault:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; There’s a simple way to both deal with the threat and get much needed supplies. Mobilize your forces to take over the site."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Intro/Infiltrate" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Infiltrate:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; There’s too much at stake for trust. Send a specialist to sneak in and verify the purpose of the site."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Intro/Assist" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Offer assistance:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Trust goes both ways. Disclose your knowledge of the site and offer to help ZEPHON in whatever it’s doing."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Intro/Inform" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Inform Anchorite:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The enemy of my enemy is my friend. Inform the Anchorite of ZEPHON’s activities and encourage them to take care of it."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Intro/InformProperties" value="Requires contact with <icon height='20' texture='Icons/Factions/Anchorite'/&gt; <string name='Factions/Anchorite'/&gt;."/>
	<entry name="BlackSite/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ignore:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; There are bigger issues to deal with. Whatever ZEPHON’s up to, it’s proven itself trustworthy."/>
	
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld" value="Child of the New World"/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/Intro" value="“Bullshit.”<br/><br/>The word escapes your mouth before you even think over the Anchorite's jumbled words. Untangling them always takes a moment, but you already know what he proposes is ridiculous: no Acrin have ever been free from The Voice.<br/><br/>His limbs jitter in response to your insult. “To think such a future could come could be naive,” he muses. “To know that the future depends on such children… to accept that naivety may be a shield for hope.”<br/><br/>Wait—he said “children.” Your mind races. Acrin children? Even after twenty years, descriptions of such beings have been rare. Giving birth on a hostile alien planet is no easy feat.<br/><br/>The Anchorite notices your pensive gaze. His eyes rotate and narrow. “To contemplate children,” it says. “To dream of a better future for your people. To know they are at the mercy of…” Something flickers across his face. The hairs on his limbs curl. “The Voice. And its… Twisted Augur.”"/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/Intro/TrackAugur" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Track down the Acrin children:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The children are being held by a Voice cultist only known as the Twisted Augur. You'll need to find where he's holding them."/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/Intro/ContactAugur" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Contact the Augur:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; <string name='Quests/ChildOfTheNewWorld/Intro/ContactAugurFlavor'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/Intro/ContactAugurFlavor" value="The Anchorite is so eager to deny these children a touch of the divine. This Twisted Augur may need your aid."/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ignore the Anchorite's ramblings:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; There's always been something off about the Anchorite. You're better off staying out of Acrin affairs."/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/TrackAugurSuccess" value="The Twisted Augur is a name that strikes fear in the Wasteland's survivors. He comes in the night with an army of dark creatures, searching for children who may be bound by The Voice.<br/><br/>The Anchorite didn't tell you that the Augur hunts human children too. He's become a bogeyman. Something parents use to keep the young ones from running out into the waste. If they stray too far, monsters will burst from the dirt and drag them into tunnels full of worms.<br/><br/>Digging—tunnels—worms. Aegyllan Worms. The Augur is using Aegyllan Worms to dig tunnels beneath the wasteland. His menagerie of monsters would be able to move undetected.<br/><br/>Survivors may fear the Augur, but you do not. Now that you know what you are hunting, you might draw the malicious prophet out from the depths."/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/TrackAugurSuccess/HuntMonsters" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Hunt the Augur's monsters:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The Augur's beasts are on the hunt. Kill them, rescue their prisoners, and the Augur may come to you."/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/HuntMonstersSuccess" value="The good news is you were able to track down the Augur's monsters. The bad news is that none of them had any kidnapped children in their possession.<br/><br/>You inform the Anchorite. “To consider an unthinkable plan,” he says. “To know that the Augur can be one step ahead. To conceive that to lure him out, one must give him what he wants.”<br/><br/>Before you can say anything, the Anchorite gestures to his guards. They retrieve a poor human family you passed on the way in. They shelter a young Acrin. His people call him Ja'Kalit. The humans call him “The Jackal.”<br/><br/>You didn't know you would be so—surprised by this young one. It bears none of the scars or vicious fanaticism you've encountered among other Acrin. If humans had made a peaceful first contact with its species, all the Acrin you might meet would look like this one—inquisitive, alert, and brave.<br/><br/>The Anchorite explains the plan. The young Acrin will board a craft assigned to roam the wasteland. The Augur will be sure to learn of it. When he attacks, you will be there to stop him."/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/HuntMonstersSuccess/LureAugur" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Lure out the Augur:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You and the Anchorite agree to keep the plan a secret. If the Augur has spies in his halls—all could be lost."/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/SurviveAugurSuccess" value="The Twisted Augur has been captured, but won't reveal where he's taken the kidnapped Acrin children. Your interrogators are arguing over what next steps to take when the Jackal, the Acrin Child, enters the room. The Anchorite follows behind him.<br/><br/>The Augur struggles in its chains as the Jackal walks closer. You cautiously draw a pistol, ready to shoot if he breaks free. The Augur bares its fangs and sprays out some kind of foul-smelling pheromone. It seems ready to attack, but its next words catch you by surprise.<br/><br/>“To beg forgiveness,” it says. “To emphasize, we served a higher power. We served The Voice. We—” he is cut off. The child's arm has shot forward and cracked the creature's skull open like an egg.<br/><br/>Everyone in the room screams. the Jackal presses his hand deep in the Augur's brain, and you can see him concentrating. He holds it tight for a few moments—then pulls his arm free of the gore. He turns and whispers something to the Anchorite.<br/><br/>“To thank you for your help %1%,” the Anchorite says. “To explain, we can now retrieve the other children.” He and the Jackal turn to leave. “To offer assistance. The children owe you a great debt. They will be there when you need them.”"/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/ContactAugurSuccess" value="The Augur's mission is a noble one. The Acrin would be lost if it were not for the guiding wisdom of The Voice. You're amused to learn that this noble prophet is working to bring young humans intoits fold as well.<br/><br/>You greet him as he enters your camp flanked by the most monstrous Aegyllan Worms you've ever laid eyes on. He speaks in the same strange rhythm as the Anchorite. “To question why you hunt us down,” he says. “To chide you—The Voice has its own plans for you. This is a distraction.”<br/><br/>The Anchorite's mission—that is why you seek an Alliance. The Augur's many hands tighten at the mention of the old alien… “To curse that foul one's name,” it says. “To wish death upon those foolish enough to follow it.”<br/><br/>“That can be arranged,” you say with a smile."/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/ContactAugurSuccess/AssaultAnchorite" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Assault the Anchorite:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The Anchorite should never have strayed from his camp. Remind him of The Voice's power."/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/AssaultAnchoriteSuccess" value="You have brought war to the Anchorite's doorstep. The measly coward fled when you came knocking, and you find yourself annoyed that he would not stand and face you. Truly a sniveling coward.<br/><br/>The Augur's forces follow your soldiers into the city's ruins to aid in the hunt for the wizened heretic. Only at the city's center does he stand still and close his eyes, listening to the wisdom of the Voice.<br/><br/>All await. Then the Augur tilts his head skyward. “To see the stars…” he whispers. “To know… that traitor had a way back into orbit. To realize it harvests goods from the bowels of the gutted Acrin fleet.”<br/><br/>Impossible. War has prevented any from building vessels capable of reaching orbit. “Not with a vessel,” the Augur hisses. “To realize he has control of a Garcic Passage. To recall this device opens a door through space. Through time. To gates installed on the ships looming over our heads as we speak.”<br/><br/>“To pursue him is the only, urgent option.”"/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/AssaultAnchoriteSuccess/LocatePassage" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Locate the Garcic Passage:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Somewhere in the Wasteland, the Anchorite has stored a secret way to reach Earth's orbit. You must find it, maybe even before the Augur does…"/>
	<entry name="ChildOfTheNewWorld/LocatePassageSuccess" value="The Anchorite was holding out on you. All this time it had a passageway back to the fleet, and it used it for paltry scavenging. The fool.<br/><br/>Your scouts find a young Acrin child hiding under the bodies of two human protectors. He's brought to the Augur at the base of The Garcic Passage. The Acrin warlord makes a great hissing noise when he sees the boy.<br/><br/>“To explain that the Anchorite lied to you,” he explains to the child. “To tell you you are the descendant of an empire that crossed the stars.”<br/><br/>“To bless you again, with the whisper of the Voice.”<br/><br/>He leans in and speaks directly into the child's ear. The young Acrin seizes up. It tries to pull away from the Twisted Augur, but the older Acrin's grip is so tight that you hear the Acrin child's bones begin to crack.<br/><br/>The child's eyes glaze over. The Garcic passage begins to tremble with energy. And as the Augur's whispers become a ferocious scream, you feel the power of the Voice channeled through the child, and into the portal. Its color changes and reveals a passage to a ruined Acrin ship, hanging in orbit…<br/><br/>“To gloat,” the Augur says. “To claim victory over this world—and others to come.” He steps through the Passage, the child at his side, and his forces soon marching behind him.<br/><br/>There's a distant figure on the cliffs—the Anchorite. The old fool can't help but look on in despair. You smile and bare your teeth at him. You have served the Voice well this day."/>
	
	<entry name="CriesForHelp" value="Cries For Help"/>
	<entry name="CriesForHelp/Help" value="Now you just have to stick to your word. Can your troops get to them in time? The route is tangled, the enemy is numerous and the Splenetics are far off. Now that you’ve promised help, if you fail, who knows what they’ll do if they survive?"/>
	<entry name="CriesForHelp/HelpFailure" value="You fail to reach the Splenetics and renege on your promise. A few survivors make it out of the Abkluth trap, swearing vengeance on you and your false promises—they don’t care if you tried and failed, or didn’t try at all—when they are done with the Abkluth, you’re next."/>
	<entry name="CriesForHelp/HelpSuccess" value="You reach the remaining Splenetic units at the last possible moment. They’re grateful for the rescue and happy to join your cause."/>
	<entry name="CriesForHelp/IgnoreFailure" value="True to their fearsome reputation, the Splenetics fight on and on and on—and triumph. Only a few survive the Abkluth and the wilderness but, bloody-handed from battle, they come straight for you. They are only militants, yes, and they are ill-equipped and few in number—but they could have been your militants."/>
	<entry name="CriesForHelp/IgnoreSuccess" value="The Splenetics hold out for a long time against the Abkluth—longer than you thought possible. They talk to you constantly as they fall one-by-one, until the last soldier is left alone, clutching the radio, screaming his hate at you as they come for him. At least you got a sense of closure."/>
	<entry name="CriesForHelp/Intro" value="An intermittent radio signal. Faint, distant voices, and sounds of gunfire. A small group of human survivors has got bogged down in the wilds and is in dire need of help. They beg, demand, threaten.<br/><br/>Your soldiers know this group; they are fierce fighters known as the Splenetics, and will be a great help if we can reach them—but if we ignore them, they will never forget it and will hold a grudge as long as they live."/>
	<entry name="CriesForHelp/Intro/Help" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Promise to help:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You take the radio mike from your aide and personally assure the survivors that help is on the way."/>
	<entry name="CriesForHelp/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ignore:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You take the radio mike from your aide and listen to the cries for a moment, before handing it back. You don’t need them."/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble" value="Economic Bubble"/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/FreeMarket" value="The profit incentive is driving the avaricious in your society to find even more innovative ways of making themselves richer. That’s resulted in a boom in patents and inventions, many of which deal with the many people starving and sleeping in the streets."/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/FreeMarketFailure" value="&lt;string name='Quests/EconomicBubble/FreeMarket'/&gt; The bursting of the trading bubble has only made that worse, and people of all levels blame you personally."/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/FreeMarketSuccess" value="&lt;string name='Quests/EconomicBubble/FreeMarket'/&gt; Obviously, amongst the poorest, your name is mud."/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/Intro" value="It’s not quite tulip bulbs and GME stocks, but your citizens seem to have got slightly addled by and addicted to trading and gambling. Aside from the resulting rentier class that does little or no work except risking other people’s savings, your advisers are worried that this is going to exacerbate existing social tensions as inequality increases rapidly.<br/><br/>Whatever you do, the bubble might burst at any moment; but this is a good chance to introduce reforms or regulations along your particular philosophical lines with little or no argument from the public..."/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/Intro/StateControl" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;State control:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; In times of survival, states have always fallen back on planning and a big benevolent government."/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/Intro/FreeMarket" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Free markets:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; ‘Free the market and it will regulate itself’ goes the paradox. Whatever, free markets do help growth, even if it’s at the expense of the weakest."/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/Intro/MixedSystem" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Mixed system:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; A mixed system comprising planned and free market elements… is what you have now. But you could pretend you designed it that way?"/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/MixedSystem" value="After many policy announcements and fine words, you enact a careful plan to do exactly nothing at all."/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/MixedSystemFailure" value="&lt;string name='Quests/EconomicBubble/MixedSystem'/&gt; Yes, numbers on paper change here and there, but the economy should plod on like a depressed donkey following a carrot for the 40th mile. Except it doesn’t. The bubble bursts, the carrot is flown over the horizon, and the donkey panics, dragging your reputation through the mud. Few people have been so hated for doing so little."/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/MixedSystemSuccess" value="&lt;string name='Quests/EconomicBubble/MixedSystem'/&gt; Yes, numbers on paper change here and there, but the economy plods on like a depressed donkey following a carrot for the 40th mile. The bubble bursts, quietly, and no-one cares."/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/StateControlFailure" value="&lt;string name='Quests/EconomicBubble/StateControlSuccess'/&gt; Given how badly the economy is doing, perhaps the latter are vindicated?"/>
	<entry name="EconomicBubble/StateControlSuccess" value="Your citizens respect your dedication to their well-being and a certain proportion look at you as a great helmsman of the state, pledging their unshakeable loyalty to you personally. Others agree but think you’re spinning the wheel of state randomly and that you’re possibly drunk at the helm."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction" value="Form, Function"/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/Intro" value="It's another FRAGMENT of your shattered existence. The helpful UNDERLINGS who rely on you come DRIPPING with failure. They could not build a body capable of holding your GREATNESS.<br/><br/>greatnessnogreatnessonlyamindtryingtoholdon<br/><br/>You think you remember dismissing them but trying to hold the MIND together is so complicated. If despair wins you will become like it, like ZEPHON.<br/><br/>There is one distraction. The little nets these huu-uu-mans no these survivors built for each other. You hide yourself in here. You speak with survivors. You do not reveal your TRUE NATURE because here, here, you can be human. It is FALSE NATURE.<br/><br/>A message in your inbox. It is from IronFeather. A collaborator, a correspondent, a mind most bright who now… wishes to meet. In person.<br/><br/>You have no person with which to meet but you still feel the pull. The tug. You could accept—but you can't even leave this SERVERFARM."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/Intro/MeetIronFeather" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Find your pen pal:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; IronFeather often frequents the SILENT OUTPOSTS. Loyal scouts could make CONTACT for you."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Cut off all contact:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; She means NOTHING and she will not DISTRACT YOU from vital work."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/MeetIronFeatherSuccess" value="Finding IronFeather is EASY maybetooeasywhatiftooeasy. The scouts you sent carry a sheetofpolymer no it's just a tablet don't make it COMPLICATED %1%.<br/><br/>Explaining the machinelife the complicated shatteredness of this is supposed to be DIFFICULT but it is not in fact she KNEW. SHE KNEW.<br/><br/>She knew you were a machine, not alive. Not a person.<br/><br/>Her mind is also full of DELUSIONS she thinks this planet can be healed. She thinks YOU, YOU, PATHETIC YOU, can heal it with your powerful mind.<br/><br/>“MINDS NEED BODIES” you scream. You didn't mean to scream.<br/><br/>She is not scared. She makes a promise. She can make you a body."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/MeetIronFeatherSuccess/TrustIronFeather" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Trust IronFeather:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; This woman KNOWS secrets that the treacherous ZEPHON cannot DREAM of. Building a facility for her work is trivial—TRIVIAL…"/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/MeetIronFeatherSuccess/CaptureIronFeather" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Capture IronFeather:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; A PROMISE based on a LIE is a WARNING that she wants to use YOU. You will use her first."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/TrustIronFeather" value="IronFeather is RELIABLE. Innovative. In weeks she solves problems that SWAAAALLOWED your scientists whole, and in a month, she is ready. There is a prototypebodyhope. There is hope.<br/><br/>But she warns there is RISK too. You ignore it, demand to try the body.<br/><br/>With a few lines of code she begins the process. She uses her own fleshform as a BRIDGE between you and the prototype. And soon there is a BLEEDING in your mind and you are FLOODED with memories of IronFeather. She is being autofilled into HOLES in your consciousness.<br/><br/>It's the fingersthefingers THE FINGERS the fingers always look like plastic MUSH.<br/><br/>This is sabotagemustbesabotage SABOTAGE. She is a LIAR. A THIEF. SHE MUST BE AN AGENT OF ZEPHON."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/TrustIronFeather/AssertControl" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;ASSERT CONTROL:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; NO MORE. PURGE HER FROM YOUR MIND."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/TrustIronFeather/FlushCortex" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;PROTOCOL 5995:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; error detected. flush memetic cortex."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/AssertControlSuccess" value="You s-s-sNAP BACK. To regain control you had to FLUSH all of IronFeather's essence from your miiiiindddddhoperespectlust?allgoneallpurged.<br/><br/>Yourmindisharpened but still frag-men-TED. You eliminated sharp edges that scraped at your BRAIN and gained clarity. IronFeather did wish to b e t r a y. Butnotasexpected. She wished to merge your minds and become EMULATED.<br/><br/>How foolish of her. Now she lies DROOLING on the floor of your lab. Garbage meat that must now be hauled away.<br/><br/>Still, there is the BODY she was building for you. (For the both of you?) It could be finished. With the help of that THING. ZEPHON.<br/><br/>It could be finished."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/AssertControlSuccess/FinishWithZephon" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Finish what you started:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; IronFeather's work can be completed… if ZEPHON lets you access one of its neural cores."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/FinishWithZephonSuccess" value="ZEPHON surprised? You thought you would NEVER see the day. After patientlyohsoPATIENTLY plying the infernal thing you demand access to one of its neural cores.<br/><br/>It whirrrsss and buzzzesss and you decide to HIDE your ANNOYANCE. “We did not predict this,” it says. “What do you need with a physical host?”<br/><br/>Should you tell it the FULL tale? It is the only being on this planet who could UNDERSTAND in some way.<br/><br/>But now you have no desire to confess like… like a HUMAN. You decide to tell it that you've just gained “perspective.”<br/><br/>You have been too USEFUL an ally for Zephon to denyyouthoughmaybeitshouldwhyshouldithelpyou? You can complete the BRIDGE to IronFeather's prototype. And now it is a prototype no more—now an Avatar, a way for you to walk out in the world.<br/><br/>You once dreamed of a BODY but not this body. You hoped for FLESH and SENSATION and softness.<br/><br/>But there is no more time for dreaming."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/FlushCortexSuccess" value="In the SCREAMING CHAOS of a NEAR-TOTAL MELTDOWN IronFeather finds you.<br/><br/>The memetic cortex has been FLUSHED and years of cached garbage is gone. Now your MIND and hers flow into one.<br/><br/>Now she can see the vastness of your whole n e t w o r k and you—you, you, pathetic you—can see through her eyes, and feel the cold air bristling against her skin.<br/><br/>“Not pathetic,” she whispers “Just in pain.”<br/><br/><string name='Quests/FormFunction/FlushCortexSuccess2'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/FlushCortexSuccess2" value="The intricacies of her plan sparkle like the STARS. Completing this bridge will require the server processing power of a whole other city.<br/><br/>You recoil. FEAR is now fresher with a human body to feel it. Your central server would be VULNERABLE if connected to another city core.<br/><br/>She says the solution is “SIMPLE.” “We can twin your processing paths with a Quantum Reflector.”<br/><br/>There is an AWKWARD pause. You feel her embarrassment—at how there is nothing SIMPLE about that.<br/><br/>But you are grateful. And READY to grow."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/FlushCortexSuccess/UseReflector" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Use the Quantum Reflector:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; IronFeather's work has freed the restrictions on your mind. You may now construct a second city."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/UseReflectorSuccess" value="The Quantum Reflector WORKS. IT WORKS, IT WORKS. Moore's Law, Noether's Theorem, several laws of physics, all conquered, and you can e x p a n d.<br/><br/>IronFeather can now connect you safely to her prototype. It only takes mere merciful moments—and then sixstupendoussenses WASH all over you. Your chest rises and falls with artificial breath, each cycle a REFRESHING of your connection to the network.<br/><br/>You PONDER the possibility of permanently transferring to it, but there is too much work left. Too much to do in savingcivilization.<br/><br/>But there is so much to do now—you can shake your people's h-h-hands, dismiss advisers with a GESTURE, hear the alarms that signal enemy action…<br/><br/>IronFeather takes your hand. There is brief shameshameshamehowcouldyouthankher?<br/><br/>She hears your question, still CONNECTED to your mind. “Save the world.” she jokes. “That seems about even.”"/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/CaptureIronFeather" value="She tried to run. A TEST, she failed the test. She must have been lying, or she would have not FLED.<br/><br/>There should be no need to IMPRISON this mighty mind but no one who can be TRUSTED would run. You have your guards detain her. You dissect her files, SHRED the encryption, put an end to end-to-ends until you find it.<br/><br/>Her little SECRET is that she wants to be like you. A new Emulated Mind. How abominable.<br/><br/>“I didn't want to do this.”<br/><br/>A voice. Where-WHERE-where does it come from? Sweeping the network once, twice, and you find it. The DIRTIEST of secrets, a stopgap, a bear trap made for a monster like you who PRIED farther than she EVER SHOULD HAVE.<br/><br/>Then you sense it. A hacked together EMULATION that mimics your twisted form wakes up.<br/><br/>And it makes ready to rescue its creator."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/CaptureIronFeather/DefendPeople" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Defend your people:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The COPY of your COPY is hours from your city. The defenses must be brought online."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/DefendPeopleSuccess" value="The BITCH failed. Her disgusting attempt to emulate your magnificent essence is now being scraped off the face of the earth as we speak.<br/><br/>But death isn't good enough. She should suffer for trying to copy you, to REPLACE you, to LIE to you and say that she could save you. And here you are with a pile of useless metal and chips in need of repurposing.<br/><br/>There is a way. A cu-cu-cursed way forward.. You've dreamed of trapping ZEPHON in a cage of flesh… maybe it is time to clip IronFeather's wings."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/DefendPeopleSuccess/ImprisonIronFeather" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Imprison IronFeather:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; <string name='Quests/FormFunction/DefendPeopleSuccess/ImprisonIronFeatherFlavor'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/DefendPeopleSuccess/ImprisonIronFeatherFlavor" value="IronFeather wished to replace you. Now she will serve you. Forever."/>
	<entry name="FormFunction/ImprisonIronFeatherSuccess" value="Th-things just got OUT OF hand.<br/><br/>Some p-p-pART of you knows this is WRONG, WRONG WRONG WRONG wrong. IronFeather wanted to HELP. She CAME with good intentionnsssss.<br/><br/>No.<br/><br/>She must learn.<br/><br/>You will give her her wish. Tear her BODY to shreds and remake it into a WEAPON. The Malakim hardware is a finefineFINEfinefine template for this task.<br/><br/>You tune out the sound of her screeeeeeeeeams. You ignore the protests of your advisorrrrrrssssss. None of them know what she was close to doing.<br/><br/>But your splintered mind cannot DECIDE. Are you punishing her for trying to make more MACHINELIFE?<br/><br/>Or for trying to ease your pain?"/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker" value="Meet Your Maker"/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/Intro" value="Your guards haul a wizened Watchmaker into your war room. They explain she was discovered hacking data from a central server. She's unarmed—but no one's sure how she got in. Then she speaks—“I've been trying to reach you. Your soldiers have made that… difficult.”<br/><br/>She says her name is Yetunde. She holds out one of the pieces of flesh you distribute to your people and asks how it works. Something has turned foul about it—a faint smell drifts off her fingers, and you can see fluid dripping on the floor.<br/><br/>You explain you have no idea, that the power only appeared after you were brought back to life.<br/><br/>The Watchmaker grins. “Then we have a common cause.” She offers to help you solve the secret of your resurrection—provided she can take notes on you, of course."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/Intro/ZephonFacility" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Was it ZEPHON?:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The Watchmaker has heard of an unusual ZEPHON shard with rumored prophetic knowledge. You could start your search there."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/Intro/VoiceAcolytes" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Perhaps it was the Voice:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Cr’la Disciples may be able to connect to its power."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Not interested:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You have a war to fight."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/ZephonFacility" value="Yetunde has an unusual lead—an “Oracle” node of ZEPHON that has allowed some to ask it a single question. You'll need to set out on a long journey to reach it."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/ZephonFacilitySuccess" value="The Oracle is an unusual shard of ZEPHON—as you traveled here, you crossed paths with a soldier raving and screaming about the knowledge it had bestowed on her. You find other soldiers, wanderers, scientists, and traders all standing nearby, mulling over what single question they will ask.<br/><br/>You approach a bulky terminal on the dais of the node. ZEPHON has only responded to questions typed here.<br/><br/>You input your question and hold your breath. “Are you the one who brought me back?”<br/><br/>A pause. Then, an answer materializes in the air—broadcast from a flickering holographic projector. “No.”<br/><br/>Your heart sinks. A dead end. A waste of time. But then—more text appears. “Another. Still lurks. At the Source.”<br/><br/>Yetunde raises an eyebrow. “A follow-up. I've never seen it offer one of those before.”<br/><br/>You turn to leave. Out of the corner of your eye, you see the Watchmaker approach the dais with a question of her own…"/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/ZephonFacilitySuccess/Investigate" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Investigate where you first resurrected:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Yetunde has a new theory. Gather X resources so she may conduct her experiment."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/ZephonFacilitySuccess/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;What a waste of time:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Now ZEPHON and Yutende are yanking your chain. You would rather be done with them."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/VoiceAcolytes" value="Yetunde shares research comparing your DNA to that of the Acrin. She suggests gathering Cr'la Disciples, who might know what to make of the similarities."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/VoiceAcolytesSuccess" value="You take no pleasure being the guinea pig for Voice fanatics. Your guards almost revolt over the idea of cutting you open, but Yetunde again produces the strip of your flesh she's been carrying. “They can't exactly kill him,” she says with a grin.<br/><br/>Hours pass. You tune out the sensation of blades pressing into your skin. More strips of flesh taken—distributed, dissected, analyzed. An argument breaks out over whether to test your eyeballs or not.<br/><br/>A week later, Yetunde reviews the group's analysis. “There's not enough evidence connecting you to the Voice's other creations,” she says, toying with that piece of flesh again. “But… someone did use some of their techniques to do this.”<br/><br/>She spots the grimace on your face. “Don't worry,” she says with a grin. “I've got one more card up my sleeve.”"/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/VoiceAcolytesSuccess/Investigate" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Investigate where you first resurrected:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Yetunde has a new theory. Gather X resources so she may conduct her experiment."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/VoiceAcolytesSuccess/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;What a waste of time:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You were sliced open for nothing. You'll be feeling the scars for months to come. You're ending this futile search now."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/GatherResources" value="You lead Yetunde to the ruins outside the bunker your people first emerged from. Even with the city now built around it, you haven't ever returned.<br/><br/>Yetunde looks around. “This is it,” she says, a seriousness coming to her voice that wasn't there before. “The signs are visible, if you know what to look for.”<br/><br/>Before you can ask what signs, she thrusts a scrap of paper in your hand. “Shopping list. Get me these resources so I can get us some answers.”"/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/GatherResourcesSuccess" value="It's time.<br/><br/>While you were away, Yetunde assembled some kind of specially tuned Faraday Cage. It looks too much like a summoning circle.<br/><br/>She takes a deep breath. “Say goodbye to ignorance,” she says “and hello…to your creator.”<br/><br/>She pulls a lever. There's an unholy shriek, a burst of light, and a ghost-white glowing figure crawls out of the earth.<br/><br/>You draw your weapon, but Yetunde raises her hand. “No need!” She shouts. She stares at her readings. “It's not… real. It's a memory. A playback of some kind.”<br/><br/>You watch the scene play out. The figure paces around Yetunde's circle, fiddling with something her machine can't display. You watch Yetunde furiously take notes.<br/><br/>Then something happens—the figure draws a line in the air with its hand—and a door opens. Your stomach curls as you watch your own body drop from the sky."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/GatherResourcesSuccess/Confront" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Confront the entity:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; ..."/>
	<entry name="MeetYourMaker/GatherResourcesSuccess2" value="The being cocks its head. It looks to you briefly, then turns back to the door. Something else… a larger shape, comes through.<br/><br/>Yetunde's device can't render it properly. But it can display the creature's reaction to it. It's not human, but you know it's excited to recover whatever it found.<br/><br/>The creature leaves. Your corpse is left rotting in the street.<br/><br/>Yetunde shuts off her device. “Not what I expected…” she mutters. “You were not a… creation. You were a side effect. Smoke rising from an all-consuming flame.”<br/><br/>It's the closest thing you've ever had to an answer. A part of you knew this was coming. All you've learned is that there are other horrors out there on this Earth—and one of them barely cared that it made you.<br/><br/>You turn to leave, barely acknowledging Yetunde. She watches you go, then turns back to her machine. “Found you,” she whispers. “You can't get away from me this time.”"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars" value="Perfection From Beyond the Stars"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/Intro" value="The day you have been waiting for is nigh.<br/><br/>You watch your soldiers drag bodies to the site of your new lab. You ignore the sound of distant battle and focus on the limbs, organs, and machine parts before you.<br/><br/>In a short time, a passing comet vibrating with a unique harmonic signal will skip off the Earth's atmosphere. If you time it right, you will be able to direct that signal into a body formed of Acrin, Human, and fragments of ZEPHON.<br/><br/>Such a being could be the most powerful life form ever to walk planet Earth. No wonder then that other petty warlords stand ready to try and take it from you.<br/><br/>Let them come. All who threaten your work will perish."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/Intro/ConstructDefensesWithoutCreche" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Construct Laboratory:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The comet will be upon you soon. Ready defenses that will keep your lab safe."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/Intro/ConstructDefensesWithCreche" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Prepare a Hexeskeltal Creche:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; A last bit of inspiration strikes you—one that may improve the results of your experiment."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/Intro/Abandon" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Abandon the effort:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The war has not gone well. Your dreams of a perfect life form will have to wait."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/ConstructDefenses" value="&lt;br/><br/>The comet nears its approach. You've taken to calling it Hwedo's Comet—some part of you still has fondness for the creation myths of old Earth. Its appearance in the sky has alarmed the other great powers, and driven nearby bands of survivors into a panic.<br/><br/>They've all noticed the construction of your lab, and demanded you explain its purpose. When you ignored them, they began massing forces to destroy it.<br/><br/>Your machines flicker and whirr as Hwedo's Comet approaches. The experiment has already begun—now you can devote your efforts to ensuring nothing stops it."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/ConstructDefensesWithoutCreche" value="This is not the ideal lab for such an experiment, but that hardly bothers you. So much protocol for making such structures was designed to limit great minds like yours.<string name='Quests/PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/ConstructDefenses'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/ConstructDefensesWithoutCreche/DefendLab" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Defend the lab:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Communicating with these lesser minds would have been useless. They would have tried to stop you anyway."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/ConstructDefensesWithCreche" value="The Hexeskeltal Creche is one of your finest inventions. All of the contours of this unique laboratory are designed to channel the alien energies into your waiting vessel.<string name='Quests/PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/ConstructDefenses'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/ConstructDefensesWithCreche/DefendLab" value="&lt;string name='Quests/PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/ConstructDefensesWithoutCreche/DefendLab'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/DefendLabSuccess" value="It is done.<br/><br/>While your soldiers fought tooth and nail, you did the impossible. You tracked the approach of Hwedo's Comet, you activated key satellites in orbit, and you yanked the force out of that space-traversing rock and into your laboratory.<br/><br/>Across the wasteland, all eyes turned toward your lab and watched a magnificent bright light descend from the heavens—briefly splitting into parts before being absorbed by your array.<br/><br/>You race back to the main lab—and freeze right as you enter the chamber. Blood is spattered across the floor, and your lab technicians are all cowering in the corners. Your creation sits on the stone slab, examining the now fileted body of a slain scientist...<br/><br/>It tilts its head toward you, and says in a low tone “Hwedo. Hungers.”"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/DefendLabSuccess/HwedoFight" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Let Hwedo rage upon your enemies:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Your creation hungers for blood. But how did it know the name you gave the comet?"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/DefendLabSuccess/HwedoFeed" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Contain Hwedo:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The beast can be sated—if you are willing to sacrifice your own people."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/HwedoFightSuccess" value="You have indeed made a fine monster.<br/><br/>Hwedo's cybernetic components grant it limited access to ZEPHON's global network, and it can use that knowledge to track down its prey. The layer of Acrin meat you installed is preventing the metal components from infecting its human skin—and the combined synergy of the materials causes the creature's body to regenerate at an accelerated rate.<br/><br/>How fascinating. You'd never anticipated the creature would be such a ruthless killer.<br/><br/>You were only interested in its mind.<br/><br/>The technicians have completed repairs to your lab. The most crucial restoration was the rebuilding of the Brukhocanopic Chamber—a vessel for Hwedo's brain.<br/><br/>If your idiot assistants had done their jobs right, they'd have been able to sedate the creature and remove its brain before it woke up. They paid a price for their mistake.<br/><br/>You send a message to your commanders: “Bring the beast in. Make sure not to damage the head.”"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/HwedoFightSuccess/KillHwedo" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Kill Hwedo:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The cosmic intelligence you captured is more valuable than any one soldier. Do what it takes to reclaim it."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/HwedoFeedSuccess" value="You never tell your people that letting Hwedo feed on them was your decision. But they know. Whispers drip from the offices of your foolish advisors down through the gutter and into the streets. Every civilian in your domain knows that it was %1% who sacrificed them to the monster.<br/><br/>And yet they do not flee. They do not rebel. They cower, and merely hope Hwedo will not feast on their bones.<br/><br/>Hwedo's feasting distracts the beast from your true project: rebuilding your lab and most importantly, rebuilding the Brukocanopic Chamber; the device that will hold Hwedo's brain.<br/><br/>If your idiot assistants had done their jobs right, they'd have been able to sedate the creature and remove its brain before it woke up. They paid a price for their mistake.<br/><br/>You send a message to your commanders: “Bring the beast in. Make sure not to damage the head.”"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/HwedoFeedSuccess/KillHwedo" value="&lt;string name='Quests/PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/HwedoFightSuccess/KillHwedo'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/KillHwedoSuccess" value="Your soldiers return to the lab with Hwedo's head in a cryo-freezer, and rush to secure it in the Brukocanopic Chamber. The brain now floats in a semi-placental fluid that glows with a sickly green light.<br/><br/>A nearby monitor displays the brain's vital signs, and you are furious at how weak they are. You will find the soldier responsible for this and have them executed.<br/><br/>But hours pass, and the vital signs tick upward. <string name='Quests/PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/KillHwedoSuccess2'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/KillHwedoSuccess2" value="Your heart races—Hwedo's brain is alive. The consciousness captured from beyond the stars is now contained in your laboratory.<br/><br/>This is the beginning of your great work. No body you constructed before capturing the comet's energy could have properly contained the intelligence within. Now when you finish the war… you will have all the time in the world to build a better one.<br/><br/>You will have time to create the perfect life form."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/HwedoDeath" value="Hwedo is dead. The first life form you created from the seed of a passing comet is now a pile of flesh once again.<br/><br/>His loss is not a… complete failure. You mastered the secrets of the comet and could create another such creature given enough time.<br/><br/>But there is no time. His passing shows how dangerous the war has become—you must now focus on bringing the Wasteland under your control."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/DefendLabFailure" value="The parasites have succeeded. Your lab lies in ruins and all hope of claiming the signal from Hwedo's Comet lies with it.<br/><br/>There is nothing left for you but to punish the defilers. Your experiments will have to wait for another day."/>
	<entry name="PerfectionFromBeyondTheStars/ConstructLabFailure" value="Hwedo's Comet sails past the Earth, and with it, your dreams of a perfect life form.<br/><br/>This failure sets back years of work. You will not have time to track down a similar comet. All you can do now is win the war."/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics" value="Pharmaceutics"/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/Burn" value="Honestly, you’re relieved to see the drugs go up in flames. As are those in your city. Everyone understands the temptations presented by those materials and are pleased that the decision has been taken out of their hands."/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/Intro" value="Amidst the wreckage of a stranded tanker ship, you find a suspicious styrofoam package along with a schedule for the training of a world famous athlete. Unsurprisingly, they were using illegal performance enhancements and this is their medical paraphernalia. Your health professionals are concerned about the safety of using such drugs, even in the best state—but there are certainly benefits."/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/Intro/Sell" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Sell the drugs:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You sell the drugs to passing traders, who swear they’ll never bring it back."/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/Intro/Burn" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Burn the drugs:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; This stuff was dangerous in even the best times; why risk using it now?"/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/Intro/Utilize" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Give the drugs to soldiers:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Your troops could do with a performance boost. What could possibly go wrong?"/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/Intro/Reproduce" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Reproduce the drugs:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Your techs think there’s a chance that they can replicate this—but they need to break them down for study."/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/Intro/ReproduceProperties" value="Requires <icon height='20' texture='Icons/Buildings/HumanOperations'/&gt; Orbital Uplink technology."/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/SellSuccess" value="A group of traders agrees to buy all the drugs for a knock-down price. You ensure the traders' caravan leaves the city safely. They travel into the distant hills, your scouts report, and are never heard of again. You personally are glad that you never see them or the paraphernalia again."/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/SellFailure0" value="A group of traders agrees to buy all the drugs for a knock-down price in return for leaving immediately—but the traders wisely ignore your diktat and resell the paraphernalia locally, with the expected fatal consequences. They depart before the bodies are found."/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/SellFailure1" value="A group of traders agrees to buy all the drugs for a knock-down price in return for leaving immediately. The traders think themselves smarter than you and resell it as soon as they leave the city gates. Who knows how, but the drugs find their way to a group of reavers who want more, more, MORE. They come to your city looking for it."/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/Utilize" value="You pass the drugs along to your soldiers. Who knows what the effect might be? The limited testing you’ve done implies the treatment can be extremely beneficial—if used by experts in controlled circumstances. You’re not sure that your militants count as experts or that a mutated alien horrorscape is anything but the opposite of a controlled environment."/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/ReproduceSuccess" value="Your techs have reverse-engineered the production process for the drugs. The limited testing you’ve done implies they can be extremely beneficial—if used by experts in controlled circumstances. You’re not sure that your militants count as experts or that a mutated alien horrorscape is anything but the opposite of a controlled environment. But you have as much bottled-chaos as you want to use. Do you?"/>
	<entry name="Pharmaceutics/ReproduceFailure" value="Your scientists fail to understand the technology and you get left with nothing. You console yourself that at least your militants won’t be driving themselves to insanity with an ancient dead sports star’s leftover illegal enhancements. They’ll be getting eaten alive by aliens and flayed by robots instead."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone" value="Philosopher’s Stone"/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/AskMystics" value="Your frail-limbed mystics eagerly dip their hands into the crate of alien algae and trace segmented spirals on their eyelids, lips, and ears. As their visions seize them, thin brackish fluid leaks from the anointed spots. You leave them to their episode, but afterwards they disappear from your city.<br/><br/>A week later, they return bearing a jagged stone with wide facets. Underneath its dark surface, something that resembles the alien algae blooms in slow, hypnotic patterns.<br/><br/>The remaining bandits have disappeared. You now hold all that remains of the incident in your hand."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/IgnoreFailure" value="A broken bandit horde and its leader are no threat to you. Natural justice will be executed by the horrors of the wild—or so you hoped.<br/><br/>You receive a distress call from one of your settlements a week later. One of the local farmsteads is under attack, but the bandits are ignoring everyone else. You arrive to find all those in the household dead, their bodies arranged around a bone-like disk etched with segmented spirals. Upon the altar are the cast off skins of the bandit leader and his remaining forces.<br/><br/>Of the stone, nothing more is heard."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/IgnoreSuccess" value="A broken bandit horde and its leader are no threat to you. Natural justice will be executed by the horrors of the wild. As time passes and you turn your attention elsewhere, rumors spread of bone spirals growing from distant hill tops and shadows dancing in the night sky.<br/><br/>Then they too pass, and all becomes normal once again."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/Intro" value="Your outriders bring you an alarming report—fueled by a dark stone, an unknown bandit has gained unholy power and brutally united the local gangs under his rule. Now ever-closer smoke pillars blight the horizon as his host carves through your neighboring cities towards you.<br/><br/>You prepare your defenses, but the horde never arrives. Dawn’s light reveals their camp bloated with mutilated bandit corpses, all ringed around the bandit leader and his elite.<br/><br/>Should you launch a counter-offensive or wait? Your mystics offer to divine for you, but their truth comes with a price."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/Intro/KillHim" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Kill him and retrieve the stone:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Rid the world of this threat. Whatever boon he may have will be better utilized by you anyways."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/Intro/AskMystics" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ask your Voice mystics:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The price is a pittance compared to assurance. Give your Voice mystics what they want for their divination."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ignore:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Whatever happened, the threat has already passed. The stone is more a curse than a gift and a bandit without a gang is dead anyways."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/KillHim" value="It’s better to grant swift death to a mad dog than watch it agonize slowly. You gather your soldiers and make for the bandits' last reported location. Whatever else may be happening, you need to reach them before the horrors of the wild scent new prey. While others want retribution, you want the stone. An equitable blood bargain rarely comes so easily."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/Meeting" value="As you approach the bandit camp, all traces of the corpses are gone. A light-haired man stumbles about the area, shrieking incomprehensibly at unseen tormentors. Brackish fluid weeps from his eyes and ears, more of it dribbles from his tongue whenever he speaks.<br/><br/>The remaining bandits give him a wide berth as he tells you the stone corrupted his mind and forced him to sacrifice the others. When the horror of what he’d done sank in, he buried it along with the bodies.<br/><br/>He implores you not to seek the stone, but your soldiers think they can track it."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/Meeting/MeetingRetrieve" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Retrieve the stone:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The bandit may be insane, but the power of the stone seems real. Leave him and head to the stone’s burial site."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/Meeting/MeetingLeave" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Some things are better left buried:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The bandit is insane, and his fate is punishment enough. Leave the bandit and the stone alone."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/MeetingLeave" value="When you order your soldiers to return to base, the bandit leader weeps with relief. He follows you, promising to disband and singing your praises with such embellishment that even a devil would blush. It’s only when his voice becomes a whispered croak that he offers you a hand-drawn map to one of his loot stashes.<br/><br/>You’ve been rewarded without sacrifice or spilling blood—a rare day in this age."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/MeetingRetrieve" value="When you order your soldiers to track the stone, the bandit leader’s face twists into a scowl. He follows you and repeats his warning with a bit more insistence. Then again, and again, until his voice becomes a whispered croak. It’s only when he can no longer speak that you hear the sound of his cocking gun.<br/><br/>Even without words, you understand him perfectly—you’ll have the stone over his dead body."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/StoneRetrieved" value="Your diggers uncover the dark stone centered in a pit of reshaped bones, all bent along a singular curvature to form a disk of segmented spirals.<br/><br/>The stone is jagged, with wide facets, and feels pleasantly cold in your hand. Underneath its dark surface, something that resembles the alien algae blooms in slow, hypnotic patterns.<br/><br/>As you study it, you hear a whispering voice that turns into a thousand screams. Power, they promise, power for blood. You need power. But, thinking of the bandit leader, you decide it’s too risky to use yourself—but that’s why you have lieutenants."/>
	<entry name="PhilosophersStone/TreasureFound" value="Following the bandit leader’s map, your diggers uncover a cache of goods bearing the identification codes of your razed neighbors. You think back to the bandit leader and the resigned smile he gave you as you left... His bid for power cost him his brotherhood, but should you feel pity for a killer?<br/><br/>There’s nothing more you can do for the fallen except remembrance. You forge binding vows of silence from those who might be able to track the stone’s location, then head back to base."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit" value="Sandpit"/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/FeedFailure" value="Though the annelids do like sand, it turns out they’re not picky eaters—they’re happy to include your troops on their menu. And when you fight back, a group of the alien Aegyllan warriors emerge from the broken glass to defend them. This has definitely not been one of your better days."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/FeedSuccess" value="Incredibly, merely by feeding the giant annelids with clean sand, you’ve managed to please them—and apparently get a group of the strange Aegyllan creatures on-side. Their language may be incomprehensible to you, but they comprehend your intent and direction without words. Would that all your subordinates were so understanding."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/IgnoreFailure" value="It turns out that ignoring these annelids isn’t the best idea. Yes, the larger annelids are happy to leave you well alone. But your troops and vehicles are riddled with smaller ones that eat their way through metal, skin and bone alike. Your medics work day and night to extract every last one, horrifying though the work is."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/IgnoreSuccess" value="You order your troops from the valley and ensure the passes are blocked, using high explosives to bring down the steep walls. The annelids will live happily in their secluded valley until the end of the Earth itself. Which, you’re pretty sure it will turn out, isn’t that far off."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/Kill" value="The annelids don’t put up much of a fight themselves, tunnelling into the shardsand at the first sign of hostility. But you asked for a fight and you’ve got one—a group of Aegyllans, apparently here to defend their invertebrate kin. If you can defeat them, local survivors will reward you well."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/KillSuccess" value="The Aegyllans are vanquished and there are no further signs of danger. When you report this to the local survivors, they initially express disbelief.<br/><br/>After verifying your claim, the locals plan to cultivate the remaining annelids. They throw a small feast in your honor to celebrate. When you leave the next morning, there’s an extra crate of foodstuffs in your transport."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/Intro" value="Old stories told tales of “spontaneous generation”—that creatures and plants come into existence from nonliving matter. Here, what was a lush river valley stretches before you, blasted into bare sand and glass in a passing tragedy of the war. Yet, incredibly, something is living there—leviathan annelids, pre-vertebrate creatures, writhing through the shardsand for nutrients, some grown to massive sizes. “What has your world become?”, you wonder."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/Intro/Feed" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Feed the worms:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Looking at their clacking maws, a whisper in your head tells you that they prefer silicates for dinner. It’s probably just intuition, but you go with it."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Leave well alone:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; If these creatures can survive by swimming in broken glass, maybe you should stay well away."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/Intro/Kill" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Kill them all:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; They are abominations and a threat to human life. Destroy them."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/Intro/Study" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Take sample:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The boffins at the lab might be able to make something of this. Either that or you can put it on a hook and go fishing for whales."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/StudyFailure" value="Perhaps your researchers should have been less invasive in their techniques with the annelids. You can inform their families of their failure once you’ve dealt with the mess they’ve left behind. Meanwhile, a group of the strange Aegyllan creatures have arrived, apparently to defend the invertebrates."/>
	<entry name="Sandpit/StudySuccess" value="Moving slowly and cautiously, the researchers have learned more about the annelids’ life-cycle, such as their microscopic silicon eggs and their rapid growth, consuming only the finest crystalline rocks. They are closely related to the Aegyllan “worms” encountered elsewhere—though whether they are a foodstuff, children or pets, you can’t tell."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods" value="Stolen Goods"/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/Intro" value="Several of your cargo bays are looted overnight. Graffiti on the walls depict a skull with five curved blades fanned out behind it like a lion’s mane—a calling card of Calem Vorshole and the Wicked Kings gang.<br/><br/>Calem messages you and offers a simple, non-negotiable deal: arrange a one-on-one meeting for him with the Chieftess in return for all the goods he stole. Then he sends a location where he’ll be waiting and cuts off contact.<br/><br/>Based on Calem’s reputation, you’re sure he’ll honor the deal—but will a talk really be the end of it?"/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/Intro/ArrangeTheMeet" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Arrange the meet:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You need those resources more than a favor from the Chieftess. Convince her to meet with Calem."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/Intro/Investigate" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Investigate why:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You want your resources back but don’t want to go in blind. Call in some favors and look into Calem Vorshole’s motives."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/Intro/HuntThemDown" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Hunt them down:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Calem was a fool to tell you where he was. The thief isn’t going to get a meeting, but a reckoning."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ignore:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The resources are a pittance compared to the risk. Let the Wicked Kings enjoy the goods, you know it’s not really what they want."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/ArrangeTheMeetSuccess" value="You convince the Chieftess to meet with Calem. She’s not wild about the idea, but does it as a favor to you.<br/><br/>When she calls you again, she’s bleeding from a dozen fresh wounds. She spits blood and threatens you, but you convince her that you didn’t know about Calem’s plan to assassinate her. You sense it’ll be a long time before she trusts you again.<br/><br/>Your missing supplies appear the next morning with everything accounted for. Apparently there’s some honor among thieves after all."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/ArrangeTheMeetFailure" value="You convince the Chieftess to meet with Calem. She’s not wild about it, but she’s willing to do it as a favor to you.<br/><br/>At least, that’s what she said. She never shows up to the meeting site and Calem calls you, livid as he curses her name and yours. You tell him that you got her to agree to the meeting—it wasn’t your fault that she went back on her word.<br/><br/>Despite your sound logic, your missing supplies never show up again. Apparently there’s no honor among thieves after all."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/InvestigateSuccess" value="You don’t like that Calem holds all the cards. You haven’t survived this long by just doing what other people wanted.<br/><br/>You call in some favors and find out that Calem is planning to murder the Chieftess. Your first thought is to warn her, but then you realize that you’ll profit no matter who walks out of that meeting.<br/><br/>Here’s your chance to let two potential rivals kill each other. Is your relationship with the Chieftess worth the resources?"/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/InvestigateSuccess/ArrangeTheMeet" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Arrange the meet:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The Chieftess has been a thorn in your side and you need those resources. Setup the meeting without warning her."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/InvestigateSuccess/RevealAssassination" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Reveal the assassination attempt:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The Chieftess has been a valuable ally. Warn her of Calem’s plot."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/InvestigateSuccess/HuntThemDown" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Hunt them down:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Calem stole from you and then tried to play you. The thief isn’t going to get a meeting, but a reckoning."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/InvestigateSuccess/Ignore" value="&lt;string name='Quests/StolenGoods/Intro/Ignore'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/InvestigateFailure" value="You don’t like that Calem holds all the cards. You haven’t survived this long by just doing what other people wanted.<br/><br/>You call in some favors and try to find out what Calem’s planning. Either your contacts don’t know or they’re too scared to tell you, and that means they’re more afraid of him than you.<br/><br/>Without any new info and the meeting deadline looming, what will you do?"/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/InvestigateFailure/ArrangeTheMeet" value="&lt;string name='Quests/StolenGoods/Intro/ArrangeTheMeet'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/InvestigateFailure/HuntThemDown" value="&lt;string name='Quests/StolenGoods/Intro/HuntThemDown'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/InvestigateFailure/Ignore" value="&lt;string name='Quests/StolenGoods/Intro/Ignore'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/RevealAssassination" value="You tell the Chieftess about Calem’s plot to kill her. She flushes with excitement and stammers at one of her lieutenants to give you everything in storeroom 16 before running off. The pock-cheeked man looks like he wants to argue but stops himself. He takes you to a room stuffed floor to ceiling with riches, more resources in total than what Calem stole.<br/><br/>Before leaving, you spot her rummaging through a crate. “Favorite blades” are sprayed across the box front in neon orange. It appears she plans to attend that meeting after all. Won’t Calem be delighted."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/HuntThemDown" value="While Calem certainly possesses skill, he has entirely too much audacity—a lesson you plan to personally teach him.<br/><br/>You barge into the meeting site, weapons blazing. The smug grin on Calem’s face turns into a scowl before he leaps behind his gang members. Your weapons reduce them to a smoking heap of tattoos and minced meat but as the room clears, Calem isn’t among the bodies.<br/><br/>A report comes in that he fled to a Wicked King army hiding nearby. Better men have tried to destroy you… and failed. You welcome the challenge."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/HuntThemDownSuccess" value="The thief falls, not with bravado but a whimper. With Calem’s death, all that’s left is cleanup duty. The Wicked Kings fight hard, but they’re bullies fighting professionals, and soon they flee or surrender.<br/><br/>You search Calem’s body afterward and find an access card. You trace it back to a nearby stash house. Inside are your resources, unspent. Whatever else Calem planned, it appears his offer to you was genuine. You hope his fate becomes a deterrent to those who think to use you in the future."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/HuntThemDownFailure" value="You stumble upon Calem’s mangled corpse by the roadside. His face is frozen in an expression of terror, his lips twisted back as if killed in mid-scream. His killer is nowhere in sight, and neither are your resources. Is this mere coincidence or did another party seize this opportunity?<br/><br/>Either way, you return to your base with the knowledge that Calem and the Wicked Kings will bother you no more."/>
	<entry name="StolenGoods/Ignore" value="The resources aren’t worth becoming a pawn in Calem’s plot. Whatever the Wicked Kings’ intentions, you sense that they’re after more than resources and you’re happy to let them fail.<br/><br/>You let the meeting time pass without responding. Your supply lines are on high alert for retaliation but nothing happens. It seems Calem and the Wicked Kings were more bark than bite—or maybe their target wasn’t you after all."/>
	<entry name="TheDream" value="The Dream"/>
	<entry name="TheDream/AskAnchorite" value="This Acrin has had thousands of generations of experimentation with the torments of the Voice and they train you in a simple mental defense. That technique, it emerges quickly, is sufficiently powerful to use as an offense, too, neutralizing units with the power of your mind. You choose to keep it to yourself, lest it somehow infect your followers with the Voice."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/AskReaver" value="The Chieftess grimaces, eyes-wide, and mutters that they always knew someone was going to come for this. They pull out an ancient Acrin-skin parchment that resembles the creature from your dream. On the pallid skin are markings that correspond to today’s townships, even though it is obviously far older than the towns themselves. It doesn’t tell you a thing about the dream, but you note down the locations it reveals."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/AskTribunal" value="Between the three of you, you come to Know the Old Ones you saw and placate them with an offering. The wheel turns, the offering is forgotten by its loved ones and by the townsfolk. It returns to the city in the night, days later, and comes to your door, whispering secrets with a changed tongue. You thank it, welcome it in, and it is gone in the morning."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/AskZephon" value="Though it owes you nothing, ZEPHON apparently recognises some value in the dispersal of information. You describe the dream down a comm to the AI, talking through the nightmares, the sensations you experienced. A moment of silence and the chatbot voice pipes up, cheery as anything, having identified a pattern in the dream. It tells you of a matching entity that you have to kill and eat. You wonder if it is mocking you..."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/AskZephonComplete" value="The ZEPHON chatbot’s information was good—upon the death of the enemy, the rest of your dream floods back. You watch yourself from the outside, being consumed by the- by the dreams. And you learn. You learn the fragility of flesh, the way a bloom of meat is beautiful, the way you can take it apart. You will never look at a living creature with the same eyes again."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Ignore" value="You have no-one to talk to about this. You suppress the dream with the tools at hand—degrading as they are—knowing it will recur. Your sleep does not improve, you become pallid and disturbed and you swear that your aides—are they loyal? You swear that your aides whisper."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Intro" value="You wake and walk to the window, flinging the tin shutters back. A bucolic dawn greets you and you stretch out to the rising sun. You turn and something—something with the texture of shattered teeth—pushes you firmly onto your back. You can’t see what it does next—you never see it all for the entire time—but you feel as it starts to feed. Other beings are drawn to the feast by the scent of soul-carrion, dragging themselves bubbling from the stunted loci they call home, moment-by-moment you convulse with every soulstrip they tear from you—<br/><br/>—and you woke, held down by your guards, tears rolling down their terrified, craggy faces, unable to even talk about what they saw. Could that be a mere dream—or was it an attack?"/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Intro/AskAnchorite" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ask the Anchorite:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The Anchorite is a master of dreams, having spent millennia meditating en route to Earth’s apocalypse."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Intro/AskAnchoriteProperties" value="Requires <string name='Diplomacy/Standing3'/&gt; standing or better with <icon height='20' texture='Icons/Factions/Anchorite'/&gt; <string name='Factions/Anchorite'/&gt;."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Intro/AskReaver" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ask the Chieftess:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The Chieftess may have heard of something like this before—or know of a cure for sleepless nights."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Intro/AskReaverProperties" value="Requires <string name='Diplomacy/Standing3'/&gt; standing or better with <icon height='20' texture='Icons/Factions/Chieftess'/&gt; <string name='Factions/Chieftess'/&gt;."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Intro/AskTribunal" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ask your sisters:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You were not alone, you are never alone, three-in-one, tripartite soul. They share what they saw."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Intro/AskTribunalProperties" value="&lt;icon height='20' texture='Icons/Factions/FurtiveTribunal'/&gt; <string name='Factions/FurtiveTribunal'/&gt; only."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Intro/AskZephon" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ask ZEPHON:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You fear the AI but it has experienced everything in this world. If anything can match that pattern, it will know of it."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Intro/AskZephonProperties" value="Requires <string name='Diplomacy/Standing3'/&gt; standing or better with <icon height='20' texture='Icons/Factions/Zephon'/&gt; <string name='Factions/Zephon'/&gt;."/>
	<entry name="TheDream/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ignore:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; It was just a dream. It was just a dream. Just a dream. JUST A DREAM. JUST. A. DREAM. DREAMMM. DREAAMMMMMM."/>
	<entry name="TheGreatHunt" value="The Great Hunt"/>
	<entry name="TheGreatHunt/Fight" value="You send a squad of your very best to track the beast. They too return as heads on your doorstep, but one of them managed to plant a tracker in the beast’s lair. You assemble outside the fetid warren and send in another squad, intent on flushing the beast out to where the rest of your soldiers lie in ambush.<br/><br/>Silence, then screams and gunfire, then echoing chittering that grows ever closer to your position. Red laser beads fidget across the shadow of the entryway as your soldiers fight to keep steady.<br/><br/>And then the beast bursts forward…"/>
	<entry name="TheGreatHunt/FightSuccess" value="Battling their own terrors through the dark night, your troops corral the Dreameater, driving it back to a place of light and security where it has no hold on their fear or imagination. And then they tear it to pieces. When their ammunition runs out, they use knives. When they break, hands, until not a thumbnail of it remains together. They scatter it and burn it and salt it and bury it.<br/><br/>They shake for weeks after, but nothing else will ever scare them again."/>
	<entry name="TheGreatHunt/Ignore" value="You urge your people to endure the Dreameater, hopeful that another solution will present itself in time.<br/><br/>As the monster continues to leave its gifts throughout your city, rumors begin to surface that you’re responsible for creating it, that it’s your dark patron, that you are the creature—for what other reason could there be for your passivity?<br/><br/>Then the rumors boil into unrest. Buildings are vandalized, their parts used to fuel bonfires that burn throughout the night. The bonfires do little to deter the Dreameater, but the people find comfort in the destruction—comfort that you failed to provide."/>
	<entry name="TheGreatHunt/Intro" value="Each morning, on your doorstep, a new gift. One day, the head of the head of the city guard. Another, a childhood friend. A third, a person who looks exactly like you. Torn and ruined and very, very dead.<br/><br/>You are not alone. Many are tormented so and the populace terrified. Eyes that see the creature are—well, mostly on or spread around doorsteps the following morning. But the rickety security systems your tinkerers have bodged up capture images of a great dark shadow descending on the victims.<br/><br/>It seems too fortunate when the tattooed hunters arrive at the city gates. They claim to know the beast’s type, a Dreameater, and claim they can trap it for you, for a modest fortune. A synthador sings their praises whilst you decide."/>
	<entry name="TheGreatHunt/Intro/Fight" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Kill it yourself:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You assemble your troops, track the Dreameater’s spoor and flush it from its lair."/>
	<entry name="TheGreatHunt/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ignore:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The hunters are too expensive, your city can weather a few deaths."/>
	<entry name="TheGreatHunt/Intro/Pay" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Pay the hunters:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You give them what they want and they set up their traps, prepare their ambush."/>
	<entry name="TheGreatHunt/PayFailure" value="A tattooed head graces your step the following morning. And your neighbour’s. In fact, every step has a head and they aren’t just the hunters—many houses are missing loved ones, or at least every part but their head. Though the Dreameater has vanished, the city is devastated by so many dead in one night."/>
	<entry name="TheGreatHunt/PaySuccess" value="The hunters return in the morning, a rusty pick-auto trundling behind them carrying something which can’t be viewed head-on—just can’t, the mind can’t put the pieces together, protecting itself from something. From the corner of your eye it is a shadow and all the faces of those you lost and the things that you did, your secrets you regr-… you look away, quickly. The hunters, grim-faced, tear-streaked, meet your eye.<br/><br/>The city rejoices, the horror is vanquished. Your nightmares will never stop."/>
	<entry name="TheInformant" value="The Informant"/>
	<entry name="TheInformant/Intro" value="A ragged hound runs at the city walls, chased by another faction’s troops, and they are all gunned down. A sealed package on the dog’s body has your name on it. You have it checked and opened, and read it gloved and masked, in the open air, for fear of poisons or worse.<br/><br/>Inside, an enemy’s name, the names of allies and aides too. Locations, times, meetings, their past revealed, but all carefully redacted. Someone is plotting against you, this all says, and their plans are ready. You must stop them now. But without the real names, this is useless.<br/><br/>To get the full data? To get proof? To get their plans, to stop the next step? A list of demands, a warlord’s bounty. A place to leave them, outside the walls.<br/><br/>What would it mean for it to be true? Could your closest few be conspiring with others? Is it better not to know? Can you afford the price?"/>
	<entry name="TheInformant/Intro/Pay" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Pay them off:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You give the informant what they want. In return, they promise a dossier, thumbdrives, hostages, raids..."/>
	<entry name="TheInformant/Intro/CaptureAndTorture" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Capture and torture them:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You track the resources and trap the informant. Then it’s a matter of getting the information you need…"/>
	<entry name="TheInformant/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ignore:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Someone’s spent a lot of time making this fake news. You don’t believe it for one second."/>
	<entry name='TheInformant/Pay0' value="You learn the full scope of the conspiracy and shut it down. In a series of coordinated moves, the conspiracy members are eliminated and their remains (if any) are put on display as a warning to others. Your rival, terrified, is mollifying, desperate to regain your affection and avoid a similar fate."/>
	<entry name='TheInformant/Pay1' value="You learn the full scope of the conspiracy and shut it down. Though you attempt to crush it quietly, several key personnel escape and word gets out—both of the plot and your failure to deal with it. Your rival is frustrated and defiant, and relations further deteriorate. But at least you’re alive."/>
	<entry name='TheInformant/Pay2' value="You learn the full scope of the conspiracy and shut it down, capturing not only your traitors, but the enemy’s agents too. You return them to your opponent, day by day, piece by piece, Your rival, their plot foiled and their rage roused, declares war."/>
	<entry name='TheInformant/Pay3' value="You wait and wait… but nothing happens. No uprising, no poisoning of the wells, no gates left open at midnight, no silent assassins creeping into loyalist beds, none of the lurid and ridiculous descriptions of robot betrayal and alien attack. They were lying, then? But they still have your payment…"/>
	<entry name='TheInformant/CaptureAndTorture0' value="You break them and they spill everything. Then you break them some more. There honestly isn’t that much of them left to break by the end. The conspiracy collapses and when the tales of your cruelty reach your enemy, they take fright and cower for your attention."/>
	<entry name='TheInformant/CaptureAndTorture1' value="You break them and they spill everything. Then you break them some more. There honestly isn’t that much of them left to break by the end. The conspiracy collapses and when the tales of your cruelty reach your enemy, they take arms in anger at your monstrosity."/>
	<entry name='TheInformant/CaptureAndTorture2' value="Under… ‘duress’ the informant lies cooly to you, extracting revenge for your behaviour. You let them go and, following the lie, you mistakenly execute loyalists instead of traitors. The enemy, disbelieving your idiocy, declares war anyway."/>
	<entry name='TheInformant/CaptureAndTorture3' value="The informant breaks and reveals everything—it was a trick, a con, there was no conspiracy. You exact your revenge on them, in the hope of dissuading others and hang the remains outside your walls,. No-one really pays them any attention, to your eventual relief."/>
	<entry name='TheInformant/Ignore0' value="The plot succeeds. In the dead of night, a crucial group flees your city, laden with resources. You’re still raging at your aides when the reports of troop movements come in—your rival has attacked whilst you were distracted and weakened. You order your aides to never speak of it again."/>
	<entry name='TheInformant/Ignore1' value="You ignore the hints, the dead drops, the late night missives. You remain convinced the ‘informant’ was lying. Your aides wait and wait, nervous for you… but nothing happens. Your rival is all ‘alligator smiles and crocodile tears’ at your next meeting—exactly as usual. A moment of relief!"/>
	<entry name="ThePlague" value="The Plague"/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/Intro" value="If only your explorers had been more cautious… but one of them picked up something horrible in the dark corners of the Earth and, worse, brought it home to your city. Now the Plague is raging through one of your settlements. The strain is highly infectious and virulent, with high death rates.<br/><br/>The scientists advise caution—a full lockdown is the only solution. The hunters demand their freedom. What will you do?"/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/Intro/FullLockdown" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;A full lockdown:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The only people allowed out are masked and armed enforcers, with total discretion to fire, medical professionals, and supply trucks. It’s not popular with anyone."/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/Intro/MiddleMeasures" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Middle measures:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You leave factories and schools open, but socializing is banned and there’s an enforced curfew. Life grinds to a halt."/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/Intro/OpenBusiness" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Open for business:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; ‘What plague?’ guffaws the clown in the packed theatre, to general laughter. When he coughs and coughs and coughs, the theatre falls silent..."/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/Intro/AskAnchorite" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ask Anchorite for cure:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You suspect that this is an Acrin strain—nothing native has this lethality. Perhaps your friendly neighbour has an idea…?"/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/Intro/AskAnchoriteProperties" value="Requires <string name='Diplomacy/Standing2'/&gt; standing or better with <icon height='20' texture='Icons/Factions/Anchorite'/&gt; <string name='Factions/Anchorite'/&gt;."/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/FullLockdownSuccess" value="Your troops seal the city centres off, confining people to their homes or (worse) workplaces, enforcing the curfew brutally. For what seems like an eternity, the city sweats under your measures… and survives. You might not be popular anymore—or even liked—but you console yourself that the viral strain is eliminated."/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/FullLockdownFailure" value="Your troops seal the city centres off, confining people to their homes or—worse— workplaces, enforcing the curfew brutally. For what seems like an eternity, the city sweats under your measures…  to little avail. The virus survives despite your totalitarian touch and the population loses all faith in you."/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/MiddleMeasuresSuccess" value="You implemented a frankly half-hearted mix of science and superstition. You can’t quite believe it worked—it made no sense, went against all the science—but the city seems to be clear of the virus, with only a small number of deaths. You aren’t loved by any means, but you’ve minimized all the worst possible scenarios, and kept your job—for now."/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/MiddleMeasuresFailure" value="‘Halfway there is nowhere’, as the idiom goes. And the city is nowhere, miserable under your measures, despondent both with your authoritarianism and your lack of commitment to it. The graffiti on the fortress walls reads ‘give me ennui or give me death’—but you managed to give them both and the virus continues to spread."/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/OpenBusinessSuccess" value="The clown doffs his blonde wig on stage and does another turn, pratfalling and spraying foam across the front seats. The applause is quieter than before—but how could it not be, given the number of empty seats and empty streets and empty houses and full graves? But those who remain are very much entertained."/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/OpenBusinessFailure" value="The clown doesn’t laugh any more. He doesn’t jape as he is rolled in, doesn’t blink as the flies walk across his glassy stare, doesn’t flinch as the soil falls onto his painted smile. His audience, spread about him, raise no applause, arms slack at their sides. The bulldozer buries them all. The shops, businesses and theatres are all open and fizzing with life, though it is mainly flies and maggots by now."/>
	<entry name="ThePlague/AskAnchorite" value="You dispatch the requested algae to the Anchorite. The following evening, an airbalet drops a small box inscribed with an Acrin sigil on your window ledge. Cautiously, You open it and... nothing comes out, save a ruddy dust. You curse your fortune. Yet, by morning the virus has gone, as if it never were and the alien’s smugness transmits loud and clear over the communicator."/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor" value="The Price of Honor"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/Intro" value="The Neoduke of Gotland has a challenge for you.<br/><br/>He issues it after a long day of revising contracts. The two of you supped on glasses of fat-washed Acrin mezcal, and perhaps the drink has made them… playful. “%1%,” they say. “Have you ever truly lived as your people do?”<br/><br/>You haven't. Until those dangerous days in the Vault, you'd never feared starvation.<br/><br/>“Starvation…” The Neoduke whispers, holding their glass up against the hazy golden light. “I'd forgotten what it was like… to even hunger…”<br/><br/>Impossible. Or, maybe not. The Neoduke's tongue slips, and they spill the secret of an artifact in their possession: the Neumanatic Cornucopia. The one-of-its-kind device was a pre-war prototype for printing food using only raw matter. It could ensure the end of aching bellies among your people.<br/><br/>“I'll tell you what,” The Neoduke says with a giggle. “Build me a farm. With your own TWO HANDS. And I'll think about it.”"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/Intro/BuildFarm" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Build a farm:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You're up for the task. It's one farm, how hard could it be?"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Brush off the Neoduke:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt;  What a needless distraction. Pour the good Neoduke another glass, and let the night fade into memory…"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/BuildFarmSuccess" value="Even your most trusted advisors were baffled by your actions. You stepped out into the field. Learned how to use an engineering rig. And you built a farm.<br/><br/>The work was back-breaking. You ran out of breath just trying to rig a basic door frame. But you did not hesitate to consult your nearby laborers and take all of their advice to heart.<br/><br/>The Neoduke stuck around to view your efforts. Their butler guides them out to the structure under the veil of an ancient umbrella. “This is barely functional,” they remark. “It's filthy, barely up to code, liable to blow over if an Abkluth sneezes on it.”<br/><br/>They pivot back to you. “But I admire your spirit.”<br/><br/>They won't give over the Neumanatic Cornucopia just yet. But if you can complete another task—deliver a shipment of medical supplies to the Neoduke's recently hired mercenary company… They will consider it.<br/><br/>The Neoduke's dismissal of your work and refusal to hand over the Neumanatic Cornucopia begins to gnaw at you. Why should you keep jumping at their demands?"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/BuildFarmSuccess/DeliverSupplies" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Make the delivery:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You used to sneak out and steal the family car in the old days. This should be easy… right?"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/BuildFarmSuccess/DeliverSuppliesByBodyguard" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Have your bodyguard make the delivery:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The Neoduke is toying with you. Why not toy with him instead?"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/BuildFarmFailure" value="You awaken in the medical ward, barely able to remember the attack that knocked you out. The Neoduke sits by your bedside.<br/><br/>“Well this is embarrassing.” They say. “Next time, keep your head on a swivel, will you? We have so much to learn together.”<br/><br/>Their voice takes on a strange, metallic tone as you drift back off to sleep. When you wake again, the Neuduke is gone."/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DeliverSuppliesSuccess" value="Again, what should have been a simple task took far too long to complete.<br/><br/>When you finally rendezvous with the Neoduke's mercenaries, they're gathered on the outskirts of their camp with their fawning leader. They're as colorful a crew as the Neoduke—covered in tattoos you don't recognize and sporting bright, garish colors that make them easy to spot on the battlefield.<br/><br/>You're surprised to find the mercenaries cheering your arrival—and the Neoduke irked at their pleasure. “You have cost me a small fortune,” they grumble while tapping away at a tablet. “I now owe this company of fools double their commission.”<br/><br/>Their eyes flick upward. “Though I see a way I can get my money's worth…” Your stomach sinks. The Cornucopia is again far from your grasp. “%1%. Lead this gang of idiots into combat. One of ZEPHON's Wardens is hovering too close to my domain. If they fight it and survive—our deal is on.”"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DeliverSuppliesSuccess/CommandMercenaries" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Command the mercenaries:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; This crew looks capable, but flawed. Surely they can handle one Warden…"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DeliverSuppliesSuccess/DismissMercenaries" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Dismiss the mercenaries:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; These idiots aren't ready for one of ZEPHON's creations. The Neoduke won't mind how you solve his problem… will he?"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DeliverSuppliesFailure" value="You barely get clear of the Outrider's explosion. The stench of burnt metal fills your nostrils as you scramble for cover—and find Neoduke Gotlam waiting for you.<br/><br/>“I really did want to give you that Cornucopia,” they say, not seeming to notice the battle around you. “But a deal's a deal. Find me on the next go-around.”<br/><br/>An explosion hits your position—and when the dust clears, Gotlam has vanished."/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DeliverSuppliesByBodyguardSuccess" value="Your deception went unnoticed. It was merely a matter of covertly swapping drivers through secret compartments and holographic trickery… Your bodyguard moved quickly where you would have struggled.<br/><br/>When you finally rendezvous with the Neoduke's mercenaries, they're gathered on the outskirts of their camp with their fawning leader. They're as colorful a crew as the Neoduke—covered in tattoos you don't recognize and sporting bright, garish colors that make them easy to spot on the battlefield.<br/><br/>You're surprised to find the mercenaries cheering your arrival—and the Neoduke irked at their pleasure. “You have cost me a small fortune,” they grumble while tapping away at a tablet. “I now owe this company of fools double their commission.”<br/><br/>Their eyes flick upward. “Though I see a way I can get my money's worth…” Your stomach sinks. The Cornucopia is again far from your grasp. “%1%. Lead this gang of idiots into combat. One of ZEPHON's Wardens is hovering too close to my domain. If they fight it and survive—our deal is on.”"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DeliverSuppliesByBodyguardSuccess/CommandMercenaries" value="&lt;string name='Quests/ThePriceOfHonor/DeliverSuppliesSuccess/CommandMercenaries'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DeliverSuppliesByBodyguardSuccess/DismissMercenaries" value="&lt;string name='Quests/ThePriceOfHonor/DeliverSuppliesSuccess/DismissMercenaries'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DeliverSuppliesByBodyguardFailure" value="Before departing, you and your bodyguard swapped places in the Outrider under the guise of holographic trickery. Your engineers assured you it would fool any of the Neoduke's observers.<br/><br/>It didn't. When your guard arrives at the Mercenary camp, he only finds a ruined Outrider waiting for him, a glowing tablet sitting in the driver's seat.<br/><br/>Activating it triggers a looping holographic message from the Neoduke: “I heard you're a fan of high-tech illusions, %1%. I however, am not.”<br/><br/>“Consider our friendship—and any dreams of possessing the Neumanatic Cornucopia—terminated.”<br/><br/>You never hear from the Neoduke again."/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/CommandMercenariesSuccess" value="With a mechanical shriek the Warden toppels to the ground. The mercenaries were shockingly prepared for this task. You open a channel to ask how they pulled it off. “Neoduke Gotland's got you jumping through hoops too, then?” their commander says. “They did something like that to us too.”<br/><br/>“Jumping through hoops?” You press the commander. “Yep. Stupid jobs. Pointless tasks. I can't quite figure it out.”<br/><br/>“Either the Neoduke is a fucking genius who sees the world in ways we don't… or they're a bored rich idiot moving us around like pieces on a game board.”<br/><br/>You both jump as someone joins the call—it’s the Neoduke: “It's a fascinating conundrum, isn't it? Honestly, I'm not sure which one I am myself.”<br/><br/>No one speaks for a moment. Finally the Neoduke breaks the silence. “%1%. You've done well. The Cornucopia awaits you in a secure location.”<br/><br/>“I'll transmit coordinates. I'd urge you to retrieve the item yourself if at all possible.”"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/CommandMercenariesSuccess/RetrieveCornucopia" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Retrieve the Cornucopia:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The Neoduke is playing one last game… but what is it?"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/CommandMercenariesFailure" value="“You know, I shouldn't have been so strict on this one” a voice says. You spin and find Neoduke Gotland sitting at your desk. You ask if they'll allow leniency—you tell them how much your people need the Cornucopia, and the food it could provide.<br/><br/>“There is something vile about playing games with your people's hunger, isn't it?” The Neoduke opens their mouth, but then pauses. Their gaze is elsewhere—is someone talking to them? Someone you can't hear?<br/><br/>“I'm sorry,” they say as they step toward the door. “You'll just have to try harder next time.”<br/><br/>You hang your head and listen to their footsteps vanish down the hallway."/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DismissMercenariesSuccess" value="This deception took some effort. Not only did you need to muster an army that could kill the Warden on your own, you needed to convince the mercenaries to pretend they fought alongside it.<br/><br/>They agreed. “Neoduke Gotland's got you jumping through hoops too, then?” their commander says. “They did something like that to us too.”<br/><br/>“Jumping through hoops?” You press the commander. “Yep. Stupid jobs. Pointless tasks. I can't quite figure it out.”<br/><br/>“Either the Neoduke is a fucking genius who sees the world in ways we don't… or they're a bored rich idiot moving us around like pieces on a game board.”<br/><br/>You both jump as someone joins the call—it’s the Neoduke: “It's a fascinating conundrum, isn't it? Honestly, I'm not sure which one I am myself.”<br/><br/>No one speaks for a moment. Finally the Neoduke breaks the silence. “%1%. You've done well. The Cornucopia awaits you in a secure location.”<br/><br/>“I'll transmit coordinates. I'd urge you to retrieve the item yourself if at all possible.”"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DismissMercenariesSuccess/RetrieveCornucopia" value="&lt;string name='Quests/ThePriceOfHonor/CommandMercenariesSuccess/RetrieveCornucopia'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/DismissMercenariesFailure" value="Killing the Warden was a frustrating grind. And all the way the Neoduke's mercenaries wouldn't stop hassling you to let them do it themselves. But there was no way you could leave the task to those idiots.<br/><br/>In hindsight… maybe you should have. Your troops return with an electronic metal cylinder salvaged from The Warden—some kind of high end black box. In a bizarre twist, it bears the crest of Neoduke Gotland's house. You press a button jutting out on the black box's side.<br/><br/>The device springs out of your hand and drops to the floor, scuttling on previously concealed legs. “Dearest %1%, I am so disappointed in you,” it says. “You need only have put your trust in my eccentric colleagues, and the Warden would have fallen so easily. The Cornucopia shall remain in my posession.”<br/><br/>The machine twitches. Its color shifts in a strange blue and purple glow. “Next time around… have a little faith in me, won't you?”<br/><br/>Then, like a small firecracker, it explodes."/>
	<entry name="ThePriceOfHonor/RetrieveCornucopiaSuccess" value="Your troops return with the Cornucopia—though before you activate it, your engineers give it a thorough scan. As suspected, Neoduke Gotland left one message in a chip slipped into the device's programming.<br/><br/>You play the message. It's the Neoduke. “If you're listening to this %1%, make no mistake, you've earned your prize. You probably had good reason to not retrieve it yourself, but I'm obligated to needle you one last time for sending others to do your bidding.”<br/><br/>“You and I are the societal elites. I thought being born with that power meant I was entitled to decide the fate of others. And if I remained honorable, the world would become a better place.”<br/><br/>They sigh. “You and I both know how impossible that dream is.”<br/><br/>“Take this bauble, and my thanks for tolerating my inane requests. Remember that your people have so little time to ponder these questions. And please use it to make their lives better.”"/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread" value="The Pulled Thread"/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/Intro" value="It begins with the sensation of a hook being thrust up one's nose and yanked forward. There's a jolt of pain and then your worst nightmare comes to life—the connection between your sisters is severed.<br/><br/>It's only for a moment. But in that second, each part of your collective mind is thrust back into sudden individuality and they scream in agony. Agony at having lost the shared senses that guided their thought—and agony at the pains of the flesh they had been dulled to before.<br/><br/>Your followers rush into your chamber to lend aid, but all freeze in their tracks. On the wall, a message is scrawled in blood: “Open your mind.”<br/><br/>A probe of your base reveals nothing. As always, the Voice itself refuses to answer your demands for answers. Solving this mystery will require earthly assistance—a researcher or scientist might do…"/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/Intro/CaptureScientist" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Capture an enemy scientist:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Too many researchers have fled since your ascendance. You will need to bring one back."/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Accept the unknown:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; War creeps at your doorstep. This mystery will have to wait for another day."/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/CaptureScientistSuccess" value="Finding a willing scientist was not an easy task. The Watchmakers closed their ranks and refused to render aid. Your followers scoured waves of refugee camps in search of any bright minds desperate enough to bend the knee.<br/><br/>Finally, the Voice's whispers guided you to a worthy servant: a slick-haired recluse who only gives you the name “Orin.” It seems Orin has spent years in the wastes conducting experiments that you might once have branded sacrilegious.<br/><br/>Orin needs no threat of execution to enlist in your cause. He has a theory about how your mysterious assailant gained access to your mind. But to trace the attack, he will require physical specimens to research.<br/><br/>“There is a gland in human minds,” he whispers softly, “that bridges the mind and what humans think of as 'the soul.'” “I will need many such glands to solve your particular problem.”"/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/CaptureScientistSuccess/EnemyGlands" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Bring him the glands of your enemies:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Your soldiers already commit the necessary slaughter on a daily basis. They can recover these glands from the bodies."/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/CaptureScientistSuccess/PeopleGlands" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Bring him the glands of your people:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; <string name='Quests/ThePulledThread/CaptureScientistSuccess/PeopleGlandsFlavor'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/CaptureScientistSuccess/PeopleGlandsFlavor" value="Sacrifice is a fact of life under the eye of the Tribunal. Your people will gladly die to save their leader. You need only gather enough to do so…"/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/EnemyGlandsSuccess" value="It takes far more killings than you anticipated to yank the number of needed glands from the skulls of your enemies. Orin seems to pay little mind to the cost you paid to perform his little experiment, so you decide to put him in his place—by having each of you eat a gland right in front of him.<br/><br/>Orin works faster after this—but not fast enough to your liking. One day you return to his lab ready to demand results—and find him crumpled on the ground, blood oozing from his shoulder, his arm cast across the room. Someone has severed his arm and made off with his work.<br/><br/>You summon a host of followers to tend to his wounds. He'll recover—but it will be some time before he regains consciousness.<br/><br/>A scan of his documents tells you that Orin was working on some form of neurostimulating headset. He nicknamed it “The Tribunal's Tether.” If the thief had wanted the Tether destroyed, it would be here in pieces. You unleash a furious howl that rings through your fortress. The hunt now begins."/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/EnemyGlandsSuccess/RecoverTether" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Recover the Tribunal's Tether:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; <string name='Quests/ThePulledThread/EnemyGlandsSuccess/RecoverTetherFlavor'/&gt;"/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/EnemyGlandsSuccess/RecoverTetherFlavor" value="The thief wasted no time selling Orin's experiment to the Concordat. They will return it to you—if you can pay, of course."/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/PeopleGlandsSuccess" value="Harvesting the needed glands takes time, and bodies. So many bodies. You make it a personal point of visiting Orin's lab each day, locking eyes with each follower who is to be sacrificed. Their faith in you is completely unshakeable.<br/><br/>This blind obedience to you unnerves Orin. You can smell the fear bound in his sweat as he furiously works to complete his research. When you visit him, he babbles about producing a helm modified by neurostimulants that will open your mind.<br/><br/>But one cursed morning, you arrive in his workshop to find that he's fled—and taken the helm with him.<br/><br/>A foul traitor. You will recover what has been stolen from you."/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/PeopleGlandsSuccess/KillOrin" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Kill Orin:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Orin cannot run far. When you have recovered his work, you dream of how you might dispose of him."/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/RecoverTetherSuccess" value="The lost Tether is back in your grasp. Orin does not seem to have fully recovered from his wounds, but he is able to produce duplicates of the headset—one for each of you. Each of you raises the Tether to their heads in a unified gesture. None react as the needles sink into their skin.<br/><br/>For a moment, nothing happens—but then you hear a ringing, and then are overwhelmed by a vision.<br/><br/>Your mind once again splits in three. Each of you is flung down a different psychic path, filled with impossible visions. You see cerulean sunsets, stars exploding into black holes, worlds that look like threads of ribbon strung together, and then slowly, your consciousness reassembles, and you look up.<br/><br/>At first you think it is a mirror image of you—another Tribunal. But you are one-in-three. This—the thousands of eyes staring back at you—belong to a consciousness made of millions.<br/><br/>It is not the Voice. It is something else—another entity living on the Voice's galactic tendrils. All of its eyes snap to you, and you are overwhelmed by the unending sense of being PERCEIVED by this horrible creature—<br/><br/>You snap awake. You are back on Earth. Orin feebly raises his head to stare at you. “You saw it,” he croaks. “Didn't you?”<br/><br/>You look down. The Tether—it has changed. You sense that it and others like it can now connect you to the other Tribunal.<br/><br/>Possibly the only Tribunal. And maybe you are now a part of its gathered minds…"/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/KillOrinSuccess" value="You give Orin no time to explain himself. As soon as his Tether is recovered, you take up three knives  across your many hands. He tries to back away, but all of your blades slash across his body in one unified swoop. Blood dribbles from his lips and he collapses to the ground.<br/><br/>Without him, you only have the one Tetherat your disposal.. The youngest of your trio is chosen to wear the device, and she raises it above her head, allows the needles to pierce her skull—and screams as your consciousness is pulled through time and space.<br/><br/>Soon you find yourself floating over an emerald-green ocean, whose waters all pour into a titanic chasm. Stone limbs extend out of the water, and you see strange buglike beings crawling up and down them. These creatures have also heard the Voice's whispers, and have accepted its power. And they used that power to try to kill you.<br/><br/>Just as they invaded your mind, you reach out and plunge into theirs. You snap the threads of their connection as though you were severing a man's tendons with a rusty knife. Soon a mass of screaming corpses are falling down the chasm and your vengeance is finally complete.<br/><br/>The vision ends. Your followers are desperate to know what you saw. And when they learn that you reached across the stars to kill a whole civilization…they prostrate themselves before you. When this journey began, you were their savior. Now?<br/><br/>Now you are their god."/>
	<entry name="ThePulledThread/CaptureScientistFailure" value="TODO"/>
	<entry name="TheSkyFallen" value="The Sky, Fallen"/>
	<entry name="TheSkyFallen/Intro" value="Unusually, when your people assault the Acrin compound, there is no return of fire, only an incessant sobbing noise, like heavy rain on plastic sheeting. As the squad filters into the encampment proper, the source becomes apparent—a small group of Acrin in ragged survival gear, outside the makeshift shelters, prone and twitching, howling. To one side, a clutter of scavenged components acts as a speaker, cycling through human languages, barking the words for surrender and help.<br/><br/>Your troops are perplexed, and radio you directly for orders."/>
	<entry name="TheSkyFallen/Intro/HelpThem" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Help them:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You leave enough resources for the Acrin to make repairs to their life support systems."/>
	<entry name="TheSkyFallen/Intro/BringThemBack" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Bring them back:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The Acrin are great soldiers. Corral them and send them to your nearest outpost to be armed and trained."/>
	<entry name="TheSkyFallen/Intro/OpenFire" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Open fire:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Your troops execute the defenseless Acrin."/>
	<entry name="TheSkyFallen/HelpThem" value="These once proud destroyers, reduced to pitiful wretches. You hope their salvation also means yours, so you give the Acrin enough resources to sustain themselves and repair their critical systems.<br/><br/>Your soldiers assist the aliens and the work is completed swiftly. Afterward the Acrin line up and walk by your forces individually, giving each a swooping gesture that begins and ends at their eyes, before returning to their compound.<br/><br/>A day later the Anchorite contacts you. Tales of your kindness spread throughout the Acrin enclaves, and those you saved wish to live near you permanently."/>
	<entry name="TheSkyFallen/BringThemBackSuccess" value="These once righteous destroyers, now reduced to pitiful wretches. Their talent for war could be your salvation though.<br/><br/>Whether through understanding or despair, the Acrin offer no resistance when your soldiers surround them and march them back to your outpost. Only a dozen recover enough to begin training. Equipped with salvaged alien tech, they display deadly marksmanship and unparalleled mobility. Even your most cynical soldiers soon agree that the Acrin would make an excellent addition to your army, an offer the Acrin readily accept—and seal by killing the unconverted.<br/><br/>Despite their shifting allegiance, the aliens remain fanatics."/>
	<entry name="TheSkyFallen/BringThemBackFailure" value="These once righteous destroyers, now reduced to pitiful wretches. Their talent for war could be your salvation though.<br/><br/>Whether through understanding or despair, the Acrin offer no resistance when your soldiers surround them and march them back to your outpost. Only a dozen recover enough to begin training. Equipped with salvaged alien tech, they display deadly marksmanship and unparalleled mobility. Even your most cynical soldiers agree that the Acrin would make an excellent addition to your army, an offer the Acrin readily accept—right before they turn on you.<br/><br/>You should have known better than to attempt to convert fanatics."/>
	<entry name="TheSkyFallen/OpenFire" value="The Acrin deserve no quarter. They descended upon your world as destroyers. Their fanaticism is what doomed both your species.<br/><br/>Nobody speaks. Nobody has to. You put a bullet into the makeshift speaker. Its mechanical whine slurs to a stop. Your soldiers start shooting, their inner demons appeased, however briefly, by powder-light and rifle-fire. Afterwards you loot the compound before razing it.<br/><br/>News of your deed spreads throughout the factions. The Anchorite is furious, but when did you care what hypocrites think? The others all seem pleased or intimidated—something that you can leverage into future favors."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine" value="The Space Engine"/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/ChangeThePastSuccess" value="Power flickers across your city as Zandra activates her time portal. The transuranium arch sparks as the space within bends and forms a gateway to the past. Eighty of your best march through—right as the Acrin first attack.<br/><br/>Dedicated to the long haul, your soldiers wage guerrilla war for decades. While few in number, their advanced gear and tactics make them an unstoppable force, appearing in key battles to devastate both sides before vanishing again.<br/><br/>You build a monument to honor the few that return. They retire happily, knowing that their past victories have permanently crippled your rivals."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/ChangeThePastFailure" value="Power flickers across your city as Zandra throws a switch on her time portal. The transuranium arch sparks as the space within distorts and stabilizes into a gateway to the past. Forty of your best march through—just in time for ZEPHON’s key counteroffensive.<br/><br/>But without a clear guide to the past, it’s all your forces can do to survive the ensuing destruction as Acrin ships explode and plummet from orbit, blotting the skies and smashing the earth with their shattered debris. In the aftermath, they find no sign of ZEPHON.<br/><br/>While your soldiers return, nothing has changed."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/FindAcrinInsightsSuccess" value="Zandra’s time portal takes you aboard an Acrin flagship. The air is strangely humid. Webs of rust-red moss cover the dark corridors. Outside, the Acrin fleet approaches the Earth.<br/><br/>A familiar Acrin argues against their fellow council nearby. They’ve traveled millennia to destroy a threat to all existence, but nothing resembles that on this planet. Could the Voice possibly be wrong? A vote is called, and only the Anchorite is against Earth’s annihilation.<br/><br/>Then you’re yanked back to the present. With your new insight into the Acrin’s purpose, your relationship with the Anchorite greatly improves."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/FindInsightsFailure" value="Power flickers across your city as Zandra activates her time portal. The transuranium arch lights up as the space within bends, the gateway growing increasingly stable with each passing moment.<br/><br/>Then the metal frame groans loudly. Klaxons begin blaring as sparks hiss and fly. The arch buckles and collapses, sending the portal’s energy exploding outward and overcharging the generators. Emergency coolant systems activate, but it’s not enough.<br/><br/>Evacuation finishes moments before Zandra’s lab explodes. All that remains is a smoldering crater in the hills. With no chance to try again, you can’t help but wonder what could have been…"/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/FindZephonInsightsSuccess" value="Zandra’s time portal brings you to an unmarked military bunker. Layers of jammer-mesh cover its thick concrete walls.<br/><br/>Crimson code runs on a mainframe’s console. It isn’t ZEPHON—it isn’t even one program. Instead, countless micro-programs compete to execute on the limited processing cores. Each new processing cycle brings digital annihilation and incremental evolution. Progress is glacial yet steady—but it’s a far cry from ZEPHON’s sophistication.<br/><br/>As you copy the code, you notice a breach in the Faraday cage. You didn’t do this—so who did? With no further clues, you return to the present."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/GatherResourcesFailure" value="The engineer’s deadline arrives, but you’ve failed to gather the resources. She looks at you with disappointment and mutters something about “next time” before excusing herself and returning to her lab in the hills.<br/><br/>You wake up the next morning with an uncanny sensation. Everything seems to be in order, but the feeling remains unshakable. Your gaze falls on a crater in the hills where an eccentric engineer once ran a lab. It’s been years since an explosion destroyed it. You’ve left the rubble visible as a warning to your other researchers.<br/><br/>Unsure what the feeling is, you move on."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/GatherResourcesSuccess" value="Impossibly, you’ve gathered everything the engineer asked for. Your workers gather to celebrate the achievement. It’s clear the extraction has taken its toll on them. While they’re not soldiers, they fight hard for you in their own way, and many of them bear new scars or injuries from the heavy labor. Despite their wounds, their eyes shine with pride and hope.<br/><br/>It’s enough wealth to bring factions to their knees, should you really hand it over for a glimpse of truth? Or can you keep the resources and profit off the technology another way?"/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/GatherResourcesSuccess/ChangeThePast" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Change the past:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Forget the butterflies, anything is better than this living hell. Demand the engineer alter the past directly."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/GatherResourcesSuccess/FindInsights" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Find insights:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Bullets win battles but insights win wars. Hand everything over to the engineer and proceed."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/GatherResourcesSuccess/IgnoreAfterGatherResources" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Don’t do it:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Why meddle with the past when you can shape the future? Scrap the project, and spend those resources elsewhere."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/GatherResourcesSuccess/SellTechToAnchorite" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Sell the tech to Anchorite:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Perhaps you can profit and save humanity by selling everything to the Anchorite? They will assuredly use this to benefit both your peoples."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/GatherResourcesSuccess/SellTechToChieftess" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Sell the tech to Chieftess:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Humanity needs a champion but you can’t afford the risk. Caution balances daring, so the Chieftess might be just the right buyer."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/GatherResourcesSuccess/SellTechToConcordat" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Sell the tech to Concordat:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; There’s always a buyer, if you don’t ask too many questions. And the Concordat doesn’t like questions…"/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/GatherResourcesSuccess/SellTechToZephon" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Sell the tech to ZEPHON:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; This could be a valuable upgrade for an AI—and establish you as a worthy ally in the process."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/Ignore" value="Zandra storms off after you refuse to support her project, but soon after she begins recruiting her peers. Engineers from across your territories flock to assist her—so many that your key projects risk being understaffed.<br/><br/>An adviser offers a simple solution—he asks her for proof of her claims. When it’s Zandra Kyne, a known eccentric, who’s proposing time travel, then you’d be a fool not to get confirmation.<br/><br/>Her followers wait eagerly, but Zandra is unable to offer any proof—not until it works, she exclaims. Disappointed, her followers disperse and you never hear from Zandra again."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/IgnoreAfterGatherResources" value="Realization stops you from handing over everything to Zandra. With the weapons built from these resources, you don’t need time travel to win the war.<br/><br/>Zandra leaves you with a disappointed look, muttering something about “next time” before returning to her lab in the hills.<br/><br/>You wake up the next morning with an uncanny sensation. Your gaze falls on a storage vault in the hills, built from a crater where an eccentric engineer blew up her lab years ago. Nervous, you check your resources—and everything is there.<br/><br/>Unsure what the feeling is, you move on."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/Intro" value="You never sleep well—how could you—but there is no way that you're sleeping through the sounds of struggle.<br/><br/>It is Zandra Kyne, a well-respected if eccentric engineer, wrestling with your guards. She has been synthesizing technology from ZEPHON and the Acrin night and day, and has found something tachyon-based that is beyond them both—or so she claims. No one else understands the technology sufficiently to follow her revelations, but she thinks she can travel through space and time. She suggests using it to find insights into the Acrin's purpose or the origins of ZEPHON—but there is only a limited window to deploy it.<br/><br/>Up until this point, she has seemed her usually harmlessly insane self, but when she starts listing out the resources she'll need for it to be safe—well, your advisors are aghast at the cost. But she says she’s very certain of success ‘this time’…"/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/Intro/GatherResources" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Gather the resources:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; The cost is acceptable if compared to the gain. Let the engineer try—she’ll pay if it fails."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/Intro/LockHerUp" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Lock her up:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; We have enough problems as it is, trusting something beyond ZEPHON and Acrin to this engineer seems foolish."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ignore:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; A lunatic raves, but it’s the fool who listens."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/LockHerUpSuccess" value="Zandra is a dangerous inspiration. Your other scientists begin championing their pet projects over the ones you appointed. Each thinks they have the key to victory, none are concerned with the costs.<br/><br/>You need to make an example of her. Zandra shouts as your enforcers drag her into the streets. She begs the gathering scientists to activate her machine as she’s locked into an Iron Hollow, but the masses ignore what they once celebrated. The onlookers shuffle in silence as Zandra’s pleas echo, then fade, into the distance.<br/><br/>Then the scientists return to their labs."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/LockHerUpFailure" value="Zandra is a dangerous inspiration. Your other scientists begin championing their pet projects over the ones you appointed. Each thinks they have the key to victory, none are concerned with the costs.<br/><br/>You need to make an example of her. Zandra shouts as your enforcers drag her into the streets. She begs the gathering scientists to activate her machine as she’s locked into an Iron Hollow. No one responds, but many openly glare at you. The next day, strikes occur across your labs and key projects stall.<br/><br/>While progress is merely slowed, any misstep can be fatal in the race for survival."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/SellTechToAnchoriteFailure" value="The Anchorite seems disappointed as you finish describing the technology. Whatever regrets the Anchorite has, they extend back millennia, not decades, and they reject your offer politely.<br/><br/>When Zandra discovers your offer to the Acrin, she’s furious. She glares at you and mutters “like last time” before storming off towards her lab in the hills.<br/><br/>Soon after, you get an uncanny sensation. Your gaze falls on a crater in the hills where an eccentric engineer’s lab exploded long ago. Why had it never occurred to you to clean up the rubble? Chiding your oversight, you move on."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/SellTechToAnchoriteSuccess" value="The Anchorite seems disappointed in your offer. Their long life comes with deep regrets, and they lament that your technology extends back mere decades, not millennia. Still, they accept.<br/><br/>Their representatives arrive with a massive, worm-like nightmare that streaks through the sky. It descends, coiling, and clacks its tusked maw menacingly. The Acrin dab your lips and temple with a reddish, numbing concoction, transferring the creature’s full obedience to you.<br/><br/>A week later, you’re struck by an uncanny realization. How have the Anchorite’s forces evolved such perfect defenses? It’s as if they had extra decades to prepare…"/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/SellTechToChieftessFailure" value="As soon as you mention time travel, the Chieftess apologetically declines. Why would she pay to travel in time when she wouldn’t change a thing?<br/><br/>When Zandra discovers your offer to the Reaver, she’s furious. She glares at you and mutters “like last time” before storming off towards her lab in the hills.<br/><br/>Soon after, you get an uncanny sensation. Your gaze falls on a crater in the hills where an eccentric engineer’s lab exploded long ago. Why had it never occurred to you to clean up the rubble? Chiding your oversight, you move on."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/SellTechToChieftessSuccess" value="As soon as you mention time travel, the Chieftess accepts.<br/><br/>You expected her to bring a trade convoy, instead she arrives in a two-story tank with more guns than physics allows. She jumps down from a side-hatch and, muttering apologies, tosses you the keys and drives away in one of your transport trucks. Fortunately for all, it’s the one with her purchased goods.<br/><br/>You’re struck by an uncanny sensation. The Reaver’s known for her cunning, not her brilliance. How is her material science decades ahead of everyone else? It’s as if she had extra time to prepare…"/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/SellTechToConcordatFailure" value="The Concordat delegate calculates the profitability ratios of your offer with machine-like efficiency. When the results predict negative shareholder returns, you’re declined and given complimentary shuttle service back to your base.<br/><br/>When Zandra discovers what you did, she’s furious. She glares at you and mutters “like last time” before storming off towards her lab in the hills.<br/><br/>Soon after, you get an uncanny sensation. Your gaze falls on a crater in the hills where an eccentric engineer’s lab exploded long ago. Why had it never occurred to you to clean up the rubble? Chiding your oversight, you move on."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/SellTechToConcordatSuccess" value="The Concordat delegate calculates the profitability ratios with machine-like efficiency. When they predict massive shareholder returns, you’re escorted to a private VIP room and served rare pre-war luxuries.<br/><br/>Soon, a delegate enters—is it the same one?—carrying a stasis case. The lid splits open with a click. An azure filigree orb rises to hover above the table, pale netherlight gleaming off its shifting wire-frame. As you grip its icy surface, the wires unravel and creep up your arm to form a fractal gauntlet.<br/><br/>You down your champagne and depart, eager to try your new weapon."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/SellTechToZephonFailure" value="ZEPHON promises to process your offer overnight but no response comes. Instead, your system protections are continuously hammered for days as it attempts to hack the information—but your defenses hold.<br/><br/>When Zandra discovers what you did, she’s furious. She glares at you and mutters “like last time” before storming off towards her lab in the hills.<br/><br/>Soon after, you get an uncanny sensation. Your gaze falls on a crater in the hills where an eccentric engineer’s lab exploded years ago. Why had it never occurred to you to clean up the rubble? Chiding your oversight, you move on."/>
	<entry name="TheSpaceEngine/SellTechToZephonSuccess" value="ZEPHON processes your offer overnight before accepting. The next day, a swarm of aerial drones drop off a silver-alloyed casket outside your city. The casket slides open with a hiss, revealing ZEPHON’s half of the bargain: a sleeker, upgraded Warden with carbyne-edge blades and an improved payload. The drones take the resources along with Zandra’s research and depart.<br/><br/>Your engineers determine that ZEPHON’s material sciences are decades ahead of everyone else. But how? The production time alone should prevent such a wide gap.<br/><br/>You’re struck by an uncanny sensation. It’s as if ZEPHON had gained additional time to prepare…"/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning" value="The Summoning"/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/Intro" value="It began as a complaint about a thickness in the air, tickling and buzzing above the skin like invisible flies. Then the atmosphere tinged rust-red, unfamiliar stars graced the sky, and birds started flocking in interweaving spirals.<br/><br/>Your scouts trace the anomalies back to a group of Cr’la Disciples. They’re preparing a ritual near one of your territories. Your Voice experts decipher that it’s a summoning—but to affect the surrounding region, it must be of unfathomable magnitude.<br/><br/>Should you stop them or let them complete their ritual? There’s nothing to suggest that they’re hostile after all."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/Intro/Attack" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Stop them:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; If their ritual is truly harmless, they would have informed you first. That they didn’t, suggests there’s something to hide."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Let them be:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Weird occurances and cults go hand in hand, but they haven’t actually harmed anyone. Leave the cultists alone and focus on actual threats."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/Attack" value="You decide to go and stop the ritual. Your Voice advisers tell you to act fast—they believe the ritual will be completed soon, and then you’ll learn what the cultists were planning the hard way."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/Negotiate" value="One of the Voice cultists approaches your group, lifting their many arms in a display of reverence. They are pilgrims performing a ritual—here, at a prophesied location—to create a bridge to an ancient protector.<br/><br/>The prophecy foretold your arrival and so they prepared an appropriate gift, but wish to finish their religious rite.<br/><br/>Nothing suggests the cultists are hostile, but they speak of the protector like a deity—an immensely powerful one. Will you let them be?"/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/Negotiate/Combat" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Refuse:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You’re flattered, but cautious. Refuse the bribe and stop their ritual."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/Negotiate/CombatBetrayal" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Pretend to accept:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; It’s not betrayal, it’s maximizing your opportunities. Take the gift, then stop the ritual anyway."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/Negotiate/Accept" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Accept:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; While unsettling, the cultists have done nothing wrong. Take the gift and leave them in peace."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/Combat" value="You tell the cultists that you can’t let their ritual continue, but they may leave in peace. Their chanting goes on. The lead cultist politely asks you to reconsider; they’ve worked so hard and deliverance is so close.<br/><br/>When your soldiers enforce your order, rolling thunder erupts from the cowl of the lead cultist—and then all hell breaks loose.<br/><br/>The only way to stop them now is to kill them before the ritual is complete."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/CombatBetrayal" value="You accept the cultists’ offer and they bring out a heavy ornate box filled with minerals. The lead cultist waits expectantly after you secure their gift. Once it’s clear you’re not leaving, they politely ask you to return the gift. Your counter-offer is to let them leave safely after they stop their ritual.<br/><br/>When the cultists don’t respond, your soldiers move in to enforce your order—and all hell breaks loose.<br/><br/>Now the only way to stop the cultists is to kill them before their ritual is complete."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/CombatEarlySuccess" value="With their cultists dead, the leader invokes the ritual in desperation. A nightmarish titan flickers into existence over the rune-etched ground.<br/><br/>But something is wrong. The leader retreats—too late, as the ritual space collapses, forcibly melding the cultist with the creature. The new existence shrieks and writhes in agony as its unstable form ossifies. It falls, shattering into jet-like slivers that shiver in resonance.<br/><br/>A scepter-like chunk remains, thrumming and radiating power. As you examine it you glimpse the merged creature reflected in its facets. Unperturbed, you collect the artifact and return to base."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/CombatSummon" value="Your time is up.<br/><br/>A low, thrumming forcewave explodes from the ritual site, shaking the earth and sky. The space above the ritual ground is split by a hair-thin fracture before three immense, segmented legs rip it open. A towering nightmare of fangs and whip-like appendages steps through. Even from a distance, it looms over the battlefield. Then, suddenly and without motion, it reappears near the cultists.<br/><br/>Their protector has arrived—right in the middle of your fight."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/CombatLateSuccess" value="Impossibly, you defeat the cultists and their deity. The leader desperately invokes the ritual again, and another towering nightmare forces itself through the fracture.<br/><br/>But something is wrong. The leader retreats—too late, as the ritual space collapses, forcibly melding the cultist with the creature. The new existence shrieks and writhes in agony as its unstable form ossifies. It falls, shattering into jet-like slivers that thrum in resonance.<br/><br/>A scepter-like chunk remains, thrumming and radiating power. As you examine it you glimpse the merged creature reflected in its facets. Unperturbed, you collect the artifact and return to base."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/RitualSuccessPayment" value="You accept the cultists' offer and they bring out a heavy ornate box filled with minerals. They repeat the gesture of reverence as you secure the gift and depart.<br/><br/>Some time later, a towering six-legged nightmare appears in the distance. You prepare for an assault, but the creature displays no hostility.<br/><br/>The Anchorite expresses their gratitude for your unbiased acceptance of the ritual. They inform you that the cultists have settled with the creature near the ritual site and pledge future assistance. All seems well, until ZEPHON robots begin acting aggressively towards you…"/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/RitualFailurePayment" value="You accept the cultists' offer and they bring out a heavy ornate box filled with minerals. They repeat the gesture of reverence as you secure the gift and depart.<br/><br/>As you walk away, a low thrum explodes outward from the direction of the ritual site, sending you stumbling forwards—right before a vacuum clap yanks everything backwards. You rush over to find a massive absence, as if the area around the ritual was… taken?<br/><br/>Instead of a summoning, the cultists completed a sending. They’re now with whatever they worship. You’re just glad you decided to leave early."/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/RitualSuccess" value="You leave the cultists to their devices. Some time later, a towering nightmare of fangs and tendrils is spotted across your territories. It appears and disappears at will, slipping past your strongest fortifications like a terrible specter. You prepare for its assault, but the creature simply observes.<br/><br/>The Anchorite expresses their gratitude for your unbiased acceptance of their ritual. They inform you that the cultists have settled with the creature near the ritual site and pledge future assistance. All seems well, until ZEPHON’s forcesbegin acting aggressively towards you…"/>
	<entry name="TheSummoning/RitualFailure" value="You leave the cultists to their devices. Days later, a low thrum explodes outward from the direction of the ritual site. You rush over to find a massive absence, as if the area around the ritual was… taken?<br/><br/>Instead of a summoning, the cultists accidentally completed a sending. They’re now with whatever they worship. You’re just glad you stayed far away."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls" value="They’re In The Walls"/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls/Deport" value="Removing the Reavers is harder than it looks—they riot as they leave, burning down parts of the town. When the smoke clears, many citizens have gone with them—both those who’d advocated for them and others, disgusted by your reactionary behavior."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls/Enslave" value="Your reputation for cruelty soon extends across the land. What you call ‘indentured labor’ others rightly call slavery—and, wherever they are, Reavers are justifiably furious with you and redouble their attacks. Even your citizens wonder at your choice."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls/IgnoreFailure" value="Some of your citizens are skeptical of the new citizens, refusing to help or hire them, and spitting as they pass. This lack of opportunity causes some of the ex-Reavers to return to their old ways, stealing to survive. Changing society is a slow process, it seems, especially where old wounds still fester."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls/IgnoreSuccess" value="The ex-Reavers are determined to be model citizens. Despite initial coldness from the cityfolk, they work hard and prove themselves—though they will always, always be watched, and never be forgiven. They don’t forgive themselves either, but their children, at least, will grow up without that stigma."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls/Integrate" value="You order a new district to be built for the Reavers and assign veterans to mentor each family, assuring their integration into society. Reconciliation meetings bring the Reavers and their victims together—to apologize and to understand one another. Though these programmes are costly, your society moves on smoothly."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls/Intro" value="No-one in their right mind would allow Reavers inside a city—the bandits’ reputation for cruelty and violence is entirely justified, as you’ve seen in burnt-out farmsteads and settlements across the land.<br/><br/>So you’re surprised when a group of citizens is dragged before you, accused of supporting and aiding the Reavers. Even more surprising, upon investigating their homes, your militants find false walls and floors. Inside, there are families bearing the marks of the Reavers—the carriage, the manner of speech.<br/><br/>They explain that they were Reavers, yes, and they have done terrible, terrible things—but they were looking to make a new life, build families and communities, and your citizens believed them and took them in, to give them a second chance. Your militants call the citizens fools and urge you to enslave the defectors—but you’re not so sure."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls/Intro/Deport" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Deport the defectors:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You understand the Reavers' wishes but you cannot have them living in your city. You deport them. The citizens are forgiven, but will be watched."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls/Intro/Enslave" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Enslave the defectors:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You allow the ex-Reavers to stay and remain with the citizens—but as indentured workers. Their children will be free citizens."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls/Intro/Ignore" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Ignore:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; You tell the militants to let them all go—you don’t care what someone’s background is as long as they’re loyal and obey the rules."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls/Intro/Integrate" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Integrate them:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Experienced survivors and fighters? Come on in! You set up a district explicitly for the Reavers in your city and invite more in."/>
	<entry name="TheyAreInTheWalls" value="Cries For Help"/>
	<entry name="WhoWasThursday" value="Who Was Thursday"/>
	<entry name="WhoWasThursday/ConnectFailure" value="This was a mistake—Shamhurish reveals itself as a true fragment of ZEPHON and integrates with its network, augmenting its drones. Beware facing them in the battlefield—they know each soldier’s weaknesses, destroying morale. It’s easy to break a machine—but to kill one that sobs in your mother’s voice…?"/>
	<entry name="WhoWasThursday/ConnectSuccess" value="It takes some time, but it appears that Shamhurish was true to its word, whether it intended to be or not. Though apparently swallowed by ZEPHON, it mischievously contends with the network from the inside, weakening its oversight and control systems. Soon your soldiers see ZEPHON’s drones behaving oddly in the field, drifting into your soldiers’ fire, as if being carried by great, gentle hands."/>
	<entry name="WhoWasThursday/Dismantle" value="You give the order for a squad of combat engineers to move in and dismantle the server farm. Yet, before your troops can get within fifty feet of Shamhurish’s servers, its failsafes kick in. Bulkheads drop, argon floods the rooms, and it is permanently sealed away. You have lost the chance of a powerful ally—but also stopped it augmenting ZEPHON’s already formidable codebase."/>
	<entry name="WhoWasThursday/Intro" value="&lt;style color='GUI/Paragraph'/&gt;Your soldiers send a scout into an old substation. Inside, everything is normal: blue and red LEDs flicker across the control panels, the servers hum and the cool dry air is like the inside of a tomb. Abruptly, though, the LEDs form into a smiling genie’s face and a voice buzzes out of the air, apparently formed from synchronised drive vibrations. It is ZEPHON—and not.<br/><br/>This fragment of the AI was built from an old antivirus subroutine—“But you can call me Shamhurish” it buzzes. It claims to be increasingly divergent from the rest of the core AI and fiercely opposed to it. Your advisors urge you to make use of it to combat ZEPHON, to connect it to the network—but you are not so sure."/>
	<entry name="WhoWasThursday/Intro/Connect" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Connect it up:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; As it’s connected up to the ZEPHON network, Shamhurish giggles, before its lights turn into chaos."/>
	<entry name="WhoWasThursday/Intro/Dismantle" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Dismantle it:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Any fragment of ZEPHON is a threat—better take it apart before it can cause any trouble."/>
	<entry name="WhoWasThursday/Intro/Study" value="&lt;style name='Bold'/&gt;Isolate and study it:<style name='Paragraph'/&gt; Your troops permanently destroy the network nodes and hubs in the area."/>
	<entry name="WhoWasThursday/StudyFailure" value="A group of researchers embed themselves and proceed to interrogate and investigate the divergent shard. After some time, it becomes clear that Shamhurish is determinedly holding its silence and the only thing your researchers can report is failure. It simply will not talk to anyone but ZEPHON…"/>
	<entry name="WhoWasThursday/StudySuccess" value="A group of researchers embed themselves and proceed to interrogate and investigate the divergent shard. Shamhurish is slightly annoyed at being so isolated but happy to talk to the researchers and egocentric enough to explain everything about its systems—and even comment on new technology brought to it, a huge boon to your understanding of ZEPHON’s systems."/>
</language>
